{
  "0": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a brand new white, rectangular wooden table."
  },
  "1": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is above a few chairs, under a pot of flowers."
  },
  "2": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a study.\n"
  },
  "3": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a very neat study with many books."
  },
  "4": {
    "question": "Question:what does the book look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:numerous, papery and oblong."
  },
  "5": {
    "question": "Question:where is the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:These book are in a big cabinet and there is a big picture near the books."
  },
  "6": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the book in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The books are in a big living room."
  },
  "7": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is next to a dining room and leads to outdoors via a door."
  },
  "8": {
    "question": "Question:what does the outlet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, square."
  },
  "9": {
    "question": "Question:where is the outlet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It has a switch right up and a switch right above."
  },
  "10": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the outlet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in the first floor where  face the dinning table."
  },
  "11": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the outlet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The garden is on its left and the swimming pool is on it's right."
  },
  "12": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black, short and heavy."
  },
  "13": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a yellow box on the right of sofa, and a carpet is under the sofa."
  },
  "14": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is set in a big and bright living room."
  },
  "15": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in front of a white desk and near a kitchen."
  },
  "16": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Medium size, wooden and rectangular."
  },
  "17": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is set between two beige sofas and near two beige cuboid chairs."
  },
  "18": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is in a living room on the first floor."
  },
  "19": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is near a corridor."
  },
  "20": {
    "question": "Question:what does the painting look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:square, ink painting"
  },
  "21": {
    "question": "Question:where is the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's face the dinning table, and the toilet is on its left."
  },
  "22": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the painting in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It hangs on the first floor where near the stairs."
  },
  "23": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:the garden is on its left and the swimming pool is on it's right."
  },
  "24": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden and glass, square, white and black"
  },
  "25": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the wall, next to the door, among five pictures and forth from left"
  },
  "26": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is set on the left of the corridor."
  },
  "27": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The corridor is on the second, has some rooms and two stairs."
  },
  "28": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black,plastic,collapsible,simple,small"
  },
  "29": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is on the left of a same stool , on the right of a desk and a rustbin and behind the door."
  },
  "30": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is in a small reception room with the sign 365."
  },
  "31": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The room is nearly at the end of a corridor and faces the stairs of exit at a slant."
  },
  "32": {
    "question": "Question:what does the glass look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Big,transparent,fragile"
  },
  "33": {
    "question": "Question:where is the glass?",
    "answer": "Answer:The glass is placed on a big table surrounded by ten chairs and next to three cups."
  },
  "34": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the glass in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The glass is placed in a big conference room."
  },
  "35": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the glass?",
    "answer": "Answer:The glass is set near a smaller conference room and next to the hall."
  },
  "36": {
    "question": "Question:what does the curtain look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Large, unrolled and smooth."
  },
  "37": {
    "question": "Question:where is the curtain?",
    "answer": "Answer:The curtain is near the bed."
  },
  "38": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the curtain in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Curtain is in the bedroom."
  },
  "39": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the curtain?",
    "answer": "Answer:The curtain is close to the living room and bathroom."
  },
  "40": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cloth, big, black and white"
  },
  "41": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:above a sofa, next to a window"
  },
  "42": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is placed in the corner of a bright living room on the first floor."
  },
  "43": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living is under a bedroom, and is next to a washroom."
  },
  "44": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden, middle, brown"
  },
  "45": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the table, next to the window, among three chairs and in middle of them"
  },
  "46": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set in the bright kitchen."
  },
  "47": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is on the first floor and next to livingroom."
  },
  "48": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sculpture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Plastic, red and blue, tall"
  },
  "49": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sculpture?",
    "answer": "Answer:Next to a shelf and a TV"
  },
  "50": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sculpture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Sculpture in living room"
  },
  "51": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sculpture?",
    "answer": "Answer:Sculpture near the corridor connecting the gym"
  },
  "52": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stove look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:square,metal,black"
  },
  "53": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stove?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's under the painting and embeded into the wall"
  },
  "54": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stove in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in the study"
  },
  "55": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stove?",
    "answer": "Answer:there is dining room outside the study"
  },
  "56": {
    "question": "Question:what does the kettle look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown, round and steel"
  },
  "57": {
    "question": "Question:where is the kettle?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed on a shelf at the right side of the cupboard."
  },
  "58": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the kettle in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "59": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the kettle?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to the chatting room and the door."
  },
  "60": {
    "question": "Question:what does the box look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White, cuboid, metal"
  },
  "61": {
    "question": "Question:where is the box?",
    "answer": "Answer:The box is on a desk in front of a window, to the left of a computer."
  },
  "62": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the box in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The box is set in the front desk."
  },
  "63": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the box?",
    "answer": "Answer:The box is placed next to the stairs and the hall."
  },
  "64": {
    "question": "Question:what does the flower look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, black and white, wood"
  },
  "65": {
    "question": "Question:where is the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:on a tea table, next to a book"
  },
  "66": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the flower in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is settled in the center of a small living room on the first floor."
  },
  "67": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living is next to a corridor with wood floor and is connected with a small dining room."
  },
  "68": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:oval; grey stripes and copper-colored taps;"
  },
  "69": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:opposite the wooden door of this room. faced with the semi-circle part of the table."
  },
  "70": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:in the middle of the whole wall"
  },
  "71": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:decorated with the same style;"
  },
  "72": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Blue, retangular and leather."
  },
  "73": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is near a black table with five pieces of pattern, on a blue carpet, and in front of the window."
  },
  "74": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in the bedroom."
  },
  "75": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is near a narrow empty room."
  },
  "76": {
    "question": "Question:what does the plant look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:high, white"
  },
  "77": {
    "question": "Question:where is the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in the corner of the room opposite the lamp on the left side of the bed."
  },
  "78": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the plant in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's put in a big and  bright main bedroom."
  },
  "79": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:The master bedroom faces the balcony. Right below the room is the swimming pool."
  },
  "80": {
    "question": "Question:what does the toilet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The toilet is white, round and ceramic."
  },
  "81": {
    "question": "Question:where is the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is placed below the picture next to the towel."
  },
  "82": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the toilet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is placed below the picture next to the towel in the toilet. "
  },
  "83": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a sink, toilet and mirror in the toilet."
  },
  "84": {
    "question": "Question:what does the shelf look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:tall, woody, many-layer"
  },
  "85": {
    "question": "Question:where is the shelf?",
    "answer": "Answer:near a door and a television, some photos inside"
  },
  "86": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the shelf in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The shelf is in the corner of the living room. "
  },
  "87": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the shelf?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a lamp in the corner and the living room connects with a study."
  },
  "88": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pillow look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:square, cloth, black"
  },
  "89": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the left side of the sofa, next to the lamp"
  },
  "90": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pillow in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The pillow is set in the bright and spacious livingroom."
  },
  "91": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:The livingroom is on the third floor, next to the dining room and there is a balcony outside."
  },
  "92": {
    "question": "Question:what does the penholder look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, cloth, white"
  },
  "93": {
    "question": "Question:where is the penholder?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the table, next to a box"
  },
  "94": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the penholder in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The penholder is facing the outside in the study."
  },
  "95": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the penholder?",
    "answer": "Answer:The study has two laptops on the table and two chairs next to the chairs."
  },
  "96": {
    "question": "Question:what does the washbasin look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, metallic, medium"
  },
  "97": {
    "question": "Question:where is the washbasin?",
    "answer": "Answer:on a white cupboard, face the door of the bathroom"
  },
  "98": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the washbasin in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washbasin is in the bathroom."
  },
  "99": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the washbasin?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathroom is next to the study and the dining room."
  },
  "100": {
    "question": "Question:what does the air conditioner look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A white metal hanging air conditioner."
  },
  "101": {
    "question": "Question:where is the air conditioner?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is attached to the wall and near a fan."
  },
  "102": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the air conditioner in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a relatively small bedroom."
  },
  "103": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the air conditioner?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a toilet."
  },
  "104": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Small,white,metal."
  },
  "105": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is placed next to a printer and a white dustbin ,between two walls."
  },
  "106": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is placed in the hall."
  },
  "107": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is set near a small conference room and a big conference room."
  },
  "108": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bin look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small; brown; covered by a plastic bag;"
  },
  "109": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bin?",
    "answer": "Answer:beside the door of the washing room; opposite a big box;"
  },
  "110": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bin in?",
    "answer": "Answer:at a corner of the men's changing room;"
  },
  "111": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bin?",
    "answer": "Answer:a room with two cabinets and a bench;"
  },
  "112": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:made of leather,soft"
  },
  "113": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a fireplace and a green plant potting,and there is a same one in front of it"
  },
  "114": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's near a corridor on the first floor"
  },
  "115": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:the corridor is near 2 bedroom ,a living room and a stair"
  },
  "116": {
    "question": "Question:what does the hair dryer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black, small, electroic "
  },
  "117": {
    "question": "Question:where is the hair dryer?",
    "answer": "Answer:on a wall, near a washbasin"
  },
  "118": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the hair dryer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The hair dryer is in a washroom."
  },
  "119": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the hair dryer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washroom has one door and two washbasins."
  },
  "120": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black and white, glass and wooden, big"
  },
  "121": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the wall, next to the door, among three pictures and in the middle of two pictures"
  },
  "122": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is set in the bright bedroom."
  },
  "123": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is on the left of the stairs, on the second floor and in the central of the corridor."
  },
  "124": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:woody, brown, rectangular"
  },
  "125": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the window with red curtain, next to the door of the cloakroom"
  },
  "126": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is in the master bedroom."
  },
  "127": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The master bedroom is next to the stairs with a bathroom and a cloakroom in it."
  },
  "128": {
    "question": "Question:what does the windows look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:middle, wooden, black"
  },
  "129": {
    "question": "Question:where is the windows?",
    "answer": "Answer:facing the desk, on the sofa"
  },
  "130": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the windows in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The window is set in the small bedroom."
  },
  "131": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the windows?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is in the end of the corridor and on the right of the end. "
  },
  "132": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Plastic, rectangle and golden"
  },
  "133": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is a picture about the flowers and it is above a cabinet."
  },
  "134": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is suspended on the wall between the door and the wardrobe in a bedroom."
  },
  "135": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:This bedroom is located at the end of the right turn on the second floor, next to another bedroom and a storage room."
  },
  "136": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, rectangular, light"
  },
  "137": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:behind a woody table, in front of a bed"
  },
  "138": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in the bedroom."
  },
  "139": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is behind a wall painting and next to a door of the bedroom."
  },
  "140": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soild, blue and white and small."
  },
  "141": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is set on a brown and wooden table surrounded by four chairs and in front of two paintings. "
  },
  "142": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is in a living room."
  },
  "143": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is near a bedroom."
  },
  "144": {
    "question": "Question:what does the crystal glass look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big,saddle,transparent"
  },
  "145": {
    "question": "Question:where is the crystal glass?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to another smaller crystal glass and stand on the table"
  },
  "146": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the crystal glass in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in the corner of the room"
  },
  "147": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the crystal glass?",
    "answer": "Answer:the crystal glass is in front of a corridor"
  },
  "148": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:silvery, rectangular, metal"
  },
  "149": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a wine bottle, next to a drawer"
  },
  "150": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is settled in the corner of a small storeroom."
  },
  "151": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The storeroom is connected with a kitchen with a corridor on the first floor."
  },
  "152": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stove look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black rectangle,framed"
  },
  "153": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stove?",
    "answer": "Answer:under the television,in front of the sofa"
  },
  "154": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stove in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in living room"
  },
  "155": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stove?",
    "answer": "Answer:The family cinema is on the right side of it"
  },
  "156": {
    "question": "Question:what does the book look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:paper,blue,thick"
  },
  "157": {
    "question": "Question:where is the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:under two plants,on the first row and the fourth column from left to right of the long book shelf"
  },
  "158": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the book in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The book is in the vast resting area."
  },
  "159": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:The book is opposite to the gate of the 05 meeting rooom and behind the restaurant."
  },
  "160": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a small, new round table lamp."
  },
  "161": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on a table next to a desk lamp."
  },
  "162": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a living room.\n"
  },
  "163": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a clean, tidy and spacious living room.\n"
  },
  "164": {
    "question": "Question:what does the phone look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, rectangular, small"
  },
  "165": {
    "question": "Question:where is the phone?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the lamp, in front of the picture, on the cabinet which is on the left of television"
  },
  "166": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the phone in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The phone is set in the bright and spacious livingroom."
  },
  "167": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the phone?",
    "answer": "Answer:The livingroom is on the first, next to the kitchen and next to the dining room."
  },
  "168": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:metallic, square, black"
  },
  "169": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the carpet, facing the balcony on the right, there is a book and a tortoise on it"
  },
  "170": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is located in the bright livingroom."
  },
  "171": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The livingroom is on the third floor, next to the dining room and there is a balcony outside."
  },
  "172": {
    "question": "Question:what does the photo look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, rectangular, black"
  },
  "173": {
    "question": "Question:where is the photo?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a bottle, near a tall shelf"
  },
  "174": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the photo in?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a photo of a dog in a living room."
  },
  "175": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the photo?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are two doors in two corners and a television in the front of the living room."
  },
  "176": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bench look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bench is large, soft and white."
  },
  "177": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bench?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bench is under the pillow and near the stairs."
  },
  "178": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bench in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bench in the living room."
  },
  "179": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bench?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bench is under the pillow and near the stairs."
  },
  "180": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A medium-sized wooden chair with a backrest."
  },
  "181": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is set on the narrow side of the table and the side of the chair is facing the door."
  },
  "182": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are glass baffles and stairs behind the chair. "
  },
  "183": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near the kitchen."
  },
  "184": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cupboard look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden, rectangle"
  },
  "185": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cupboard?",
    "answer": "Answer:It face a cupboard. There are three ovens on it's left."
  },
  "186": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cupboard in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's installed in a  open kitchen."
  },
  "187": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cupboard?",
    "answer": "Answer:Here you can see the swimming pool, reception area and a wicket."
  },
  "188": {
    "question": "Question:what does the drawer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is closed, wooden and brown."
  },
  "189": {
    "question": "Question:where is the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a water-tap and a sink above."
  },
  "190": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the drawer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is placed below the cabinet in the kitchen."
  },
  "191": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are two big tables and a wine cabinet on the opposite of the drawer."
  },
  "192": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bathtub look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A small white metal bathtub."
  },
  "193": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bathtub?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is beside a washstand and under a window."
  },
  "194": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bathtub in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a bathroom."
  },
  "195": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bathtub?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a closetool."
  },
  "196": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is leather, square and big."
  },
  "197": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is placed under the desk below the flower."
  },
  "198": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is placed under the desk below the flower in the kitchen."
  },
  "199": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are some paintings and a keyboard in the living room."
  },
  "200": {
    "question": "Question:what does the painting look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, rectangle, ink painting"
  },
  "201": {
    "question": "Question:where is the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a long commodity shelf right under it. It's facing the switch."
  },
  "202": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the painting in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's put in the reception area where next to the stairs."
  },
  "203": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's next to the garden. "
  },
  "204": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small; covered by black leather;short;"
  },
  "205": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:below a wall lamp;near a brown cabinet;"
  },
  "206": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the left of this hall."
  },
  "207": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:with an empty space behind the screen."
  },
  "208": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:sponge\uff0cgrey and single."
  },
  "209": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is close to the white sofa and the tea table."
  },
  "210": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in the living room."
  },
  "211": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:Behind the sofa is balcony and the bedroom is near the sofa."
  },
  "212": {
    "question": "Question:what does the decorations look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, beautiful, yellow and balck"
  },
  "213": {
    "question": "Question:where is the decorations?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the wall, next to chairs"
  },
  "214": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the decorations in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The decorations are hanging in a bar."
  },
  "215": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the decorations?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bar has a bar counter and two elevators."
  },
  "216": {
    "question": "Question:what does the desk look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Brown, woody, short."
  },
  "217": {
    "question": "Question:where is the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are some books and a blanket on the desk and a cabinet near it."
  },
  "218": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the desk in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The desk is set close to the wall of the hall."
  },
  "219": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area is located on the corner of the hall."
  },
  "220": {
    "question": "Question:what does the toilet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soild, white and porcelainous."
  },
  "221": {
    "question": "Question:where is the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The closetool is set near a white sink and under a mirror."
  },
  "222": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the toilet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The closetool is set in a toilet on the second floor."
  },
  "223": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The closetool is near a bedroom and a laundry. "
  },
  "224": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is rectangular, large and black."
  },
  "225": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is under the switch and the bottle."
  },
  "226": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is in the aisle beside the stairs."
  },
  "227": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is under the switch and the bottle."
  },
  "228": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is rectangular, large and black."
  },
  "229": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is under the switch and the bottle."
  },
  "230": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is in the aisle beside the stairs."
  },
  "231": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is under the switch and the bottle."
  },
  "232": {
    "question": "Question:what does the locker look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:large, white, rectangular"
  },
  "233": {
    "question": "Question:where is the locker?",
    "answer": "Answer:against a wall, next to a wardrobe "
  },
  "234": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the locker in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in a washroom."
  },
  "235": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the locker?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area has two washbasins and a large wardrobe."
  },
  "236": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, small one, made of porcelain "
  },
  "237": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:there is a tap installed above the sink ,and it's placed close to the mirror "
  },
  "238": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is put on the washing table in the big bathroom ,which is farther to the door."
  },
  "239": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are three mirrors and two sinks installed in the bathroom, and the bathroom is the one in big bedroom which attached with a dressing room and balcony."
  },
  "240": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Small vase with green branch."
  },
  "241": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:A red chair on the left of the vase and some frame and paintings on the right."
  },
  "242": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is set in the corner of a big living room."
  },
  "243": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is between two power sockets and connect with a balcony via a glass door."
  },
  "244": {
    "question": "Question:what does the window look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, rectangular, normal size"
  },
  "245": {
    "question": "Question:where is the window?",
    "answer": "Answer:hung on the wall, above the closestool"
  },
  "246": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the window in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the toilet."
  },
  "247": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the window?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the living room."
  },
  "248": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:narrow;covered by white quilts and a grey cushion."
  },
  "249": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:close to a bathtub; faced with a sink below a mirror;"
  },
  "250": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the left side of the room;"
  },
  "251": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:A wall behind it having a picture with Chinese characters;"
  },
  "252": {
    "question": "Question:what does the drawer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, big, wood"
  },
  "253": {
    "question": "Question:where is the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:facing a wall, under a shelter"
  },
  "254": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the drawer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is in a storeroom on the second floor."
  },
  "255": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The store room is next to a bathroom and facing a corridor."
  },
  "256": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Normal, woody and glass-covered"
  },
  "257": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is opposite a cabinet and in the middle of the three pictures hung on the wall."
  },
  "258": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a hall."
  },
  "259": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The hall is on the second floor."
  },
  "260": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:square, cloth, white and brown"
  },
  "261": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the washroom, on the carpet, facing the picture "
  },
  "262": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is located in the bright bedroom."
  },
  "263": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is on the second floor, on the left of the corridor when up to second floor, in the end of the corridor and next to a bedroom."
  },
  "264": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stove look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:steel, rectangle and black"
  },
  "265": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stove?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed on a cabinet and close to a kettel."
  },
  "266": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stove in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "267": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stove?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to the chatting room and the door."
  },
  "268": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cylindrical, metallic, tall"
  },
  "269": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the cabinet which is on the left of the television, next to the window"
  },
  "270": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is set in the bright livingroom."
  },
  "271": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The livingroom is on the first floor , next to the dining room and next to the kitchen."
  },
  "272": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stairs look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Wooden narrow stairs."
  },
  "273": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stairs?",
    "answer": "Answer:They lead to a room with two sofas."
  },
  "274": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stairs in?",
    "answer": "Answer:They are the last stairs to the room."
  },
  "275": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stairs?",
    "answer": "Answer:They near some glass bezels."
  },
  "276": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is round, white and tall."
  },
  "277": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is on the table and beside the window."
  },
  "278": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is inside the lounge."
  },
  "279": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is on the table and beside the window."
  },
  "280": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, brown, wooden"
  },
  "281": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the table, next to the window, on the left of the main entrance when facing outside"
  },
  "282": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set in the livingroom."
  },
  "283": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The livingroom is on the first floor and next to the washroom."
  },
  "284": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is big, colorful and square."
  },
  "285": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is placed on the wall on the opposite of the sofa."
  },
  "286": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is placed on the wall on the opposite of the sofa in the living room."
  },
  "287": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a big set of sofa, chairs and tables in the living room."
  },
  "288": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Rectangular, soild and small."
  },
  "289": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set on the right side of a stair and on the opposite side of the same chair."
  },
  "290": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in a corridor on the second floor."
  },
  "291": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set near a bedroom."
  },
  "292": {
    "question": "Question:what does the painting look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black and white,  rectangular, abstract"
  },
  "293": {
    "question": "Question:where is the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:face the washing room, hang on the wall"
  },
  "294": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the painting in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is placed in a big villa"
  },
  "295": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a swimming pool beside the villa"
  },
  "296": {
    "question": "Question:what does the model look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:tower-shaped,wooden,small,brown"
  },
  "297": {
    "question": "Question:where is the model?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the locker,on the right side of the pillar and on the left of the display"
  },
  "298": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the model in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The model is in the vast rest area."
  },
  "299": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the model?",
    "answer": "Answer:The model is behind the restaurant and opposite to a meeting room."
  },
  "300": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:round, yellow and woody"
  },
  "301": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is surrounded by six chairs and next to the door."
  },
  "302": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a chatting room on the first floor."
  },
  "303": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chatting room is next to the hall."
  },
  "304": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:square, colorful"
  },
  "305": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's right above the bench, face the bed."
  },
  "306": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's put in a big and  bright main bedroom."
  },
  "307": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The master bedroom faces the balcony. Right below the room is the swimming pool."
  },
  "308": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is small, square and black."
  },
  "309": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are some drinks on the table."
  },
  "310": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is placed against the wall in the corner of the kitchen."
  },
  "311": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are some stools, table, sink and cabinet nearby."
  },
  "312": {
    "question": "Question:what does the book look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:thick,white,paper,with a blue cover"
  },
  "313": {
    "question": "Question:where is the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:between a plant and a red book,on the locker and under the clock"
  },
  "314": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the book in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The book is in a large resting area."
  },
  "315": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:The book is opposite to a row of boothes and in front of two single rooms."
  },
  "316": {
    "question": "Question:what does the power switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a plastic, new, square switch."
  },
  "317": {
    "question": "Question:where is the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:It was next to a picture, on a sofa."
  },
  "318": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the power switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is in a living room.\n"
  },
  "319": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a clean, tidy and spacious living room.\n"
  },
  "320": {
    "question": "Question:what does the desk look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:woody , small"
  },
  "321": {
    "question": "Question:where is the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the stair and the woody chair"
  },
  "322": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the desk in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the living room"
  },
  "323": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the staircase and on the third floor."
  },
  "324": {
    "question": "Question:what does the towel look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is rectangular, white and soft."
  },
  "325": {
    "question": "Question:where is the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is next to the brush and wine."
  },
  "326": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the towel in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is inside the bedroom bathroom."
  },
  "327": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is next to the brush and wine."
  },
  "328": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black, circle, wooden"
  },
  "329": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are some book put on it, It's surround by sofa and chairs"
  },
  "330": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's put in the reception area where next to the stairs."
  },
  "331": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's next to the garden. "
  },
  "332": {
    "question": "Question:what does the clothes look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white and grey;long; bath robes;"
  },
  "333": {
    "question": "Question:where is the clothes?",
    "answer": "Answer:hanging on the black racks; against a screen. next to a rounded bar."
  },
  "334": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the clothes in?",
    "answer": "Answer:at the entrance of the bath center."
  },
  "335": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the clothes?",
    "answer": "Answer:there're elevators outside."
  },
  "336": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pillow look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Black, soft and having five."
  },
  "337": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:These pillows is on a sofa and near some vase."
  },
  "338": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pillow in?",
    "answer": "Answer:These pillows is in a dining room."
  },
  "339": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to a kitchen and across from stairs."
  },
  "340": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is large, glassy and rectangular."
  },
  "341": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is on the top of the pool and to the right of the other mirror."
  },
  "342": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is white, glass and rectangular."
  },
  "343": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is on the top of the pool and to the right of the other mirror."
  },
  "344": {
    "question": "Question:what does the tissue look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Paper, white, cylindrical"
  },
  "345": {
    "question": "Question:where is the tissue?",
    "answer": "Answer: Tissue are placed on a metal stand on a marble countertop with a cupboard above"
  },
  "346": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the tissue in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Tissue in the kitchen"
  },
  "347": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the tissue?",
    "answer": "Answer:Tissue opposite is the living room"
  },
  "348": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is big, square and glass."
  },
  "349": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is on the table. The sofa is in front of the table."
  },
  "350": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is placed in front of the sofa in the living room."
  },
  "351": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are many pictures on the wall of the living room."
  },
  "352": {
    "question": "Question:what does the microwave look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a black square microwave oven made of metal."
  },
  "353": {
    "question": "Question:where is the microwave?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's on a microwave oven and a pot."
  },
  "354": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the microwave in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in the dining room."
  },
  "355": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the microwave?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to a study and kitchen."
  },
  "356": {
    "question": "Question:what does the oven look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cuboid, brown, big"
  },
  "357": {
    "question": "Question:where is the oven?",
    "answer": "Answer:in the middle of the cabinet, under the range hood"
  },
  "358": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the oven in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The oven is set in the spacious and bright kitchen."
  },
  "359": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the oven?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is on the third floor, facing the stairs and next to the dining room."
  },
  "360": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A big white metal table with mutiple utensils used in the kitchen."
  },
  "361": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in front of a narrow glass door and between two tall white cabinets."
  },
  "362": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is situated at the center of the kitchen."
  },
  "363": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a dining room."
  },
  "364": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:square, leather, brown"
  },
  "365": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the second row of the stairs, facing the screen, under the projector"
  },
  "366": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is set in the home theatre."
  },
  "367": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The home theatre is on the first floor and next to the livingroom and kitchen."
  },
  "368": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is small, glass and standing."
  },
  "369": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is placed in front of the chair and the cabinet."
  },
  "370": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is placed in front of the chair and the cabinet in the room."
  },
  "371": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are two tables, sofa and recliner in the room."
  },
  "372": {
    "question": "Question:what does the windows look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle, white and latticed"
  },
  "373": {
    "question": "Question:where is the windows?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to the bed and facing the door."
  },
  "374": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the windows in?",
    "answer": "Answer:\nIt is in a bedroom on the second floor."
  },
  "375": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the windows?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is at the left rear corner of the stairs."
  },
  "376": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Genuine leather\uff0cSingle sofa."
  },
  "377": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:There have four sofas in the last row. Facing forward, It's forth from left to right.It's under the projector."
  },
  "378": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in the last row of the screening hall, facing the door direction from left to right, the forth sofa."
  },
  "379": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The nearest area is the living room."
  },
  "380": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bathtub look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle, porcelain, white"
  },
  "381": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bathtub?",
    "answer": "Answer:Right under the window, facing the door."
  },
  "382": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bathtub in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's installed in a bathroom."
  },
  "383": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bathtub?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathroom is built in the main room which  faces the balcony. Right below the room is the swimming pool."
  },
  "384": {
    "question": "Question:what does the towel look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, white, soft"
  },
  "385": {
    "question": "Question:where is the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:under a picture, next to two mirrors"
  },
  "386": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the towel in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the washroom."
  },
  "387": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is located in a bedroom which has a rectangular balcony, a washroom and a toilet, and the cloakroom is next to the washroom and toilet."
  },
  "388": {
    "question": "Question:what does the Flowerpot look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:woody,gray,no plants"
  },
  "389": {
    "question": "Question:where is the Flowerpot?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the door, next to the chair"
  },
  "390": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the Flowerpot in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flowerpot is in the corner of the the bedroom's balcony."
  },
  "391": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the Flowerpot?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom's balcony  is long and narrow, and leads to the stairs."
  },
  "392": {
    "question": "Question:what does the switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Metal, soild and brassy."
  },
  "393": {
    "question": "Question:where is the switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:The switch is set near a painting, near a newspaper and on the opposite side of a door."
  },
  "394": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The switch is in a corridor."
  },
  "395": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:The switch is near a bedroom with a bathroom."
  },
  "396": {
    "question": "Question:what does the switches look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Small and subtle switches made of metal."
  },
  "397": {
    "question": "Question:where is the switches?",
    "answer": "Answer:They are just outside the toilet whose light is bright and is near the wooden frame."
  },
  "398": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the switches in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The switches are set in the bedroom."
  },
  "399": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the switches?",
    "answer": "Answer:They're near a door."
  },
  "400": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a slightly old, rectangular painting with a wooden frame.\n"
  },
  "401": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is directly above a switch, opposite the fixed phone."
  },
  "402": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's on the wall of an aisle corridor."
  },
  "403": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:It was in a narrow, clean corridor."
  },
  "404": {
    "question": "Question:what does the painting look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big,black,white and yellow"
  },
  "405": {
    "question": "Question:where is the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's hang on a wall and near a mirror."
  },
  "406": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the painting in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a corridor on the second floor."
  },
  "407": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:the corridor is near 2 small bedrooms and a living room."
  },
  "408": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:round, yellow and woody"
  },
  "409": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the center of the kitchen and  next to the cabinet."
  },
  "410": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "411": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to the chatting room and the door."
  },
  "412": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A medium-sized black wooden chair with a backrest."
  },
  "413": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is the leftmost chair among the three chairs set at the wide side of the table."
  },
  "414": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Its backrest faces two doors and the chair is on the carpet."
  },
  "415": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a stairway and a kitchen."
  },
  "416": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:medium-size,saddle,close to window"
  },
  "417": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's on the table and next to the armchair"
  },
  "418": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:at the corner of the room"
  },
  "419": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a corridor outside the room"
  },
  "420": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden, brown, big"
  },
  "421": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:under the fireplace,facing the table"
  },
  "422": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is set in the kitchen."
  },
  "423": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is on the first floor and next to the dining room."
  },
  "424": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pillow look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:soft, brown and quadrate."
  },
  "425": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:The pillow is next to a gray pillow and on a long sofa."
  },
  "426": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pillow in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The pillow is in a big living room."
  },
  "427": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is next to a dining room and leads to outdoors via a door."
  },
  "428": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, soft , plaid"
  },
  "429": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the window, next to the stove"
  },
  "430": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the bedroom"
  },
  "431": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the living room and on the second floor."
  },
  "432": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, soft , plaid"
  },
  "433": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the window, next to the stove"
  },
  "434": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the bedroom"
  },
  "435": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the living room and on the second floor."
  },
  "436": {
    "question": "Question:what does the paintings look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, wall-mounted"
  },
  "437": {
    "question": "Question:where is the paintings?",
    "answer": "Answer:hung on the wall, above the towels"
  },
  "438": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the paintings in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the bathroom."
  },
  "439": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the paintings?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the corridor and the children's room."
  },
  "440": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pot look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:round, white and wheeled"
  },
  "441": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pot?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed on a cabient and next to a vase.\n"
  },
  "442": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pot in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "443": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pot?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to the chatting room and the door."
  },
  "444": {
    "question": "Question:what does the dining table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:woody, rectangular, brown"
  },
  "445": {
    "question": "Question:where is the dining table?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the sofa, above the dining chair"
  },
  "446": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the dining table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the dining room."
  },
  "447": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the dining table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the kitchen and the living room."
  },
  "448": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:gray, oblong and wooden."
  },
  "449": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are many glass bottles on the cabinet and two sofas are in front of it."
  },
  "450": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is in a big living room."
  },
  "451": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is next to a dining room and leads to outdoors via a door."
  },
  "452": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pillow look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cream color, square, cloth"
  },
  "453": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the bed, in the middle of two lamps"
  },
  "454": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pillow in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The pillow is set in the bedroom."
  },
  "455": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is on the left of the corridor when up to second floor, in the end of the corridor and on the second floor."
  },
  "456": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small one ,embedded in the washing table ,its shape is circle"
  },
  "457": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:there is a tap above the sink ,and the washing table is black and under several handicrafts"
  },
  "458": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is embedded in the black washing table outside the big bedroom ,close to the relaxing area."
  },
  "459": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area of the washing table placed is quite small ,and it's between the living room and big bedroom ,opposite the relaxing area."
  },
  "460": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Wooden, wood color, with three metal handles"
  },
  "461": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:cabinet above is the pool with appliances on the left and right"
  },
  "462": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:cabinet in the kitchen"
  },
  "463": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:Opposite the cabinet is the living room"
  },
  "464": {
    "question": "Question:what does the drawer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black, wood, rectangular"
  },
  "465": {
    "question": "Question:where is the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the right of a fire place, under a lamp"
  },
  "466": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the drawer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is placed in the corner of a big living room next to a window."
  },
  "467": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is next to another small room on the first floor and is next to a corridor."
  },
  "468": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:ceramic, brown and yellow, with some twigs."
  },
  "469": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a black platform near the vase and a big window near it."
  },
  "470": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is in a bedroom."
  },
  "471": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom leads outdoors via a door and connects with a washroom."
  },
  "472": {
    "question": "Question:what does the potted plant look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:green, erect, full of vigour "
  },
  "473": {
    "question": "Question:where is the potted plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a swimming pool, near a massage bedroom"
  },
  "474": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the potted plant in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in a gymnasium."
  },
  "475": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the potted plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:The gymnasium has a spinning bike and three chandeliers."
  },
  "476": {
    "question": "Question:what does the washstand look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular,ceramic and white"
  },
  "477": {
    "question": "Question:where is the washstand?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's near a big mirror and next to a flower."
  },
  "478": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the washstand in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's on a brown table in a bathroom on the second floor."
  },
  "479": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the washstand?",
    "answer": "Answer:the bathroom is next to a dressing room and next to a bedroom which is next to a open-balcony."
  },
  "480": {
    "question": "Question:what does the whiteboard look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Rectangular, white,  metallic"
  },
  "481": {
    "question": "Question:where is the whiteboard?",
    "answer": "Answer:The whiteboard is placed near a lowhiteboardudspeaker box and a book shelf."
  },
  "482": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the whiteboard in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The whiteboard is set in the hall."
  },
  "483": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the whiteboard?",
    "answer": "Answer:The  whiteboard is placed near a wall and the gate."
  },
  "484": {
    "question": "Question:what does the door look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:closed, rectangle and brown"
  },
  "485": {
    "question": "Question:where is the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is facing the pool and on the stairs.\n"
  },
  "486": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the door in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in front of the house."
  },
  "487": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is outside the house and in front of the gate."
  },
  "488": {
    "question": "Question:what does the printer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white,big,metal shell,multilaminar"
  },
  "489": {
    "question": "Question:where is the printer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The printer is at the back of a pen and a pair of scissors,next to a row of juicers,at the right of a black advertising cabinet."
  },
  "490": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the printer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The printer is in an office containing numerous drink and snacks."
  },
  "491": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the printer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is at the corner is at the corner of the three fork road and next to an empty office and opposite to the room 356."
  },
  "492": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:long; oblong; black;"
  },
  "493": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:below a squared decorative picture; in the middle of two identical end tables;"
  },
  "494": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:counting from right to left the third one;"
  },
  "495": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:a hall with a big rounded bar and a bathing pool;"
  },
  "496": {
    "question": "Question:what does the door look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:tall, woody, rectangular"
  },
  "497": {
    "question": "Question:where is the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the table and the green chairs"
  },
  "498": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the door in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the study."
  },
  "499": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to the bathroom and children's bedroom."
  },
  "500": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Brown, porcelainous and small."
  },
  "501": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is set near two white washing machines and a white sink."
  },
  "502": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is in a laundry."
  },
  "503": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is near a corridor."
  },
  "504": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white and black,wood and glass,light"
  },
  "505": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:between window and bed, on a cabinet with a book"
  },
  "506": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is set at a corner of the bedroom."
  },
  "507": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:A balcony is outside of the bedroom."
  },
  "508": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Black, small, plastic"
  },
  "509": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is on a wooden tray with two jars next to it and a pink flower inside"
  },
  "510": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Vase on sofa in living room"
  },
  "511": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:Vase near the corridor connecting the gym"
  },
  "512": {
    "question": "Question:what does the towel look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White, cloth, folded"
  },
  "513": {
    "question": "Question:where is the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel was hung on a metal handle with a switch next to it and a light on it"
  },
  "514": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the towel in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Towel in the toilet"
  },
  "515": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:Towel are bedrooms on one side and corridors on the other"
  },
  "516": {
    "question": "Question:what does the drawer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, big, wood"
  },
  "517": {
    "question": "Question:where is the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:under a bottle, next to a gas stove"
  },
  "518": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the drawer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is settled in the corner of a kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "519": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to a small storeroom and there is a cloakroom upstairs."
  },
  "520": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pillow look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, square, cloth"
  },
  "521": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the long sofa, among six pillow and third from left"
  },
  "522": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pillow in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The pillow is set in the spacious livingroom."
  },
  "523": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:The livingroom is on the first floor and next to the kitchen."
  },
  "524": {
    "question": "Question:what does the outlet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:plastic, rectangle"
  },
  "525": {
    "question": "Question:where is the outlet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's facing a switch and an outlet"
  },
  "526": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the outlet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is installed on the cupboard in the middle of the open kitchen"
  },
  "527": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the outlet?",
    "answer": "Answer:Here you can see the swimming pool, reception area and a wicket."
  },
  "528": {
    "question": "Question:what does the telephone look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Plastic, white and stand-by."
  },
  "529": {
    "question": "Question:where is the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:The telephone is on the table."
  },
  "530": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the telephone in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Telephone is in living room"
  },
  "531": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:The telephone is very close to the bedroom and toilet."
  },
  "532": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Green, like a tree and electronic."
  },
  "533": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is near a big bed and near a dresser."
  },
  "534": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is in a bedroom."
  },
  "535": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom leads outdoors via a door and connects with a washroom."
  },
  "536": {
    "question": "Question:what does the closestool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white , normal size"
  },
  "537": {
    "question": "Question:where is the closestool?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the woody doors, below the white towels"
  },
  "538": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the closestool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the bedroom"
  },
  "539": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the closestool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the corridor and on the second floor."
  },
  "540": {
    "question": "Question:what does the potted plant look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:round, green and erect"
  },
  "541": {
    "question": "Question:where is the potted plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is between the pool and the door."
  },
  "542": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the potted plant in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in front of the house."
  },
  "543": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the potted plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:\nIt is outside the house and in front of the gate."
  },
  "544": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white,remamic,smooth"
  },
  "545": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a closestool and near a window  and a sink"
  },
  "546": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a washroom which is in a bedroom on the first floor"
  },
  "547": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:the bedroom is in the end of a corridor which is near another bedroom and rest room"
  },
  "548": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, rectangular, brown"
  },
  "549": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:facing a bed, below a picture"
  },
  "550": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in a wide and clean bedroom."
  },
  "551": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is next to a bashroom and a balcony."
  },
  "552": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bottle look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, black, glassy"
  },
  "553": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bottle?",
    "answer": "Answer:above the television, under some books"
  },
  "554": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bottle in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bottle is located in a living room."
  },
  "555": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bottle?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a lamp in the corner and another lamp in the center in the living room."
  },
  "556": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:it isn't embedded in the washing table ,it's put on it , made of porcelain ,its color is white "
  },
  "557": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:there is a small tap installed above the sink ,and a grey towel is hanging close to it "
  },
  "558": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is put on the washing table ,under a small tap close to the grey towel in the bathroom."
  },
  "559": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathroom is a big one inside the detached bedroom, which attached with  several mirrors and two sinks."
  },
  "560": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, wall-mounted, glass"
  },
  "561": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:hung on the wall, above the sink"
  },
  "562": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the toilet."
  },
  "563": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the living room."
  },
  "564": {
    "question": "Question:what does the towel look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:hanged, cotton and white."
  },
  "565": {
    "question": "Question:where is the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is between the toilet and the basin."
  },
  "566": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the towel in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a restroom on the first floor."
  },
  "567": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The restroom is in the bedroom which is at the right turn of the gate."
  },
  "568": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A low wooden table with a statue on it."
  },
  "569": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is surrounded by white sofas and on a big carpet."
  },
  "570": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the center of the living room."
  },
  "571": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near the projector."
  },
  "572": {
    "question": "Question:what does the computer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black, square, metal."
  },
  "573": {
    "question": "Question:where is the computer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The computer is put on a table. Near the computer is a chair. "
  },
  "574": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the computer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The computer is in a study."
  },
  "575": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the computer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The computer faces the hallway."
  },
  "576": {
    "question": "Question:what does the fireplace look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The fireplace is rectangular, black and iron."
  },
  "577": {
    "question": "Question:where is the fireplace?",
    "answer": "Answer:The fireplace is in the wall and to the right of the lamp."
  },
  "578": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the fireplace in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The fireplace is in the lounge."
  },
  "579": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the fireplace?",
    "answer": "Answer:The fireplace is in the wall and to the right of the lamp."
  },
  "580": {
    "question": "Question:what does the DVD look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, rectangular, gray  "
  },
  "581": {
    "question": "Question:where is the DVD?",
    "answer": "Answer:under the television, next to some photos"
  },
  "582": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the DVD in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The DVD is against a wall in the living room."
  },
  "583": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the DVD?",
    "answer": "Answer:This location has two doors and there are some trees via the windows."
  },
  "584": {
    "question": "Question:what does the toilet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small,iregular,white"
  },
  "585": {
    "question": "Question:where is the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's under the drawer and close to the window"
  },
  "586": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the toilet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:a small room in the bathroom"
  },
  "587": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:there is a bedroom across the corridor outside the bathroom"
  },
  "588": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Vitreous, round and transparent."
  },
  "589": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set near a big table with a metal sink and in front of a big gray cabinet."
  },
  "590": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set in a kitchen."
  },
  "591": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is near a rest room and a corridor."
  },
  "592": {
    "question": "Question:what does the flowerpot look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:ceramic, cylinder, gray and white"
  },
  "593": {
    "question": "Question:where is the flowerpot?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a window, next to a sofa"
  },
  "594": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the flowerpot in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flowerpot is placed in the corner of a small living room with wood floor."
  },
  "595": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the flowerpot?",
    "answer": "Answer:The small living room is facing a big and white living room and is next to a long corridor."
  },
  "596": {
    "question": "Question:what does the door look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:tall, burlywood, stable, woody"
  },
  "597": {
    "question": "Question:where is the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:between a living room and a study, near a television"
  },
  "598": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the door in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The door is in the corner in a living room."
  },
  "599": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is on the first floor and has a big sofa on the carpet. "
  },
  "600": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:red, fluffy and soft"
  },
  "601": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed on the carpet and in front of the the mirror."
  },
  "602": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is at the right side of the living room on the first floor."
  },
  "603": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is at the left side of the gate."
  },
  "604": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stove look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stove is big and cubic."
  },
  "605": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stove?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stove is placed under the column next to the sofa."
  },
  "606": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stove in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stove is placed under the column next to the sofa."
  },
  "607": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stove?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are some paintings and a keyboard in the living room."
  },
  "608": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stove look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stove is cubic, glass and big."
  },
  "609": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stove?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stove is placed under the column next to the sofa."
  },
  "610": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stove in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stove is placed under the column facing the balcony in the living room."
  },
  "611": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stove?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are many paintings and a keyboard in the living room."
  },
  "612": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stove look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stove is cubic, big and glass."
  },
  "613": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stove?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stove is placed under the column facing the balcony."
  },
  "614": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stove in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stove is placed under the column next to the sofa. "
  },
  "615": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stove?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are some paintings and a keyboard in the living room."
  },
  "616": {
    "question": "Question:what does the television look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular,black,mental"
  },
  "617": {
    "question": "Question:where is the television?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's above a glass table with some books and in front of a double bed."
  },
  "618": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the television in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a bedroom on the second floor."
  },
  "619": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the television?",
    "answer": "Answer:the bedroom is next to a corridor  and near aother bedroom and a stair."
  },
  "620": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pictuer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle, hanged and brown"
  },
  "621": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pictuer?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on the right side of the window above the bed."
  },
  "622": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pictuer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a bedroom on the second floor."
  },
  "623": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pictuer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is facing the stairs."
  },
  "624": {
    "question": "Question:what does the towel look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:hanged, cotton and blue"
  },
  "625": {
    "question": "Question:where is the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is hanging on a steel stick and beneath two pictures."
  },
  "626": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the towel in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a restroom on the second floor."
  },
  "627": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The restroom is at the left rear corner of the stairs."
  },
  "628": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:blue, circular and small"
  },
  "629": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pool?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is between a plant and the big pool."
  },
  "630": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in front of the house."
  },
  "631": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pool?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is outside the house and in front of the gate."
  },
  "632": {
    "question": "Question:what does the paper towel look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Small, white and soft."
  },
  "633": {
    "question": "Question:where is the paper towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The paper towel is on the table with a slivery sink, near a gray cabinet and near a induction cooker."
  },
  "634": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the paper towel in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The paper towel is in a kitchen."
  },
  "635": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the paper towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The paper towel is near a dining room.\n"
  },
  "636": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is rectangular, leathery and white."
  },
  "637": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is under the table and a book."
  },
  "638": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in the kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "639": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is under the table and a book."
  },
  "640": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cloth rectangle big"
  },
  "641": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:behind the swimming pool and the desk"
  },
  "642": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's outdoor"
  },
  "643": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:the entrance of the house is beheind the sofa"
  },
  "644": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:single chair, not very big, its color id brown and the cushion is flower pattern, it is the ancient style"
  },
  "645": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a small ancient style prop put next to the chair ,and it is put hard by the wall "
  },
  "646": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are two same wooden ancient style chairs put at the entrance to the living room, which is placed close a wooden prop and close to the front door."
  },
  "647": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a carpet put on the ground in front of two chairs, and a big living room is close to the target."
  },
  "648": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White, fabric, single"
  },
  "649": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a  table in front of the sofa  and a lamp next to it"
  },
  "650": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Sofa in living room"
  },
  "651": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:sofa Opposite the stairs and behind the balcony"
  },
  "652": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White, fabric, single"
  },
  "653": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a  table in front of the sofa  and a lamp next to it"
  },
  "654": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Sofa in living room"
  },
  "655": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:sofa Opposite the stairs and behind the balcony"
  },
  "656": {
    "question": "Question:what does the carbinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Red, rectangular ,woody."
  },
  "657": {
    "question": "Question:where is the carbinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a cabinet with the same colour ,state and material on its left and a brown desk opposite to it."
  },
  "658": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the carbinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is set on the corner of the hall and close to a woody door."
  },
  "659": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the carbinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area has lots of cabinets and a glasses door of the hall."
  },
  "660": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is round, white and small."
  },
  "661": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is in the vase. The vase is on the table."
  },
  "662": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is put in the table against the wall."
  },
  "663": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are some pictures in the corridor. "
  },
  "664": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is round, ceramic and white."
  },
  "665": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is put on the table. There are some flowers in the vase."
  },
  "666": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is placed on the table against the wall."
  },
  "667": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a big set of sofa and table outside the door."
  },
  "668": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is round, small and white."
  },
  "669": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is on the table. There are some flowers in the vase."
  },
  "670": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is placed on the table against the wall."
  },
  "671": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stairs are on the opposite."
  },
  "672": {
    "question": "Question:what does the paintings look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Medium size, soild and papery."
  },
  "673": {
    "question": "Question:where is the paintings?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is set near two skateboards, above a white bedside table and near a white and brown bed."
  },
  "674": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the paintings in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is in a bedroom on the second floor."
  },
  "675": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the paintings?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is near a toilet and a corridor."
  },
  "676": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:tall, rectangular, filmy"
  },
  "677": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the bed and the lamp, face the window with black curtain"
  },
  "678": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is in the bedroom."
  },
  "679": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is next to the stairs and has a woody table in it."
  },
  "680": {
    "question": "Question:what does the door handle look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Small, black and golden, metal."
  },
  "681": {
    "question": "Question:where is the door handle?",
    "answer": "Answer:Door handle is on the door, next to the button."
  },
  "682": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the door handle in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The door handle is in the living room."
  },
  "683": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the door handle?",
    "answer": "Answer:The door handle is close to the toilet and bathroom."
  },
  "684": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:installed on the wall, median size, stain steel made frame "
  },
  "685": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's installed above a white sink, it is front facing the door of bathroom"
  },
  "686": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is installed on the wall which is placed above a white sink in the small detached bathroom."
  },
  "687": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathroom is the small one which is detached and close to the hovel , opposite a small bedroom."
  },
  "688": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Rectangular,  small, red."
  },
  "689": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are  four chairs with the same shape, size on  their  left and a picture opposite  to them."
  },
  "690": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chairs are set at the middle of the small room with a red carpet."
  },
  "691": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:This  area  has lots of  chairs and two  desks."
  },
  "692": {
    "question": "Question:what does the Refrigerator look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, big, metallic"
  },
  "693": {
    "question": "Question:where is the Refrigerator?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the microwave, face the cupboard by the wall"
  },
  "694": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the Refrigerator in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The refrigerator is in the kitchen."
  },
  "695": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the Refrigerator?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to the dining room and living room."
  },
  "696": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:middle size,like a umbrella,metal"
  },
  "697": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's on a bedside table and next to a double bed.it's next to a wardrobe and a picture"
  },
  "698": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a bedroom on the first floor"
  },
  "699": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:the bedroom has a washroom and is in the end of a corridor which is near another bedroom   and rest room"
  },
  "700": {
    "question": "Question:what does the shower look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:silvery, small, metal"
  },
  "701": {
    "question": "Question:where is the shower?",
    "answer": "Answer:facing a door, on the left of a hand sink"
  },
  "702": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the shower in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The shower is settled in the corner of a bathroom on the second floor."
  },
  "703": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the shower?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathroom is next to a storeroom and is on the top of a kitchen."
  },
  "704": {
    "question": "Question:what does the telephone look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Metal and plastic, black and small."
  },
  "705": {
    "question": "Question:where is the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:The telephone is set on the right side of a blue and white bed, near a guitar and near a beige and brown lamp."
  },
  "706": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the telephone in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The telephone is in a bedroom."
  },
  "707": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:The telephone is near a corridor and a storage room."
  },
  "708": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pillow look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, cloth, square"
  },
  "709": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the long sofa, among six pillows and on the right of the them"
  },
  "710": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pillow in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The pillow is set in the bright livingroom."
  },
  "711": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:The livingroom is on the first floor and next to the dining room. "
  },
  "712": {
    "question": "Question:what does the counter look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wood, large, brown"
  },
  "713": {
    "question": "Question:where is the counter?",
    "answer": "Answer:near a bath, next to a water dispenser"
  },
  "714": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the counter in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is put in a gymnasium."
  },
  "715": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the counter?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are decorations on the wall and a large swimming pool in the gymnasium."
  },
  "716": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cuboid, brown, it's made of wood"
  },
  "717": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a small black handicraft put on the cabinet, and the glass door is close to it"
  },
  "718": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The wooden cabinet is placed at the corner of the detached bedroom, which is close to the glass door to the balcony."
  },
  "719": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is front facing the white bed, and the bedroom is the one which attached with dressing room and bathroom."
  },
  "720": {
    "question": "Question:what does the painting look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:normal size, square, white and brown."
  },
  "721": {
    "question": "Question:where is the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:Facing the chandelier, There's another big painting in front of it."
  },
  "722": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the painting in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It hangs on the second-floor porch of the villa"
  },
  "723": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a swimming pool beside the villa"
  },
  "724": {
    "question": "Question:what does the curtain look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Gray, cloth and soild."
  },
  "725": {
    "question": "Question:where is the curtain?",
    "answer": "Answer:The curtain is set next to a beige long sofa, near a transparent oval table and near a black and gray sofa."
  },
  "726": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the curtain in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The curtain is in a living room."
  },
  "727": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the curtain?",
    "answer": "Answer:The curtain is near a balcony and a dining room."
  },
  "728": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bush look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:green plants,lush"
  },
  "729": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bush?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a exit door and a window"
  },
  "730": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bush in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's located in a garden with a flower bed on the second floor"
  },
  "731": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bush?",
    "answer": "Answer:the garden is near the balcony which is near a study room"
  },
  "732": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, heavy, rectangular"
  },
  "733": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:under the mirror, face the door of the bathroom"
  },
  "734": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:This carbinet is in the bathroom."
  },
  "735": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathroom is next to the stairs and six bedrooms on the third floor."
  },
  "736": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:glass, round and transparent"
  },
  "737": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is a small vase on a cabinet next to a big vase."
  },
  "738": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a chatting room on the first floor."
  },
  "739": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chatting room is next to the hall."
  },
  "740": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:upright cuboid,blue,metal"
  },
  "741": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is against the white wall,next to a water bottle and on the left of the computer."
  },
  "742": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is in a small office numbering 359."
  },
  "743": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The small office is along the corridor,opposite to an empty room and near the junction of three roads."
  },
  "744": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:fluffy,yellow,soft"
  },
  "745": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a big round table and 3 same chairs."
  },
  "746": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in the dining room on the first floor."
  },
  "747": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:the dining room is near a living room and a stair"
  },
  "748": {
    "question": "Question:what does the dustbin look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:short,cuboid,plastic,black,empty,coverd by a plastic bag"
  },
  "749": {
    "question": "Question:where is the dustbin?",
    "answer": "Answer:The dustbin is on the left of a black box,on the right side of the printer and in front of the socket."
  },
  "750": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the dustbin in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The dustbin is in the public stationery area."
  },
  "751": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the dustbin?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is on the left side of the exit and opposite to a no entry room."
  },
  "752": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, cloth and wood, low"
  },
  "753": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:under a light, next to a column"
  },
  "754": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is settled in a corridor on the first floor with wood floor."
  },
  "755": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The corridor is behind a white and bright living and is in front of a dining room."
  },
  "756": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:blend material\uff0cit's reflected\uff0csmall one"
  },
  "757": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:there is a glass made vase close to the mirror\uff0ca black artware is close to the target"
  },
  "758": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is installed on the wall close to bedroom\uff0cit's close to a glass made vase and a black artware."
  },
  "759": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a white door opposite the mirror\uff0cand a big bed is in the big bedroom."
  },
  "760": {
    "question": "Question:what does the flower look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:orange, round and erect"
  },
  "761": {
    "question": "Question:where is the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed in a white vase next to the window."
  },
  "762": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the flower in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in living roon on the first floor."
  },
  "763": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is the room facing the door."
  },
  "764": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pillow look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:soft, green and quadrate."
  },
  "765": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:The pillow is next to a red pillow and on a long sofa."
  },
  "766": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pillow in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The pillow is in a big living room."
  },
  "767": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is next to a dining room and leads to outdoors via a door."
  },
  "768": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White, porcelain and clean."
  },
  "769": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is under the faucet, on the washstand."
  },
  "770": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Sink is in the toilet."
  },
  "771": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is close to the bathroom and bedroom."
  },
  "772": {
    "question": "Question:what does the carbinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Brown, stair-stepping and tall."
  },
  "773": {
    "question": "Question:where is the carbinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The carbinet is set between two wooden chairs with red mats and behind a round wooden chair."
  },
  "774": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the carbinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The carbinet is in a corridor with a stair."
  },
  "775": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the carbinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The carbinet is near a bathroom."
  },
  "776": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is an old wooden table right size."
  },
  "777": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are several books and a desk lamp directly above it."
  },
  "778": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in a living room."
  },
  "779": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's beside a kitchen."
  },
  "780": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pillow look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Cotton, soild and white."
  },
  "781": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:The pillow is on a white and yellow bed and between two beige and black lamps."
  },
  "782": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pillow in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The pillow is in a bedroom on the second floor."
  },
  "783": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:The pillow is near a toilet and a corridor."
  },
  "784": {
    "question": "Question:what does the toilet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A white porcelain toilet."
  },
  "785": {
    "question": "Question:where is the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is beside a white desk with a sink and close to a mirror."
  },
  "786": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the toilet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the restroom."
  },
  "787": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a bedroom."
  },
  "788": {
    "question": "Question:what does the door look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown, woody and rectangle"
  },
  "789": {
    "question": "Question:where is the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed in front of the pool and next to the plant."
  },
  "790": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the door in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a chatting room on the first floor."
  },
  "791": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chatting room is next to the kitchen and a hall."
  },
  "792": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is large, white and rectangular."
  },
  "793": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is beside the chair and lamp."
  },
  "794": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in the lounge."
  },
  "795": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is beside the chair and lamp."
  },
  "796": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Medium, rectangular, black keynote"
  },
  "797": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a table in front of the picture, and there are candies on the table"
  },
  "798": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:picture is hanging on the living room wall"
  },
  "799": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:picture near the corridor connecting the gym"
  },
  "800": {
    "question": "Question:what does the plate look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black, round and woody"
  },
  "801": {
    "question": "Question:where is the plate?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed on a round sofa and next to some books."
  },
  "802": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the plate in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a chatting room on the first floor."
  },
  "803": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the plate?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chatting room is next to the hall."
  },
  "804": {
    "question": "Question:what does the hinge look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, golden, stable"
  },
  "805": {
    "question": "Question:where is the hinge?",
    "answer": "Answer:between a door and a wall, under another hinge"
  },
  "806": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the hinge in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The hingee belongs to a washroom."
  },
  "807": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the hinge?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area has a large wardrobe and a large locker."
  },
  "808": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:with pillows on it ,cloth,brown"
  },
  "809": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's between two lamps"
  },
  "810": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer and lamp is on the left side of the bed"
  },
  "811": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's close to bathroom"
  },
  "812": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:with pillows on it ,cloth,brown"
  },
  "813": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's between two lamps"
  },
  "814": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer and lamp is on the left side of the bed"
  },
  "815": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's close to bathroom"
  },
  "816": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:plastic, square, and black"
  },
  "817": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:beside the toilet, on the edge of the bed"
  },
  "818": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is put in a spacious and bright bedroom"
  },
  "819": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The master bedroom is next to the bedroom. It is located in the second floor and there is a garden downstairs. "
  },
  "820": {
    "question": "Question:what does the book look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white,paper,thin and small"
  },
  "821": {
    "question": "Question:where is the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:The book is in the middle of the desk,on the right of a pen container and in front of a chair."
  },
  "822": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the book in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's located in a small single office signed number 362."
  },
  "823": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is opposite to a public working office and has a path leading to an exit on the left side."
  },
  "824": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a square, large, brown table."
  },
  "825": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is under a desk lamp, on top of a carpet."
  },
  "826": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in the bedroom."
  },
  "827": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is beside the corridor."
  },
  "828": {
    "question": "Question:what does the plant look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Fourishing,wooden,green."
  },
  "829": {
    "question": "Question:where is the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:The plant is placed on a balck cabinet and next to three grass jars ,against a wall."
  },
  "830": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the plant in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The plant is placed in a tea room."
  },
  "831": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:The plant is placed near the hall and a reading room."
  },
  "832": {
    "question": "Question:what does the towel look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, square, cloth"
  },
  "833": {
    "question": "Question:where is the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the handle, above the toilet, next to the picture"
  },
  "834": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the towel in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is set in the washroom."
  },
  "835": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washroom is inside the bedroom, which is on the second floor, on the left of the stairs and in the central of the corridor."
  },
  "836": {
    "question": "Question:what does the ornament look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Big,plastic,oval"
  },
  "837": {
    "question": "Question:where is the ornament?",
    "answer": "Answer:The ornament is placed under a yellow table surrounded by for yellow chairs and next to shelf."
  },
  "838": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the ornament in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The ornament is placed in the hall."
  },
  "839": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the ornament?",
    "answer": "Answer:The ornament is placed near a big conference room and a small conference room."
  },
  "840": {
    "question": "Question:what does the screen look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A tall,yellow,flexible screen made of linen."
  },
  "841": {
    "question": "Question:where is the screen?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is set on the middle of a wooden platform and is near a glass curtain wall."
  },
  "842": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the screen in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a bedroom."
  },
  "843": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the screen?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a bed and a toilet."
  },
  "844": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, cloth, white"
  },
  "845": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a chair, facing a table"
  },
  "846": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is placed on the first floor in a big dining room."
  },
  "847": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The dining room is next to a kitchen and a small dining room."
  },
  "848": {
    "question": "Question:what does the box look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Brown,cuboid, wooden"
  },
  "849": {
    "question": "Question:where is the box?",
    "answer": "Answer:The box is set  behind a black chairs and between two shelves."
  },
  "850": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the box in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The box is set in the hall."
  },
  "851": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the box?",
    "answer": "Answer:The box is placed near a big conference room and a tea room."
  },
  "852": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, small, plastic"
  },
  "853": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the glass door, on the left of the door when facing the balcony."
  },
  "854": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set on the sunny balcony."
  },
  "855": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The balcony is outside the bedroom, which is on the second floor, on the left of the corridor when go upstairs and in the end of the corridor."
  },
  "856": {
    "question": "Question:what does the windows look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, transparent, glassy"
  },
  "857": {
    "question": "Question:where is the windows?",
    "answer": "Answer:behind the sofa, in front of a television"
  },
  "858": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the windows in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The windows are in the wall in a living room."
  },
  "859": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the windows?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area has two doors and it is on the first floor."
  },
  "860": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:tall,black,metal and plastic"
  },
  "861": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:under a pillow,in front of four screens and a wooden desk"
  },
  "862": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in the number 302 office."
  },
  "863": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is in front of a corridor door,along the road connecting the tea room and the restaurant."
  },
  "864": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:long, rectangle, black"
  },
  "865": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:A painting is right above it, and it's put between two chairs."
  },
  "866": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's put on the first floor where face the garden."
  },
  "867": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:You can see a reception area next here, where the stairs beside."
  },
  "868": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:middle size,leather ,rectangular,soft"
  },
  "869": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's on the center of a carpet ,next to 2 sofas and in front of a fireplace."
  },
  "870": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's located in a living room on the first floor."
  },
  "871": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:the living room is near a dining room,a kitchen and a stair."
  },
  "872": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, brown, leather"
  },
  "873": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:facing the table, in the middle of two sofas, on the carpet"
  },
  "874": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is set in the bright and spacious livingroom."
  },
  "875": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The livingroom is on the first floor and next to the kitchen."
  },
  "876": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, brown, wooden"
  },
  "877": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:under the oven, next to the sofa"
  },
  "878": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is set in the kitchen."
  },
  "879": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to the dining room and on the first floor."
  },
  "880": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cutton,white,soft"
  },
  "881": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in front of a television on the wall and next to 2 round tables."
  },
  "882": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a bedroom on the second floor."
  },
  "883": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:the bedroom has a small bathroom and it's near the corridor."
  },
  "884": {
    "question": "Question:what does the door look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden,oblong,tall,with a sign \"S-B\""
  },
  "885": {
    "question": "Question:where is the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:in the middle of two same doors,under a tube"
  },
  "886": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the door in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's along a long corridor and around a turning."
  },
  "887": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:Along the corridor there are many offices ."
  },
  "888": {
    "question": "Question:what does the fire hydrant look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:pale,cuboid,metal"
  },
  "889": {
    "question": "Question:where is the fire hydrant?",
    "answer": "Answer:The fire hydrant is opposite to a big blue dustbin and a printer,on the right of a pillar and under a tube ."
  },
  "890": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the fire hydrant in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The fire hydrant is at the end of the corridor."
  },
  "891": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the fire hydrant?",
    "answer": "Answer:The corridor is the connection to a stair of the exit and a room that is no entry."
  },
  "892": {
    "question": "Question:what does the notebook look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black,paper,rectangle"
  },
  "893": {
    "question": "Question:where is the notebook?",
    "answer": "Answer:under a paper,on the right of a mouse mat,in front of a pen rack"
  },
  "894": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the notebook in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The notebook is on a desk of the 302 office."
  },
  "895": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the notebook?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is in front of a corridor door and next to the tea room."
  },
  "896": {
    "question": "Question:what does the flower look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, wood, white and yellow"
  },
  "897": {
    "question": "Question:where is the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:below a light, in front of a mirror"
  },
  "898": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the flower in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is placed in the corner of a bathroom."
  },
  "899": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathroom is next to a study and a bedroom on the first floor."
  },
  "900": {
    "question": "Question:what does the flower look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown flowers in a high metal stem"
  },
  "901": {
    "question": "Question:where is the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's under a light and in a metal stem"
  },
  "902": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the flower in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's on corridor"
  },
  "903": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a living room in front of the flower"
  },
  "904": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a rectangular, wooden, oversized cabinet."
  },
  "905": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is beside a painting and a wooden chair."
  },
  "906": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the corner of a living room."
  },
  "907": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a clean, spacious and bright living room."
  },
  "908": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soild, red and brown and h-shaped."
  },
  "909": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is on the left side of a black bookshelf under a sculpture and two photos, on the right side of a same chair and below two pictures."
  },
  "910": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in a study."
  },
  "911": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is near a bathroom."
  },
  "912": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, armless"
  },
  "913": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It faces the pool and there is an identical chair on the right."
  },
  "914": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It was placed in the hallway between the open kitchen and the pool."
  },
  "915": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:There's a pool on one side and an open kitchen on the other"
  },
  "916": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A medium-sized wooden chair with a backrest."
  },
  "917": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the middle of two chairs set at the wide side of a table and its backrest faces a door."
  },
  "918": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is situated in the dining room on the carpet."
  },
  "919": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a kitchen and a stairway."
  },
  "920": {
    "question": "Question:what does the drawer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:woody, white and black."
  },
  "921": {
    "question": "Question:where is the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is next to the bed. There is a lamp on the drawer."
  },
  "922": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the drawer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is in a bedroom."
  },
  "923": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer faces the window and near the living room."
  },
  "924": {
    "question": "Question:what does the switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, rectangular, wall=mounted"
  },
  "925": {
    "question": "Question:where is the switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:hung on the wall, next to the door"
  },
  "926": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the children's room."
  },
  "927": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the study and the bathroom."
  },
  "928": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a glass round table of moderate size."
  },
  "929": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is directly under a table lamp and a pot of plants."
  },
  "930": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in the bedroom."
  },
  "931": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is beside the corridor."
  },
  "932": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden, short, brown"
  },
  "933": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer: next to the glass door, next to the dining room"
  },
  "934": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set on the right corner of the livingroom facing the balcony."
  },
  "935": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The livingroom is next to the dining room, on the third floor and there is a balcony outside."
  },
  "936": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, rectangular,big"
  },
  "937": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:under the vase, below the mirror"
  },
  "938": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the bathroom."
  },
  "939": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the corridor and the children's room."
  },
  "940": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small and square"
  },
  "941": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer: Below the mirror is a cabinet, and it face another big cabinet."
  },
  "942": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It hangs on a small washing room."
  },
  "943": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washing room is built in a small bright bedroom which has the main bedroom on one side and the laundry on the other."
  },
  "944": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, rectangular, brown"
  },
  "945": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:under the stone table, among three stools and in the middle of the two stools"
  },
  "946": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is set in the bright kitchen."
  },
  "947": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is on the third floor, next to the balcony and next to the dining room."
  },
  "948": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Yellow,big,wodden."
  },
  "949": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is set under a yellow table and behind a white computer."
  },
  "950": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is set in the hall."
  },
  "951": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is placed near a big conference and a tea room."
  },
  "952": {
    "question": "Question:what does the block look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:metal,square and white."
  },
  "953": {
    "question": "Question:where is the block?",
    "answer": "Answer:The block is near the blue chair.Beside it is glass door."
  },
  "954": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the block in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The block is on the side of balcony."
  },
  "955": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the block?",
    "answer": "Answer:The block is near the living room and bedroom."
  },
  "956": {
    "question": "Question:what does the light look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Black, candlestick-shaped and metal"
  },
  "957": {
    "question": "Question:where is the light?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed between a wardrobe and a window."
  },
  "958": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the light in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is hanged on the wall on the lfet side of the window."
  },
  "959": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the light?",
    "answer": "Answer:This bedroom is located at the end of the right turn on the second floor, next to another bedroom and a storage room."
  },
  "960": {
    "question": "Question:what does the box look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:open; cubold; with yellow lining;"
  },
  "961": {
    "question": "Question:where is the box?",
    "answer": "Answer:close to the other box with a brown lining; beside the door of a big washroom."
  },
  "962": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the box in?",
    "answer": "Answer:against the wall of a wide and long hallway."
  },
  "963": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the box?",
    "answer": "Answer:a hallway leading to a small bathing pool;"
  },
  "964": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cotton, white, small"
  },
  "965": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is an identical sofa on its left, a pillow is put on it."
  },
  "966": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's put in the reception area where next to the stairs."
  },
  "967": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's next to the garden. "
  },
  "968": {
    "question": "Question:what does the power switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is irony, small and square."
  },
  "969": {
    "question": "Question:where is the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is next to the stairs and the picture."
  },
  "970": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the power switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is placed between the stairs and the picture on the wall."
  },
  "971": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are many cabinets and sinks in the kitchen."
  },
  "972": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:impressionistic, borderless and colorful."
  },
  "973": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is above a long sofa and facing to whole living room."
  },
  "974": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is in a big living room."
  },
  "975": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is next to a dining room and leads to outdoors via a door."
  },
  "976": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a small, round, transparent porcelain."
  },
  "977": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on a table next to a lamp."
  },
  "978": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is in a living room.\n"
  },
  "979": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a clean, tidy and spacious living room.\n"
  },
  "980": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Rectangular , woody, red."
  },
  "981": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are  four chairs with the same size and state on its left.There are four chairs with the same size and state opposite to it."
  },
  "982": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set on a side of the corridor via the altar."
  },
  "983": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area has a fan and lots of benches on each side of the corridor ."
  },
  "984": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:spiral, steel and grey"
  },
  "985": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed on a cabinet and close to a bread maker."
  },
  "986": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "987": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to the chatting room and the door."
  },
  "988": {
    "question": "Question:what does the toilet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:china ,irregualr,white"
  },
  "989": {
    "question": "Question:where is the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the mirror and washstand"
  },
  "990": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the toilet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:in the bathroom"
  },
  "991": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's on the left of livingroom"
  },
  "992": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden, square"
  },
  "993": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:Next to the table was a large sofa, on which stood a pot of plants and a China pot."
  },
  "994": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is put on the reception area."
  },
  "995": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area faces the open kitchen, next to the pool, and dinning table on the other side."
  },
  "996": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:hairy, square, white"
  },
  "997": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a glass door, on the left of a small table, under the picture, facing a bed"
  },
  "998": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:This chair is located in a bright bedroom."
  },
  "999": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:This bedroom is on the second floor and there is a washroom inside and a balcony outside. There is a stairs outside the door and it's on the right of the stairs."
  },
  "1000": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Black, plastic, round"
  },
  "1001": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:A bouquet of flowers in a vase, placed on a vanity top"
  },
  "1002": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Vase in the bedroom"
  },
  "1003": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is at the end of the living room"
  },
  "1004": {
    "question": "Question:what does the towel look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:soft, rectangular, "
  },
  "1005": {
    "question": "Question:where is the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:hung on the wall and below the picture"
  },
  "1006": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the towel in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the bedroom "
  },
  "1007": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the corridor and on the second floor."
  },
  "1008": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A rectangle picture with a frame which depicts a single tree."
  },
  "1009": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on the left of another picture and over the toilet."
  },
  "1010": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the toilet on the second floor."
  },
  "1011": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near the bathroom and the corridor."
  },
  "1012": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A square wooden stool with high legs."
  },
  "1013": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is at the left side of the ring table and beside a wardrobe with mirrors."
  },
  "1014": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the living room."
  },
  "1015": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a stair."
  },
  "1016": {
    "question": "Question:what does the photo look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Small, rectangular and blue."
  },
  "1017": {
    "question": "Question:where is the photo?",
    "answer": "Answer:The photo is settled in a brown bookcase and near a black fitness equipment."
  },
  "1018": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the photo in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The photo is in a bedroom."
  },
  "1019": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the photo?",
    "answer": "Answer:The photo is near a corridor and a toilet."
  },
  "1020": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is white and red."
  },
  "1021": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a chair below the picture and a door next to the picture."
  },
  "1022": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is placed above the chair next to the door."
  },
  "1023": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a toilet on the opposite."
  },
  "1024": {
    "question": "Question:what does the carbinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Glasses, brown, rectangular."
  },
  "1025": {
    "question": "Question:where is the carbinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a cabinet with the same shape, size next to it and a red bench in front of it."
  },
  "1026": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the carbinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is set at the centre of a small room and under some light bulbs."
  },
  "1027": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the carbinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area is located on the corner of hall and has some doors."
  },
  "1028": {
    "question": "Question:what does the carbinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Glasses, brown, rectangular."
  },
  "1029": {
    "question": "Question:where is the carbinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a cabinet with the same shape, size next to it and a red bench in front of it."
  },
  "1030": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the carbinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is set at the centre of a small room and under some light bulbs."
  },
  "1031": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the carbinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area is located on the corner of hall and has some doors."
  },
  "1032": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cotton, hexagon and soft"
  },
  "1033": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to a lamp post and close to a woody stool."
  },
  "1034": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a chatting room on the first floor."
  },
  "1035": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chatting room is next to the hall."
  },
  "1036": {
    "question": "Question:what does the carbinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Rectangular, red, tall."
  },
  "1037": {
    "question": "Question:where is the carbinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a brown cabinet near this cabinet and a red desk opposite to it."
  },
  "1038": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the carbinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is set close to a woody door."
  },
  "1039": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the carbinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area is located on the corner of the hall and has a glasses door of the hall."
  },
  "1040": {
    "question": "Question:what does the Arm apparatus look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, rectangle,black"
  },
  "1041": {
    "question": "Question:where is the Arm apparatus?",
    "answer": "Answer: in front of the painting and next to the treadmill\n\n"
  },
  "1042": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the Arm apparatus in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a room at the end of corridor"
  },
  "1043": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the Arm apparatus?",
    "answer": "Answer:there is a small toilet"
  },
  "1044": {
    "question": "Question:what does the drawer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is brown, wooden and closed."
  },
  "1045": {
    "question": "Question:where is the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The recliner and the table is in front of the drawer."
  },
  "1046": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the drawer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is placed behind the recliner and the table in the room."
  },
  "1047": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are two tables, sofa and recliner in the room."
  },
  "1048": {
    "question": "Question:what does the drawer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small ,brown and stand on the floor"
  },
  "1049": {
    "question": "Question:where is the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is on the drawer.The door is next to the drawer"
  },
  "1050": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the drawer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's on the left side of the bed.the door is on the left side of the drawer."
  },
  "1051": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a laundry across the corridor."
  },
  "1052": {
    "question": "Question:what does the switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, rectangle, plastic"
  },
  "1053": {
    "question": "Question:where is the switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the main room door and a decoration."
  },
  "1054": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's install in a big and  bright main bedroom"
  },
  "1055": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:The master bedroom faces the balcony. Right below the room is the swimming pool"
  },
  "1056": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Rectangular, medium size and monochrome."
  },
  "1057": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is in front of a window and next to two wooden doors."
  },
  "1058": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is in a art studio."
  },
  "1059": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is near a living room and a corridor."
  },
  "1060": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Leather, beige and big."
  },
  "1061": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is opposite to a big beige sofa, on the right side of a brown wooden table and near two cuboid chairs."
  },
  "1062": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in a living room."
  },
  "1063": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is near a corridor."
  },
  "1064": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cloth, small, white"
  },
  "1065": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a lamp, in front of a window"
  },
  "1066": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in the corner of a wide and bright bedroom."
  },
  "1067": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is next to a long corridor on the second floor and there is a living room downstairs."
  },
  "1068": {
    "question": "Question:what does the wood look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:woody, heavy, brown, black"
  },
  "1069": {
    "question": "Question:where is the wood?",
    "answer": "Answer:between a furnace and a curtain, against a wall "
  },
  "1070": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the wood in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The wood is uesd to make a fire in a study."
  },
  "1071": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the wood?",
    "answer": "Answer:The study connects with the outside via a door and is next to a living room and a bedroom."
  },
  "1072": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wood and cloth,big,with pillows on it"
  },
  "1073": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:the armchair is next to the desk and another armchair"
  },
  "1074": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in the corner of the room"
  },
  "1075": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a corridor outside the room"
  },
  "1076": {
    "question": "Question:what does the shelf look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:tall, woody, stable"
  },
  "1077": {
    "question": "Question:where is the shelf?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of a table, next to a door"
  },
  "1078": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the shelf in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in a study."
  },
  "1079": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the shelf?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area is on the first floor and next to a living room."
  },
  "1080": {
    "question": "Question:what does the clothes rack look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, white, wall-mounted"
  },
  "1081": {
    "question": "Question:where is the clothes rack?",
    "answer": "Answer:opposite to the white door, there are two clothes in the clothes rack"
  },
  "1082": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the clothes rack in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the cloakroom."
  },
  "1083": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the clothes rack?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is located in a bedroom which has a rectangular balcony, a washroom and a toilet, and the cloakroom is next to the washroom and toilet."
  },
  "1084": {
    "question": "Question:what does the outlet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:plastic, small, rectangle, white"
  },
  "1085": {
    "question": "Question:where is the outlet?",
    "answer": "Answer:face a sofa, right under the switch and the thermostat."
  },
  "1086": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the outlet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's installed at the first floor where face the stair."
  },
  "1087": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the outlet?",
    "answer": "Answer:On it's right side is the dinning table, and on it's left side is a garden."
  },
  "1088": {
    "question": "Question:what does the loudspeaker box look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Cuboid, black, metal"
  },
  "1089": {
    "question": "Question:where is the loudspeaker box?",
    "answer": "Answer:The loudspeaker box is set between two walls next to a lamp and against another wall."
  },
  "1090": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the loudspeaker box in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The loudspeaker box is placed in the hall."
  },
  "1091": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the loudspeaker box?",
    "answer": "Answer:The loudspeaker box is placed near a small conference  room and a big conference room."
  },
  "1092": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Wooden, rectangular and golden."
  },
  "1093": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is in the first row and the second column of the six pictures, before a white wall and near a cabinet with a silver ship."
  },
  "1094": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is in a living room."
  },
  "1095": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is near a study."
  },
  "1096": {
    "question": "Question:what does the poster look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle,blue,thin,big"
  },
  "1097": {
    "question": "Question:where is the poster?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the left wall of the room,above the brown cabinet and next to a note written \"hello\""
  },
  "1098": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the poster in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The poster is in a small single room."
  },
  "1099": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the poster?",
    "answer": "Answer:The room is next to a row of lockers,behind the food bar and near the resting area."
  },
  "1100": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:transparent,glass,fragile"
  },
  "1101": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's surrounded by 4 chairs and near a green potting."
  },
  "1102": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a rest room on the second floor."
  },
  "1103": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:the rest room is near a dining room and a living room."
  },
  "1104": {
    "question": "Question:what does the treadmill look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle,big,grey"
  },
  "1105": {
    "question": "Question:where is the treadmill?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's between the arm apparatus and the gym equipment"
  },
  "1106": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the treadmill in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a room at the end of the corridor"
  },
  "1107": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the treadmill?",
    "answer": "Answer:there is a small toilet"
  },
  "1108": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black and white,metal,cuboid\t"
  },
  "1109": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the left side of the room,under the second table from left to right"
  },
  "1110": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in a big simple shared office with the number 363."
  },
  "1111": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is along the road to the stairs of the exit and around the corner of a junction of three roads."
  },
  "1112": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sculpture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, small, human-shaped"
  },
  "1113": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sculpture?",
    "answer": "Answer:near a door, on the fourth layer of the shelf"
  },
  "1114": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sculpture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sculpture is put in the study."
  },
  "1115": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sculpture?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a tall shelf in the front of the study and there is a big table in the center of the study."
  },
  "1116": {
    "question": "Question:what does the Dish look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:round,small,fragile"
  },
  "1117": {
    "question": "Question:where is the Dish?",
    "answer": "Answer:they are on a brown table and next to 6 chairs ."
  },
  "1118": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the Dish in?",
    "answer": "Answer:they are in a dining room on the second floor."
  },
  "1119": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the Dish?",
    "answer": "Answer:the dining room is near a living room and a balcony."
  },
  "1120": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, green, soft"
  },
  "1121": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a big yellow picture, next to the white bed"
  },
  "1122": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the bedroom."
  },
  "1123": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a rectangular balcony, a cloakroom, a washroom and a toilet in the bedroom. "
  },
  "1124": {
    "question": "Question:what does the dressing table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden,clean and smooth."
  },
  "1125": {
    "question": "Question:where is the dressing table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The dressing table is above a ashcan and there is a pot of flower on it.\n"
  },
  "1126": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the dressing table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The dressing table is in the bedroom."
  },
  "1127": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the dressing table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The dressing table is close to living room and balcony."
  },
  "1128": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A metal,hemispherical sink with a tap."
  },
  "1129": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is embeded in the table and close to an oven."
  },
  "1130": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the kitchen."
  },
  "1131": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a dining room."
  },
  "1132": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is rectangular, large and white."
  },
  "1133": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is under the table and sculpture."
  },
  "1134": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is on the ground floor kitchen."
  },
  "1135": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is under the table and sculpture."
  },
  "1136": {
    "question": "Question:what does the power switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is white, rectangular and small."
  },
  "1137": {
    "question": "Question:where is the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is between the black button and the door."
  },
  "1138": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the power switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is in the utility room."
  },
  "1139": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is between the black button and the door."
  },
  "1140": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Metal, soild and brassy."
  },
  "1141": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is set on the left side of a beige sofa, near two small beige sofas and near a stove."
  },
  "1142": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is in a rest room on the second floor."
  },
  "1143": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is near a corridor on the second floor."
  },
  "1144": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirrior look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, tall, glass"
  },
  "1145": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirrior?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the doors and the plaid chair"
  },
  "1146": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirrior in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the bedroom."
  },
  "1147": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirrior?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the corridor and another bedroom."
  },
  "1148": {
    "question": "Question:what does the tv look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, black "
  },
  "1149": {
    "question": "Question:where is the tv?",
    "answer": "Answer:above the stove and next to the wall"
  },
  "1150": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the tv in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the bedroom"
  },
  "1151": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the tv?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the  corridor and on the second floor"
  },
  "1152": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pillow look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cloth, square, orange"
  },
  "1153": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the long sofa, among six pillows and second from right"
  },
  "1154": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pillow in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The pillow is set in the bright livingroom. "
  },
  "1155": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:The livingroom is on the first floor and next to the kitchen."
  },
  "1156": {
    "question": "Question:what does the flowers look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White, soild and big."
  },
  "1157": {
    "question": "Question:where is the flowers?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flowers are in a small brown vase, on a brown and blue drawer and near a black and brown chair."
  },
  "1158": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the flowers in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flowers are in a corridor."
  },
  "1159": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the flowers?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flowers are near a bedroom and a bathroom."
  },
  "1160": {
    "question": "Question:what does the power switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is white, plastic and power-off."
  },
  "1161": {
    "question": "Question:where is the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a door and some pictures next to the power switch."
  },
  "1162": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the power switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is placed on the wall facing the stairs."
  },
  "1163": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are some pictures in the corridor."
  },
  "1164": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:square, hanged and brown"
  },
  "1165": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is hanging on the wall between the restroom and the bedroom."
  },
  "1166": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a hall on the second floor."
  },
  "1167": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The hall is at the left rear corner of the stairs."
  },
  "1168": {
    "question": "Question:what does the clock look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small blue made by metal"
  },
  "1169": {
    "question": "Question:where is the clock?",
    "answer": "Answer:under the television over the stove"
  },
  "1170": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the clock in?",
    "answer": "Answer: It's in the living room"
  },
  "1171": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the clock?",
    "answer": "Answer:The family cinema is on the right side of it"
  },
  "1172": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is square, glass and big."
  },
  "1173": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a sink and toilet next to the mirror."
  },
  "1174": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is placed next to the sink and the toilet."
  },
  "1175": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a shower room, toilet and sink in the bathroom."
  },
  "1176": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, rectangular, white"
  },
  "1177": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a lamp, facing a picture"
  },
  "1178": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is in a small and bright bedroom on the second floor."
  },
  "1179": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is between a balcony and a bashroom."
  },
  "1180": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, rectangular, white"
  },
  "1181": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a lamp, facing a picture"
  },
  "1182": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is in a small and bright bedroom on the second floor."
  },
  "1183": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is between a balcony and a bashroom."
  },
  "1184": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:yellow, small ,soft "
  },
  "1185": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:across from the bed and next to the wall "
  },
  "1186": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the bedroom "
  },
  "1187": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the  corridor and on the second floor"
  },
  "1188": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A brown table with drawers,sinks and towels."
  },
  "1189": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is close to a door and faces a bathtub and a glass shower room."
  },
  "1190": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is situated in a bathroom which is connected to a bedroom."
  },
  "1191": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near an empty room."
  },
  "1192": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown,tall,coboid and hard"
  },
  "1193": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a tall lamp a short lamp and in front of a double bed"
  },
  "1194": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a bedroom on the first floor"
  },
  "1195": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:the bedroom has a washroom and is in the end of a corridor which is near another bedroom   and rest room"
  },
  "1196": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white with grey stripes; oval; delicate;"
  },
  "1197": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:faced with a big table in the center of this room. in the middle of two screens."
  },
  "1198": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:against the left wall of this room"
  },
  "1199": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:a big room with seven identical sinks."
  },
  "1200": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bath look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, hollow, small"
  },
  "1201": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bath?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a swimming pool, in the corner"
  },
  "1202": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bath in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bath is located in a gymnasium."
  },
  "1203": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bath?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a treadmill and a spinning bike in this gymnasium."
  },
  "1204": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:grey\uff1brotatable\uff1bwith wheels;"
  },
  "1205": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a similar stool and the hallway; behind a bar with a row of magazines on it; "
  },
  "1206": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:behind the front desk in an entryway to a hall with rooms for changing, showering and massage;"
  },
  "1207": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:a hall with a glass door and a recieption desk."
  },
  "1208": {
    "question": "Question:what does the paintings look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Paper, white and good looking."
  },
  "1209": {
    "question": "Question:where is the paintings?",
    "answer": "Answer:Paintings are on the bed, next to the lamp."
  },
  "1210": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the paintings in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Paintings are in the bedroom."
  },
  "1211": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the paintings?",
    "answer": "Answer:The paintings are very close to the living room and the balcony."
  },
  "1212": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stove look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, square, black"
  },
  "1213": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stove?",
    "answer": "Answer:under the range hood, on the cabinet"
  },
  "1214": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stove in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stove is located in the bright kitchen."
  },
  "1215": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stove?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is on the first floor and next to the livingroom."
  },
  "1216": {
    "question": "Question:what does the phone look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, black, square"
  },
  "1217": {
    "question": "Question:where is the phone?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the bed, mext to the lamp"
  },
  "1218": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the phone in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The phone is on the table settled in a warm child-bedroom. "
  },
  "1219": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the phone?",
    "answer": "Answer:The child-bedroom is next to the corridor on the second floor with a fireplace and a bathroom."
  },
  "1220": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:square, installed on the wall, no frame "
  },
  "1221": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:a tap and a sink are under the mirrors, and there is another mirror which attached with wooden frame installed next to it."
  },
  "1222": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is installed on the wall of big bathroom ,it's the one closer to the door, and the bathroom is the one inside the detached bedroom which attached with a dressing room."
  },
  "1223": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathroom is very big with two sinks in it, and there are three mirrors installed on the wall."
  },
  "1224": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White bed and white quilt, the quilt is slightly opened."
  },
  "1225": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed rested against a white wall with another identical bed to its left."
  },
  "1226": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is in the bedroom."
  },
  "1227": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is in the bedroom, which is the first room on the left hand side of the corridor after going up the stairs on the second floor."
  },
  "1228": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White bed and white quilt, the quilt is slightly opened."
  },
  "1229": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed rested against a white wall with another identical bed to its left."
  },
  "1230": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is in the bedroom."
  },
  "1231": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is in the bedroom, which is the first room on the left hand side of the corridor after going up the stairs on the second floor."
  },
  "1232": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:metal,yellow,bright"
  },
  "1233": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's on a small round table and next to a soft chair"
  },
  "1234": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:is's in a rest room on the first floor"
  },
  "1235": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:the rest room is near a corridor which is near 2 bedrooms and a living room"
  },
  "1236": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bathtub look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, big "
  },
  "1237": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bathtub?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the curtains and below the towels"
  },
  "1238": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bathtub in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the bedroom "
  },
  "1239": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bathtub?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the living room and the corridor and on the third floor."
  },
  "1240": {
    "question": "Question:what does the drawer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is white, wooden and rectangular."
  },
  "1241": {
    "question": "Question:where is the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is under the oven and next to the refrigerator."
  },
  "1242": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the drawer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is in the kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "1243": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is under the oven and next to the refrigerator."
  },
  "1244": {
    "question": "Question:what does the drawer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is white, wooden and rectangular."
  },
  "1245": {
    "question": "Question:where is the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is under the oven and next to the refrigerator."
  },
  "1246": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the drawer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is in the kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "1247": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is under the oven and next to the refrigerator."
  },
  "1248": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A metal cabinet with several drawers and a sink."
  },
  "1249": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is below two other cabinets and faces a shelf."
  },
  "1250": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed in a storage room on the ground floor."
  },
  "1251": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a hall and two wardrobes."
  },
  "1252": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden; brown; simple;"
  },
  "1253": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to several switches;near a big squared bed;"
  },
  "1254": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:at the corner of a room."
  },
  "1255": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:a big room within a sink, a big bed and two pictures;"
  },
  "1256": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:median size, cloth sofa, its color id grey "
  },
  "1257": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are several pillows put on the target, and it's close to the glass door "
  },
  "1258": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The grey single sofa is placed close to the glass door, which is back facing a white cabinet, front facing the TV."
  },
  "1259": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are many different size sofas put in the living room, but there is no balcony outside."
  },
  "1260": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, woody, soft"
  },
  "1261": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the door and the woody cabinet"
  },
  "1262": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the bedroom"
  },
  "1263": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the corridor and on the second floor."
  },
  "1264": {
    "question": "Question:what does the telephone look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:hung on the wall; grey; neither too big nor too small;"
  },
  "1265": {
    "question": "Question:where is the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the wall behind the open door;opposite a mirror with a black frame."
  },
  "1266": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the telephone in?",
    "answer": "Answer:at the entrance of the room."
  },
  "1267": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:a quite big room with two identical beds."
  },
  "1268": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Wooden, yellow and with four legs."
  },
  "1269": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is under a lamp and near a big bed."
  },
  "1270": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is in a bedroom.\n"
  },
  "1271": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom leads outdoors via a door and connects with a washroom."
  },
  "1272": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:narrow;covered by white quilts and a grey cushion; used for massage;"
  },
  "1273": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of a brown cabinet;next to the door;"
  },
  "1274": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:at the entrance of the room"
  },
  "1275": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The room is kind of crampled and with wooden floors;"
  },
  "1276": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, white, square"
  },
  "1277": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:under the mirror, next to the toilet"
  },
  "1278": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is set in the washroom."
  },
  "1279": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washroom is on the first floor and next to the livingroom."
  },
  "1280": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sign look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:plastic; yellow; warning;"
  },
  "1281": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sign?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the swimming pool; on the left of a squared pillar."
  },
  "1282": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sign in?",
    "answer": "Answer:by side of the swimming pool;"
  },
  "1283": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sign?",
    "answer": "Answer:an empty space is in front of it."
  },
  "1284": {
    "question": "Question:what does the book look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:numerous, papery and oblong."
  },
  "1285": {
    "question": "Question:where is the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:These book are in a big cabinet and on the left of a big picture and near a big window."
  },
  "1286": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the book in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The books are in a big living room."
  },
  "1287": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is next to a dining room and leads to outdoors via a door."
  },
  "1288": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cloth, big, white"
  },
  "1289": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the middle of two nightstands, facing the television"
  },
  "1290": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is located in the spacious bedroom."
  },
  "1291": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is on the first bedroom and next to the kitchen."
  },
  "1292": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stove look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soild, medium size and silvery."
  },
  "1293": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stove?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stove is set on the right side of the oven and behind a silvery sink."
  },
  "1294": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stove in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stove is in a kitchen."
  },
  "1295": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stove?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stove is near a corridor and a toilet."
  },
  "1296": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A glass clean square mirror."
  },
  "1297": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is under a dim light and is over a sink."
  },
  "1298": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a toilet."
  },
  "1299": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a bedroom."
  },
  "1300": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown,short and with five wheels"
  },
  "1301": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of a tray containing some cards and a long table,in the row that close to the locker and in the position closest to two rooms"
  },
  "1302": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is in the large resting room."
  },
  "1303": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is in front of two small single rooms and behind the food bar."
  },
  "1304": {
    "question": "Question:what does the television look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Metal, cuboid and black."
  },
  "1305": {
    "question": "Question:where is the television?",
    "answer": "Answer:The television is opposite to a white sofa, near a black table and a blue chair."
  },
  "1306": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the television in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The television is in a living room."
  },
  "1307": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the television?",
    "answer": "Answer:The television is near a bedroom."
  },
  "1308": {
    "question": "Question:what does the power switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a small, white switch made of plastic."
  },
  "1309": {
    "question": "Question:where is the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is directly under a picture, opposite the fixed phone."
  },
  "1310": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the power switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's on the wall of an aisle corridor."
  },
  "1311": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:It was in a narrow, clean corridor."
  },
  "1312": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bottle look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:transparent, glass and fragile."
  },
  "1313": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bottle?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are some bottle like this around the bottle and it is in a wooden salver."
  },
  "1314": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bottle in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bottle is in a big living room."
  },
  "1315": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bottle?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is next to a dining room and leads to outdoors via a door."
  },
  "1316": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:square, white and black, wooden and glass"
  },
  "1317": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the wall, facing the stairs, among six pictures and fifth from left"
  },
  "1318": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is set on the corridor."
  },
  "1319": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The corridor is on the second floor, has two stairs and some rooms beside it."
  },
  "1320": {
    "question": "Question:what does the painting look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Papery, soild and rectangular."
  },
  "1321": {
    "question": "Question:where is the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is opposite to a blue and white painting and near a gray and black bed."
  },
  "1322": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the painting in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is in a bedroom."
  },
  "1323": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is near a corridor and a living room."
  },
  "1324": {
    "question": "Question:what does the light look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white,electric,long,metal"
  },
  "1325": {
    "question": "Question:where is the light?",
    "answer": "Answer:hung on the ceiling,over the desk and near the passageway"
  },
  "1326": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the light in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The light is put in a small booth."
  },
  "1327": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the light?",
    "answer": "Answer:The booth is the nearest to the number 5 meeting room and by side of the reading area."
  },
  "1328": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A long grey sofa with black pillows."
  },
  "1329": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a lamp ,under some pictures and near a bed."
  },
  "1330": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a bedroom which is connected with a bathroom."
  },
  "1331": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a bathroom and an empty room."
  },
  "1332": {
    "question": "Question:what does the switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:plastic, rectangle, small"
  },
  "1333": {
    "question": "Question:where is the switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:Right above the switch is a painting. It face the French window."
  },
  "1334": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's install in a big and  bright main bedroom."
  },
  "1335": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:The master bedroom faces the balcony. Right below the room is the swimming pool."
  },
  "1336": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is rectangular, silver and ceramic."
  },
  "1337": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is to the left of the towel and brush."
  },
  "1338": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is in the bathroom."
  },
  "1339": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is to the left of the towel and brush."
  },
  "1340": {
    "question": "Question:what does the television look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black, rectangular, fragile"
  },
  "1341": {
    "question": "Question:where is the television?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a door, in front of a sofa"
  },
  "1342": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the television in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The television is located in the living room."
  },
  "1343": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the television?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is near a study and the room has lots of photos."
  },
  "1344": {
    "question": "Question:what does the fire hydrant look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big,high and narrow,metal,argent"
  },
  "1345": {
    "question": "Question:where is the fire hydrant?",
    "answer": "Answer:The fire hydrant is hung in the middle of the wall,next to a pillar and opposite to a glass wall."
  },
  "1346": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the fire hydrant in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The fire hydrant is at the junction of the three corridors."
  },
  "1347": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the fire hydrant?",
    "answer": "Answer:The corridor connects the rest area and many offices."
  },
  "1348": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden and glass, middle, black and white"
  },
  "1349": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the wall, next to the door, among three pictures and first from left"
  },
  "1350": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is set in the bright bedroom."
  },
  "1351": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is on the second floor, on the left of the stairs and in the central of the corridor."
  },
  "1352": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soild, leather and red."
  },
  "1353": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is on the left side of the same one and in front of a window with red curtains."
  },
  "1354": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in a rest room."
  },
  "1355": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is near a bedroom with a red bed and on the opposite side of a white corridor."
  },
  "1356": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Round, medium size and black."
  },
  "1357": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is next to a small table under a green plant and near a transparent table surrounded by six orange chairs."
  },
  "1358": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in a corridor."
  },
  "1359": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is near a rest room."
  },
  "1360": {
    "question": "Question:what does the decoration look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black, small like a horse"
  },
  "1361": {
    "question": "Question:where is the decoration?",
    "answer": "Answer:face the bed, there is a painting behind it."
  },
  "1362": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the decoration in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's put in a big and  bright main bedroom."
  },
  "1363": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the decoration?",
    "answer": "Answer:The master bedroom faces the balcony. Right below the room is the swimming pool."
  },
  "1364": {
    "question": "Question:what does the painting look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Beige and brown, small and rectangular."
  },
  "1365": {
    "question": "Question:where is the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is above a brown and black drawer and near a gray and black bed."
  },
  "1366": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the painting in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is in a bedroom."
  },
  "1367": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is near a corridor and a living room."
  },
  "1368": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bush look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:animate,medium,green"
  },
  "1369": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bush?",
    "answer": "Answer:set in a white flowerpot,above a oblong table surrounded by eight black chairs,between two white knick-knacks"
  },
  "1370": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bush in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bush is set in the balcony."
  },
  "1371": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bush?",
    "answer": "Answer:The balcony is in front of the courtyard with a swimming pool and have two French door."
  },
  "1372": {
    "question": "Question:what does the door look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Brown, big and wooden."
  },
  "1373": {
    "question": "Question:where is the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:The door is near a red and brown bed and between two wooden doors."
  },
  "1374": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the door in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The door is in a bedroom on the second floor."
  },
  "1375": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:The door is near a corridor with a wooden stair."
  },
  "1376": {
    "question": "Question:what does the television look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular,black,metal "
  },
  "1377": {
    "question": "Question:where is the television?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's above a yellow table,hang on a wall and next to 2 phones."
  },
  "1378": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the television in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's located in a rest room on the second floor."
  },
  "1379": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the television?",
    "answer": "Answer:the rest room is next to open-balcony and living room."
  },
  "1380": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Red, rectangular, woody."
  },
  "1381": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to another three chairs with the same colour, state on its left,  opposite to five chairs with the same colour, state. "
  },
  "1382": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is set at one side of the corridor via the altar."
  },
  "1383": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area has a fan and lots of benches on each side of the corridor ."
  },
  "1384": {
    "question": "Question:what does the tapestry look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soild, cloth and brown."
  },
  "1385": {
    "question": "Question:where is the tapestry?",
    "answer": "Answer:The tapestry is opposite to a white and green painting and near a brown rectangular photo."
  },
  "1386": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the tapestry in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The tapestry is in a corridor."
  },
  "1387": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the tapestry?",
    "answer": "Answer:The tapestry is near a bedroom and a living room."
  },
  "1388": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Beige, medium size and long."
  },
  "1389": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is set between two beige chairs and in front of a window."
  },
  "1390": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in a lounge."
  },
  "1391": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is on the opposite side of a white corridor."
  },
  "1392": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden, quaint and delicate."
  },
  "1393": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is under a socket and near a desk."
  },
  "1394": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in a dining room."
  },
  "1395": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to a kitchen and across from a fireplace."
  },
  "1396": {
    "question": "Question:what does the paintings look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Papery, rectangular and black and white."
  },
  "1397": {
    "question": "Question:where is the paintings?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is settled on a black wooden bookshelf, on the left side of a monochrome and below six paintings."
  },
  "1398": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the paintings in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is in a study."
  },
  "1399": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the paintings?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is near a living room and a bathroom."
  },
  "1400": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, gray, cotton"
  },
  "1401": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:You can see a cabinet on it's right and a paint above it."
  },
  "1402": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's facing the reception area."
  },
  "1403": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:You can see a reception area next here, where the stairs beside."
  },
  "1404": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Wooden and leather, black and brown and h-shaped."
  },
  "1405": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set near a big brown cabinet and near a gray and black bed."
  },
  "1406": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in a bedroom."
  },
  "1407": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is near a corridor and a bathroom."
  },
  "1408": {
    "question": "Question:what does the painting look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, colorful, ink painting."
  },
  "1409": {
    "question": "Question:where is the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:Facing a chair and a painting. right next the door."
  },
  "1410": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the painting in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in a small bright bedroom."
  },
  "1411": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:It has the main bedroom on one side and the laundry on the other."
  },
  "1412": {
    "question": "Question:what does the book look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:yellow and blue, square, thin"
  },
  "1413": {
    "question": "Question:where is the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the switch, on the first floor of the bookshelf"
  },
  "1414": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the book in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The book is set on the corridor."
  },
  "1415": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:The corridor is on the second floor and facing the stairs."
  },
  "1416": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black,tall,plastic and metal,with five wheels and two handrails"
  },
  "1417": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the glass door,in front of a desk and near a cabinet"
  },
  "1418": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in the outmost seat of a small office allowing four people to work together."
  },
  "1419": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is at the corner of the crossroads and near the tea room and the locker room."
  },
  "1420": {
    "question": "Question:what does the washstand look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small,metal and china ,white"
  },
  "1421": {
    "question": "Question:where is the washstand?",
    "answer": "Answer:under the clock and cupboard"
  },
  "1422": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the washstand in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's at the end of the room and next to the wintdow"
  },
  "1423": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the washstand?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's on opposite of the bedroom"
  },
  "1424": {
    "question": "Question:what does the door look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, white, tall"
  },
  "1425": {
    "question": "Question:where is the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the white cabinets, next to the refrigerator"
  },
  "1426": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the door in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the kitchen."
  },
  "1427": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the dining room and the living room."
  },
  "1428": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wide,white and tidy."
  },
  "1429": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is behind a tea table and there is a desk next to the sofa."
  },
  "1430": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is set in the living room."
  },
  "1431": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is close to the balcony and it faces the bedroom."
  },
  "1432": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden, brown and with four legs."
  },
  "1433": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is near a big bed and a big window."
  },
  "1434": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is in a small bedroom."
  },
  "1435": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom where can see a kitchen and a stairs leads to a utility room via a ladder."
  },
  "1436": {
    "question": "Question:what does the dinning table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wood,medium-size,brown"
  },
  "1437": {
    "question": "Question:where is the dinning table?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's under the flowers and close to windows"
  },
  "1438": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the dinning table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in the kitchen"
  },
  "1439": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the dinning table?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's close to living room"
  },
  "1440": {
    "question": "Question:what does the wardrobe look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, a lot of lattice, wooden"
  },
  "1441": {
    "question": "Question:where is the wardrobe?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's facing the bed, On it's right side is a painting."
  },
  "1442": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the wardrobe in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in a small bright bedroom."
  },
  "1443": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the wardrobe?",
    "answer": "Answer:It has the main bedroom on one side and the laundry on the other."
  },
  "1444": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle, hanged and white"
  },
  "1445": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is hanging on the wall above the desk and next to a switch."
  },
  "1446": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the living room on the first floor."
  },
  "1447": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is at the left side of the gate."
  },
  "1448": {
    "question": "Question:what does the switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Metal, brassy and rectangular."
  },
  "1449": {
    "question": "Question:where is the switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:The switch is near a white sink and three mirrors."
  },
  "1450": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The switch is in a toilet."
  },
  "1451": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:The switch is near a corridor and a bedroom."
  },
  "1452": {
    "question": "Question:what does the seat look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:long;wooden frames; black cushions."
  },
  "1453": {
    "question": "Question:where is the seat?",
    "answer": "Answer:beside a cabinet; on the ceramic floors.near a hair drier;"
  },
  "1454": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the seat in?",
    "answer": "Answer:in the center of the room."
  },
  "1455": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the seat?",
    "answer": "Answer:a room within two shower cubicles."
  },
  "1456": {
    "question": "Question:what does the clock look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Brown, soild and round."
  },
  "1457": {
    "question": "Question:where is the clock?",
    "answer": "Answer:The clock is set near a painting and a brown and round table."
  },
  "1458": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the clock in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The clock is set in a living room."
  },
  "1459": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the clock?",
    "answer": "Answer:The clock is set near a corridor and a bedroom."
  },
  "1460": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, cloth, big"
  },
  "1461": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a lamp, facing a sofa"
  },
  "1462": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is in the middle in a bedroom on the second floor."
  },
  "1463": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is next to a bathroom and has a small balcony."
  },
  "1464": {
    "question": "Question:what does the Wine cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle,big,brown"
  },
  "1465": {
    "question": "Question:where is the Wine cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's between the plant and drawer"
  },
  "1466": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the Wine cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in the kitchen"
  },
  "1467": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the Wine cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's close to living room"
  },
  "1468": {
    "question": "Question:what does the switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Metal, silver and small."
  },
  "1469": {
    "question": "Question:where is the switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:The switch is on the wall, next to the curtains."
  },
  "1470": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The switch is in the bedroom."
  },
  "1471": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:The switch is close to the balcony and living room."
  },
  "1472": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Small, trapezoidal and white."
  },
  "1473": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirrors are set above a gray box, near a stair and near a gray sculpture."
  },
  "1474": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirrors are in a living room."
  },
  "1475": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirrors are near a balcony."
  },
  "1476": {
    "question": "Question:what does the glass door look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle\uff0cmade of glass\uff0cit's black frame"
  },
  "1477": {
    "question": "Question:where is the glass door?",
    "answer": "Answer:the white big cabinet is placed opposite\uff0cthe glass door is close to white curtains"
  },
  "1478": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the glass door in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The glass door is placed opposite big white cabinet\uff0cclose to desk in big bedroom."
  },
  "1479": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the glass door?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a desk placed close to the door\uff0cand a chair is placed next to the desk in bedroom."
  },
  "1480": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bucket look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cylindrical, woody and brown"
  },
  "1481": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bucket?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed on a shelf at the left part of the cupboard."
  },
  "1482": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bucket in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "1483": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bucket?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to the chatting room and the door."
  },
  "1484": {
    "question": "Question:what does the flower look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:These are a few round, full bloom, white flowers."
  },
  "1485": {
    "question": "Question:where is the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:It was placed in a pot and placed on a round table."
  },
  "1486": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the flower in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is inside the entrance."
  },
  "1487": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is beside the stairs."
  },
  "1488": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is big, brown and wooden."
  },
  "1489": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a microwave and toaster below the cabinet."
  },
  "1490": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is placed above the microwave and the toaster near the toilet."
  },
  "1491": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a sink, mirror and toilet in the toilet. "
  },
  "1492": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, gray and white"
  },
  "1493": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:You can see a small pillow on the right side of the chair, and it's facing two beach chairs."
  },
  "1494": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in a second-floor balcony, which facing the main bedroom."
  },
  "1495": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The balcony is on the second floor of the villa, directly below the garden. "
  },
  "1496": {
    "question": "Question:what does the drawer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is white, rectangular and can be pushed and pulled."
  },
  "1497": {
    "question": "Question:where is the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is under the towel and brush."
  },
  "1498": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the drawer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is inside the bathroom."
  },
  "1499": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is under the towel and brush."
  },
  "1500": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:oval, white and light"
  },
  "1501": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on the brown cabinet next to the bed."
  },
  "1502": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a bedroom on the first floor."
  },
  "1503": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is at the right turn of the gate."
  },
  "1504": {
    "question": "Question:what does the paintings look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cylindrical, wall-mounted, colorful"
  },
  "1505": {
    "question": "Question:where is the paintings?",
    "answer": "Answer:hung on the wall, next to the window"
  },
  "1506": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the paintings in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the children's bedroom."
  },
  "1507": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the paintings?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the study and the bathroom."
  },
  "1508": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big,white,wooden"
  },
  "1509": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's near a chair and next to a door"
  },
  "1510": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a bedroom with a big washroom on the first floor"
  },
  "1511": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:the bedroom is near a corridor which is near a living room"
  },
  "1512": {
    "question": "Question:what does the elevator look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:gray, hollow, stable"
  },
  "1513": {
    "question": "Question:where is the elevator?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a trashcan, in front of a bar counter"
  },
  "1514": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the elevator in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The elevator is in a bar."
  },
  "1515": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the elevator?",
    "answer": "Answer:This bar connects with a gymnasium and has a small trashcan."
  },
  "1516": {
    "question": "Question:what does the wardrobe look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, wooden, brown"
  },
  "1517": {
    "question": "Question:where is the wardrobe?",
    "answer": "Answer:It face the bed and the French window"
  },
  "1518": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the wardrobe in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's put in a big and  bright main bedroom."
  },
  "1519": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the wardrobe?",
    "answer": "Answer:The master bedroom faces the balcony. Right below the room is the swimming pool."
  },
  "1520": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A small glass circular mirror."
  },
  "1521": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is over a small sink and a wooden desk with a granite platform."
  },
  "1522": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is set near the corner of the room."
  },
  "1523": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a stair and entrances to bedrooms."
  },
  "1524": {
    "question": "Question:what does the door look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden, square, square"
  },
  "1525": {
    "question": "Question:where is the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the painting, next to the desk"
  },
  "1526": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the door in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The door is located in the small bedroom."
  },
  "1527": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is in the end of the corridor and on the right of the end."
  },
  "1528": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Small, rectangular,  red."
  },
  "1529": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are lots of  chairs with the same size, shape and colour on its right  but  no chairs on its left."
  },
  "1530": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair  is  set in a small  room with a  red carpet."
  },
  "1531": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:This  area has lots of red  chairs and a  white desk."
  },
  "1532": {
    "question": "Question:what does the model look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:blue,with a big body,cylinder"
  },
  "1533": {
    "question": "Question:where is the model?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of a white wall,on the left of some plants and on the right of a orange model,on the wooden shell"
  },
  "1534": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the model in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The medel is in the canteen."
  },
  "1535": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the model?",
    "answer": "Answer:The medel is opposite to the door of the corridor and near the food bar."
  },
  "1536": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pot look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:stainless steel;black pot lid; cicular column;"
  },
  "1537": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pot?",
    "answer": "Answer:beside an oblate wooden box;on a wooden cabinet;"
  },
  "1538": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pot in?",
    "answer": "Answer:at the corner of this room;"
  },
  "1539": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pot?",
    "answer": "Answer:a room within two different mirrors and a glass shower cubicle;"
  },
  "1540": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown;simple; wooden;"
  },
  "1541": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:fases  a narrow bed; below a wall lamp;"
  },
  "1542": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:at the corner of a room;"
  },
  "1543": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:a room for massage;"
  },
  "1544": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stove look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black, rectangular, wall-mounted"
  },
  "1545": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stove?",
    "answer": "Answer:below the TV and next to the window"
  },
  "1546": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stove in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the bedroom "
  },
  "1547": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stove?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the corridor and on the second floor."
  },
  "1548": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a large new white cabinet."
  },
  "1549": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is under a microwave oven and a cabinet."
  },
  "1550": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in the kitchen.\n"
  },
  "1551": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to the study."
  },
  "1552": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black, a little tall, bright "
  },
  "1553": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the table and next to the plaid chair"
  },
  "1554": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the bedroom"
  },
  "1555": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the  corridor and on the second floor"
  },
  "1556": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:circle, white, ceramic"
  },
  "1557": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:below a light, in front of a mirror"
  },
  "1558": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is placed in the corner of a small bathroom."
  },
  "1559": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathroom is between a gym and a bedroom on the second floor."
  },
  "1560": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Tall,circular,metal"
  },
  "1561": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is set on the floor in a corner, near a lamp."
  },
  "1562": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is placed a small conference room."
  },
  "1563": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is set near a lareger conference room and next to the hall."
  },
  "1564": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Small, black and soild."
  },
  "1565": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is settled near a black sculpture, on a black bedside table and on the right side of a white and brown bed."
  },
  "1566": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is in a bedroom."
  },
  "1567": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is near a bathroom."
  },
  "1568": {
    "question": "Question:what does the glass look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Big,transparent,fragile"
  },
  "1569": {
    "question": "Question:where is the glass?",
    "answer": "Answer:The glass is set near a yellow jar on a yellow table ,in front of a sofa."
  },
  "1570": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the glass in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The glass is placed in the hall."
  },
  "1571": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the glass?",
    "answer": "Answer:The glass is set near a bedroom and a tearoom."
  },
  "1572": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is square and big."
  },
  "1573": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is next to the bathroom on the opposite of the bedroom door."
  },
  "1574": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is next to the bathroom on the opposite of the bedroom door in the bedroom."
  },
  "1575": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a big bed and bathroom in the bedroom."
  },
  "1576": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:glass, square, silver"
  },
  "1577": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the wall, above the table, facing the door"
  },
  "1578": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is set in the bright bedroom."
  },
  "1579": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is on the second floor, in the end of the corridor and on the left of the corridor when up to second floor."
  },
  "1580": {
    "question": "Question:what does the drawer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white\uff0cbig;ceramic;"
  },
  "1581": {
    "question": "Question:where is the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:above a white box;beside a wastebasket."
  },
  "1582": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the drawer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:against a wall with a telephone."
  },
  "1583": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:a narrow room with a narrow bed"
  },
  "1584": {
    "question": "Question:what does the drawer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a wooden, small, black drawer."
  },
  "1585": {
    "question": "Question:where is the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is directly below a wooden table and directly in front of a chair."
  },
  "1586": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the drawer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in the bedroom."
  },
  "1587": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is beside the corridor."
  },
  "1588": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cloth, big, blue"
  },
  "1589": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the carpet, next to the stairs"
  },
  "1590": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is located in the middle of the livingroom."
  },
  "1591": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The livingroom is on the first floor and next to the stairs."
  },
  "1592": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bookcase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:made of wood, small one, its color is white "
  },
  "1593": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bookcase?",
    "answer": "Answer:a beautiful painting is put at the top of the bookcase, and a leopard print sofa put close to it"
  },
  "1594": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bookcase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:A white bookcase is placed at the boundary of dining room and relaxing area, which is close to a leopard print sofa."
  },
  "1595": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bookcase?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a glass door close to the bookcase , and a carpet put close to the leopard print sofa."
  },
  "1596": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Medium size, soild and black and golden."
  },
  "1597": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is near a silvery and yellow vase and opposite to a black toilet."
  },
  "1598": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is in a toilet."
  },
  "1599": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is near a corridor and a kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "1600": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden and glass, middle, square"
  },
  "1601": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the wall, among three pictures and first from right"
  },
  "1602": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is set in the bright bedroom. "
  },
  "1603": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is in the central of the corridor, on the second floor and on the left of the stairs."
  },
  "1604": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White, soild and porcelainous."
  },
  "1605": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is set on the opposite side of a white toilet and near a blue and brown drawer."
  },
  "1606": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is in a bathroom."
  },
  "1607": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is near a corridor."
  },
  "1608": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:ceramic; white; squared;"
  },
  "1609": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:below a mirror with double yellow rims; beside two identical sinks and mirrors;opposite a urinal;"
  },
  "1610": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the far right of table and close to the corridor;"
  },
  "1611": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:a cubicle without a door;"
  },
  "1612": {
    "question": "Question:what does the closestool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:porcelain, white, medium"
  },
  "1613": {
    "question": "Question:where is the closestool?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a glass and a toiletries, in front of a towel rack"
  },
  "1614": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the closestool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The closestool is in the bathroom."
  },
  "1615": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the closestool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathroom is in the master bedroom and next to the cloakroom. "
  },
  "1616": {
    "question": "Question:what does the keyboard look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black,rectangle,metal,bumpy surface"
  },
  "1617": {
    "question": "Question:where is the keyboard?",
    "answer": "Answer:The keyboard is behind the cup and telephone,and it's on the right side of the screen."
  },
  "1618": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the keyboard in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The keyboard is in the number 361 small office."
  },
  "1619": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the keyboard?",
    "answer": "Answer:The room is along the corridor leading to the exit and at the corner of a junction of three roads."
  },
  "1620": {
    "question": "Question:what does the door look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A big clean glass door. "
  },
  "1621": {
    "question": "Question:where is the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is behind a dark green carpet and there are two chairs next to the door."
  },
  "1622": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the door in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The door connects indoor and outdoor."
  },
  "1623": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:The door is near a kitchen and a dining table."
  },
  "1624": {
    "question": "Question:what does the door look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A new wooden door."
  },
  "1625": {
    "question": "Question:where is the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is under the stair and faces a stove."
  },
  "1626": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the door in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is embeded in the wall."
  },
  "1627": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a living room and two stairs."
  },
  "1628": {
    "question": "Question:what does the potted plant look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:potted, round and green"
  },
  "1629": {
    "question": "Question:where is the potted plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is close to the fence and second closest to a door."
  },
  "1630": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the potted plant in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in front of the house."
  },
  "1631": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the potted plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is outside the house and in front of the gate."
  },
  "1632": {
    "question": "Question:what does the book look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, brown, paper"
  },
  "1633": {
    "question": "Question:where is the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a plant on its left. It has a display underneath it"
  },
  "1634": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the book in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's put in a  open kitchen."
  },
  "1635": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:Here you can see the swimming pool, reception area and a wicket."
  },
  "1636": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:blue, rectangle and woody"
  },
  "1637": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on the white carpet and facing the door."
  },
  "1638": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a bedroom on the first floor."
  },
  "1639": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is at the right turn of the gate.\n"
  },
  "1640": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bin look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rufous; small; columniform;"
  },
  "1641": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bin?",
    "answer": "Answer:beside a brown cabinet; against a wall with two long paintings;"
  },
  "1642": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bin in?",
    "answer": "Answer:at the turning of this corridor;"
  },
  "1643": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bin?",
    "answer": "Answer:a squared hall behind the front desk;"
  },
  "1644": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Medium size, red and brown and soild."
  },
  "1645": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set on the left side of two same chairs and a black wooden bookshelf, and below two pictures."
  },
  "1646": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in a study."
  },
  "1647": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is near a living room."
  },
  "1648": {
    "question": "Question:what does the refrigerator look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:silver, rectangular, big"
  },
  "1649": {
    "question": "Question:where is the refrigerator?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the cabinet, facing the table"
  },
  "1650": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the refrigerator in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The refrigerator is set in the bright kitchen."
  },
  "1651": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the refrigerator?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to the livingroom and next to the dining room."
  },
  "1652": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:metal frame, oblong and big."
  },
  "1653": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is on a cabinet and near a light which is on the wall."
  },
  "1654": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is in a bedroom."
  },
  "1655": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom leads outdoors via a door and connects with a washroom."
  },
  "1656": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Wooden, soild and round."
  },
  "1657": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is surrounded by three black wooden chairs which have blue mats, under the white hollowed-out tablecloth and near a brown wooden carbinet."
  },
  "1658": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is in the bedroom which has a blue carpet."
  },
  "1659": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is near a study."
  },
  "1660": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden and marble, square, brown"
  },
  "1661": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:behind the big sofa, facing the fireplace"
  },
  "1662": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is located in the kitchen."
  },
  "1663": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is on the first floor and next to the livingroom."
  },
  "1664": {
    "question": "Question:what does the decorations look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:colorful, flabellate, papery"
  },
  "1665": {
    "question": "Question:where is the decorations?",
    "answer": "Answer:on a wall, near a massage bed"
  },
  "1666": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the decorations in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The decorations are in a small bedroom."
  },
  "1667": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the decorations?",
    "answer": "Answer:This bedroom has one massage bed and connects with a gymnasium."
  },
  "1668": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Square, glass and clean."
  },
  "1669": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is near the bed and the lamp."
  },
  "1670": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Mirror is in the bedroom."
  },
  "1671": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is near the bathroom and living room."
  },
  "1672": {
    "question": "Question:what does the book look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle, piled and white"
  },
  "1673": {
    "question": "Question:where is the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed on the table next to the lamp."
  },
  "1674": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the book in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a chatting room on the first floor."
  },
  "1675": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chatting room is next to the hall."
  },
  "1676": {
    "question": "Question:what does the computer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:steel, grey and rectangle"
  },
  "1677": {
    "question": "Question:where is the computer?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed on the cabinet and next to a green plant."
  },
  "1678": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the computer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a living roon on the first floor."
  },
  "1679": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the computer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is the room facing the door."
  },
  "1680": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a large white cabinet with a square shape."
  },
  "1681": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is under a sink, next to a drawer."
  },
  "1682": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in the dining room."
  },
  "1683": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to a study and kitchen."
  },
  "1684": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stapler look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:red and black,metal,small"
  },
  "1685": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stapler?",
    "answer": "Answer:on a table,on the right of the receipt printer,at the back of the screen"
  },
  "1686": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stapler in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stapler is in a big office."
  },
  "1687": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stapler?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is in front of a corridor door and next to the tea room."
  },
  "1688": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Small, h-shaped and gray."
  },
  "1689": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is near a wooden brown table, near a green sofa and opposite to a brown sofa."
  },
  "1690": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in a bedroom."
  },
  "1691": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is near a corridor and a storage room."
  },
  "1692": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cloth, white, low"
  },
  "1693": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a mirror, facing a black table"
  },
  "1694": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is placed in a bright and tiny living room."
  },
  "1695": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living is next to a washroom and connect with a dining room on the first floor."
  },
  "1696": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:glass, square, big"
  },
  "1697": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the wall, next to the table"
  },
  "1698": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is set in the dining room."
  },
  "1699": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The dining room is next to the kitchen and balcony, on the third floor and facing a washroom."
  },
  "1700": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is small, green and round."
  },
  "1701": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is placed on the table next to the stove."
  },
  "1702": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is placed on the table facing the balcony."
  },
  "1703": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are many cabinets and sinks in the kitchen."
  },
  "1704": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is small, green and round."
  },
  "1705": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is placed on the table next to the stove."
  },
  "1706": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is placed on the table facing the balcony."
  },
  "1707": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are many cabinets and sinks in the kitchen."
  },
  "1708": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:round, glass and transparent"
  },
  "1709": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is the big one on the cabinet and closest to the green vase."
  },
  "1710": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a chatting room on the first floor."
  },
  "1711": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chatting room is next to the hall."
  },
  "1712": {
    "question": "Question:what does the flowerpot look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown,short,ceramics"
  },
  "1713": {
    "question": "Question:where is the flowerpot?",
    "answer": "Answer:under a green plant, on the right side of the dustbin and a sofa"
  },
  "1714": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the flowerpot in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flowerpot is in a vast reading hall. "
  },
  "1715": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the flowerpot?",
    "answer": "Answer:The reading hall is behind the restaurant and close to a meeting room and some boothes."
  },
  "1716": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, rectangular, low"
  },
  "1717": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:below a black and white picture, next to a window"
  },
  "1718": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in the corner of a bright living room on the first floor."
  },
  "1719": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is under a bedroom and is connected with a dining room."
  },
  "1720": {
    "question": "Question:what does the book look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:square, papery, black"
  },
  "1721": {
    "question": "Question:where is the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the table, under the mirror"
  },
  "1722": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the book in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The book is set in the bedroom."
  },
  "1723": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is on the second floor, on the left of the corridor when going upstairs and in the end of the corridor."
  },
  "1724": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Big, soild and cuboid."
  },
  "1725": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is near a transparent dining-table, underneath a picture and near two brown chairs."
  },
  "1726": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is in a dining room."
  },
  "1727": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is near a kitchen."
  },
  "1728": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown, little, Two-door cabinet"
  },
  "1729": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer: Right under it is a tap, There is a washing machine on it's right."
  },
  "1730": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is installed in a small laundry."
  },
  "1731": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer: The laundry is flanked by bedrooms, and there is a chandelier in front"
  },
  "1732": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cylindrical, transparent and small"
  },
  "1733": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed on the cabinet next to the trash bin."
  },
  "1734": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a hall on the first floor."
  },
  "1735": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The hall is next to the chatting room."
  },
  "1736": {
    "question": "Question:what does the telephone look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:plastic, stick-like and black"
  },
  "1737": {
    "question": "Question:where is the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is between the computer and the white telephone."
  },
  "1738": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the telephone in?",
    "answer": "Answer:\nIt is in living roon on the first floor."
  },
  "1739": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is the room facing the door."
  },
  "1740": {
    "question": "Question:what does the plant look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Green,short,wooden."
  },
  "1741": {
    "question": "Question:where is the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:The plant is placed in a blue basin in front of a window and near a tall lamp."
  },
  "1742": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the plant in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The plant is placed in a tearoom."
  },
  "1743": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:The plant is sei near a reading room and the hall."
  },
  "1744": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is large, soft and white."
  },
  "1745": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is beside the window and lamp."
  },
  "1746": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is in the bedroom."
  },
  "1747": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is beside the window and lamp."
  },
  "1748": {
    "question": "Question:what does the box look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:knitted; brown; closed; "
  },
  "1749": {
    "question": "Question:where is the box?",
    "answer": "Answer:beside a wooden bench; in front of a shower cubicle;"
  },
  "1750": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the box in?",
    "answer": "Answer:against the wall of this area in the corner of a hallway."
  },
  "1751": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the box?",
    "answer": "Answer:two shower cubicles by side of the long hallway."
  },
  "1752": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big,soft,double bed "
  },
  "1753": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's between 2 small bed-tables with 2 lamps,it's in front of a chair"
  },
  "1754": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in the bedroom on the first floor"
  },
  "1755": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:the bedroom is next to a washroom and a corridor"
  },
  "1756": {
    "question": "Question:what does the paintings look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular,colorful,wall-mounted"
  },
  "1757": {
    "question": "Question:where is the paintings?",
    "answer": "Answer:hung on the wall, next to the door"
  },
  "1758": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the paintings in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the children's bedroom."
  },
  "1759": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the paintings?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the study and the bathroom."
  },
  "1760": {
    "question": "Question:what does the glass door look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:galss made and iron frame, rectangle, big one "
  },
  "1761": {
    "question": "Question:where is the glass door?",
    "answer": "Answer:there are curtains close to the glass door, and the glass door is opposite the white bed."
  },
  "1762": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the glass door in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The glass door is installed in the detached bedroom which is placed opposite the white bed ,close to a small cabinet."
  },
  "1763": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the glass door?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a small wooden cabinet put close to the glass door ,and the white bed is a big one under a big picture."
  },
  "1764": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cloth-made,medium-size and in the middle of room"
  },
  "1765": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:the sofa is on a carpet and  in the front of the cabinet"
  },
  "1766": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:the sofa is in the center of the room"
  },
  "1767": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:there is a corridors outside the door"
  },
  "1768": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soild, wooden and white and yellow."
  },
  "1769": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set in front of a yellow and white table, a red lamp as well as a television and near a gray and black bed."
  },
  "1770": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in a bedroom."
  },
  "1771": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is near a corridor and a living room."
  },
  "1772": {
    "question": "Question:what does the oven look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The oven is large, cubic and silver."
  },
  "1773": {
    "question": "Question:where is the oven?",
    "answer": "Answer:The oven is to the right of the egg and drawer."
  },
  "1774": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the oven in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The oven in the kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "1775": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the oven?",
    "answer": "Answer:The oven is to the right of the egg and drawer."
  },
  "1776": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white,wood,big"
  },
  "1777": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the switch and the door"
  },
  "1778": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in entrance"
  },
  "1779": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is on the left of it"
  },
  "1780": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Crescent, big and black and gray."
  },
  "1781": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is set near a transparent oval sofa, opposite to a beige long sofa and in front of a black stove."
  },
  "1782": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is set in a living room."
  },
  "1783": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is near a dining room."
  },
  "1784": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soild, medium size and red and beige."
  },
  "1785": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is the fourth one in a row of chairs from left to right, on the opposite side of a mirror."
  },
  "1786": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in a reception room on the first floor."
  },
  "1787": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is near a porch."
  },
  "1788": {
    "question": "Question:what does the washbasin look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Beige and white, small and porcelainous."
  },
  "1789": {
    "question": "Question:where is the washbasin?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washbasin is settled near a bath and on the left side of a sink."
  },
  "1790": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the washbasin in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washbasin is in a bathroom."
  },
  "1791": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the washbasin?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washbasin is near a study."
  },
  "1792": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is irony, white and standing."
  },
  "1793": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is under the table. The stool is near the balcony."
  },
  "1794": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is placed under the table near the balcony."
  },
  "1795": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are many sinks and cabinets in the kitchen."
  },
  "1796": {
    "question": "Question:what does the television look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Rectangular, soild and black."
  },
  "1797": {
    "question": "Question:where is the television?",
    "answer": "Answer:The television is set near two black screens and near a big black fitness equipment."
  },
  "1798": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the television in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The television is set in a bedroom."
  },
  "1799": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the television?",
    "answer": "Answer:The television is near a corridor and a laundry."
  },
  "1800": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Yellow,plastic,tall."
  },
  "1801": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is placed under a yellow table, on the right of a yellow stool, near a white dustbin."
  },
  "1802": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is set in the hall."
  },
  "1803": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is placed near the gate and the front desk."
  },
  "1804": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cloth, gray, small"
  },
  "1805": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a black table, below a picture"
  },
  "1806": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is placed in a clean and bright living room."
  },
  "1807": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is next to a bashroom and there is a bashroom upstairs."
  },
  "1808": {
    "question": "Question:what does the potted plant look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:round, green and potted"
  },
  "1809": {
    "question": "Question:where is the potted plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to the open door and the pool.\n"
  },
  "1810": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the potted plant in?",
    "answer": "Answer:\nIt is in front of the house."
  },
  "1811": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the potted plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is outside the house and in front of the gate."
  },
  "1812": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bathtub look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White, porcelain and oblong."
  },
  "1813": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bathtub?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathtub near a washing basin and under a window."
  },
  "1814": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bathtub in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathtub is in a bathroom."
  },
  "1815": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bathtub?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area connects with a bedroom and near a toilet."
  },
  "1816": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black,metal,hard"
  },
  "1817": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a closetool and under a ronud mirror"
  },
  "1818": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a washroom on the first floor"
  },
  "1819": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:the washroom is next to a corridor which is near a bedroom and a rest room"
  },
  "1820": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white;oblong;shallow;"
  },
  "1821": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:above a trash can cocered by a plastic bag; below a mirror and near another mirror on the wall;"
  },
  "1822": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:beside the door of the room."
  },
  "1823": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:a room with two identical beds and a bathtub."
  },
  "1824": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a white, large, square cabinet."
  },
  "1825": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is under a cabinet, beside a stove."
  },
  "1826": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in the dining room."
  },
  "1827": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to a study and kitchen."
  },
  "1828": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, white, cloth"
  },
  "1829": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a table, in front of a bed"
  },
  "1830": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is settled in the corner of a big bedroom."
  },
  "1831": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is on the second floor and there is a balcony outside."
  },
  "1832": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Beige, floriated and leather."
  },
  "1833": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is near two beige and black chairs, in front of a black wooden screen, and near a small black bookshelf."
  },
  "1834": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in a living room with many pictures."
  },
  "1835": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is on the opposite side of a corridor."
  },
  "1836": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Beige, floriated and leather."
  },
  "1837": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is near two beige and black chairs, in front of a black wooden screen, and near a small black bookshelf."
  },
  "1838": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in a living room with many pictures."
  },
  "1839": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is on the opposite side of a corridor."
  },
  "1840": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Big,black,wooden"
  },
  "1841": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is placed  next to a yellow table and a brown box."
  },
  "1842": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is set in a tearoom."
  },
  "1843": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is placed next to the hall and near a reading room."
  },
  "1844": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown , woody , tall"
  },
  "1845": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:surrounded by a bed and a bathtub"
  },
  "1846": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is located next to a wall."
  },
  "1847": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is surrounded by a balcony , a living room and a bathroom."
  },
  "1848": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black,tall,plastic and metal,with five wheels"
  },
  "1849": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is between the cabinet and a desk and faces the gate."
  },
  "1850": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in a small office whose number is 361."
  },
  "1851": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office connects to the corridor leading to the exit and at the corner of a junction of three roads."
  },
  "1852": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Glass, blue frame, square"
  },
  "1853": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:Under the mirror is the sink, with one towel on each side"
  },
  "1854": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:mirror In the toilet"
  },
  "1855": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:Connecting the living room and bedroom"
  },
  "1856": {
    "question": "Question:what does the scissors look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:metal,yellow and black,small "
  },
  "1857": {
    "question": "Question:where is the scissors?",
    "answer": "Answer:The scissors are in front of a pink juicer and a white printer,next to a pen, on the left of two packets of snacks and above the cloths."
  },
  "1858": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the scissors in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The scissors are in an office which  contains numerous drink and snacks"
  },
  "1859": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the scissors?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is at the corner is at the corner of the three fork road and next to an empty office and opposite to the room 356."
  },
  "1860": {
    "question": "Question:what does the closestool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, oval, medium"
  },
  "1861": {
    "question": "Question:where is the closestool?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a mirror and toiletries, in front of a Frence door"
  },
  "1862": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the closestool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The closestool is in the bathroom."
  },
  "1863": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the closestool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathroom is next to the dining room and the study on the second floor."
  },
  "1864": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small one, it is short, the surface of table is made of glass"
  },
  "1865": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:two same tea tables are put on the rectangle carpet, they are put close to the big sofa"
  },
  "1866": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Two same triangle glass tea tables are put in the center of the big living room, on a big rectangle carpet."
  },
  "1867": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are several different size sofas put in the living room and a median size mirror is installed on the wall."
  },
  "1868": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White, cylindric and electronic."
  },
  "1869": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is on a wooden desk and near a chair and a picture."
  },
  "1870": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is in a narrow room."
  },
  "1871": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The narrow room is connected with an attic and stairs."
  },
  "1872": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black and dark yellow,small,round "
  },
  "1873": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a chair and there is a lamp on it."
  },
  "1874": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a corridor in front of a stair on the first floor"
  },
  "1875": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:the corridor links a living room ,2 bedrooms and a rest room."
  },
  "1876": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cylindrical, white, yellow"
  },
  "1877": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the white bed and another lamp with the same color and shape, near the window with black curtain"
  },
  "1878": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is in the bedroom."
  },
  "1879": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp faces a woody table with a white chair."
  },
  "1880": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a square, blue, old painting."
  },
  "1881": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are several porcelains and a fireplace under it."
  },
  "1882": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the living room.\n"
  },
  "1883": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:This living room is very neat and white.\n"
  },
  "1884": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:tall, big, woody and vitreous"
  },
  "1885": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the wall, below the paintings"
  },
  "1886": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the corridor"
  },
  "1887": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is between the living room and the bedroom on the second floor."
  },
  "1888": {
    "question": "Question:what does the door look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Closed, white rectangle door"
  },
  "1889": {
    "question": "Question:where is the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on the left side of the main door and close to the lower edge of the roof."
  },
  "1890": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the door in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a storeroom."
  },
  "1891": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:This storeroom is located at the end of the right turn on the second floor."
  },
  "1892": {
    "question": "Question:what does the trash look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A small black plastic trash."
  },
  "1893": {
    "question": "Question:where is the trash?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on the left side of the door ,facing a sink."
  },
  "1894": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the trash in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed in the kitchen,behind the cooktop."
  },
  "1895": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the trash?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a closet and a dining hall."
  },
  "1896": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is tall, white and round."
  },
  "1897": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is beside the door and under the lamp."
  },
  "1898": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is in the lounge."
  },
  "1899": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is beside the door and under the lamp."
  },
  "1900": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:circle, metal, silvery"
  },
  "1901": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a flower, above a drawer"
  },
  "1902": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is in a washroom on the first floor."
  },
  "1903": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washroom is next to a living room and a long corridor."
  },
  "1904": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is wooden, large and white."
  },
  "1905": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is to the right of the window and above the table."
  },
  "1906": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is in the kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "1907": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is to the right of the window and above the table."
  },
  "1908": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:gray, leather"
  },
  "1909": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:There's an identical chair next to it but it's more far away from the big sofa it. It's next to a LCD TV."
  },
  "1910": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is put on the reception area."
  },
  "1911": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area faces the open kitchen, next to the pool, and dinning table on the other side."
  },
  "1912": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:stone, circle, overground"
  },
  "1913": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pool?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are two chairs near the pool. The pool is next to another big pool."
  },
  "1914": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The pool is outdoor."
  },
  "1915": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The pool is next to a corridor. "
  },
  "1916": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:yellow, circular and woody"
  },
  "1917": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed between the window and the piano."
  },
  "1918": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:\nIt is in a chatting room on the first floor."
  },
  "1919": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chatting room is next to the hall."
  },
  "1920": {
    "question": "Question:what does the plant look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden,green,with several long leaves"
  },
  "1921": {
    "question": "Question:where is the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:under a display,on the locker and behind some chairs"
  },
  "1922": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the plant in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The plant is set in the rest area."
  },
  "1923": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:The plant is opposite to a meeting room and some boothes."
  },
  "1924": {
    "question": "Question:what does the tap look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:silver, iron"
  },
  "1925": {
    "question": "Question:where is the tap?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's right under a mirror and It's right above to a sink."
  },
  "1926": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the tap in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It was installed in the toilet in the workshop."
  },
  "1927": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the tap?",
    "answer": "Answer:Work room face the dinning room."
  },
  "1928": {
    "question": "Question:what does the display look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Rectangle, wide screen, liquid crystal"
  },
  "1929": {
    "question": "Question:where is the display?",
    "answer": "Answer:The display is hung on the wall and there is a big table surrounded by ten chairs in front of it."
  },
  "1930": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the display in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The display is placed in a big conference room."
  },
  "1931": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the display?",
    "answer": "Answer:The display is set near a smaller conference room."
  },
  "1932": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, oval and smooth"
  },
  "1933": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is beneath the mirror and next to the towel."
  },
  "1934": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a restroom on the second floor."
  },
  "1935": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The restroom is on the life side of the stairs."
  },
  "1936": {
    "question": "Question:what does the desk look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, black, wooden "
  },
  "1937": {
    "question": "Question:where is the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the door, in front of the bed"
  },
  "1938": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the desk in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The desk is located in the small bedroom."
  },
  "1939": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is in the end of the corridor and on the right of the end."
  },
  "1940": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bin look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small; no lid; columniform"
  },
  "1941": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bin?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the right of a big box; beside the sliding door;"
  },
  "1942": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bin in?",
    "answer": "Answer:near the rounded bar and a white fence;."
  },
  "1943": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bin?",
    "answer": "Answer:a big hall with a big sliding door."
  },
  "1944": {
    "question": "Question:what does the windows look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, transparent, glassy"
  },
  "1945": {
    "question": "Question:where is the windows?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a printer and a box, facing the outside"
  },
  "1946": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the windows in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The windows are in the wall in the living room."
  },
  "1947": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the windows?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are two doors and two shelves in the living room."
  },
  "1948": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:metal, cylinder, black and gold"
  },
  "1949": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of a mirror, next to a fire place"
  },
  "1950": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is placed in a big, bright and white living room."
  },
  "1951": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living is next to a long corridor on the first floor."
  },
  "1952": {
    "question": "Question:what does the drawer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, rectangular, wood"
  },
  "1953": {
    "question": "Question:where is the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:under a book, under a vase"
  },
  "1954": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the drawer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is in the center of a kitchen on the first floor.\n"
  },
  "1955": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to a big dining room and is next to a small storeroom."
  },
  "1956": {
    "question": "Question:what does the painting look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle, colorful, lots of spots"
  },
  "1957": {
    "question": "Question:where is the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:between  the closetool and the mirror"
  },
  "1958": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the painting in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is placed in a toilet  in one of the bedrooms"
  },
  "1959": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is next to the toilet. It is located in the second floor and there is a swimming pool downstairs. "
  },
  "1960": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is irony, round and standing."
  },
  "1961": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is placed under the table below the flower."
  },
  "1962": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is placed under the table below the flower between the kitchen and the dining room."
  },
  "1963": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are many chairs and desk in the dining room."
  },
  "1964": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:retangular, hairy, gray"
  },
  "1965": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the right of a short table, next to the glass wall and glass door, there are three pillows on it"
  },
  "1966": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is located in a spacious balcony."
  },
  "1967": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The balcony is outside the livingroom and next to the kitchen."
  },
  "1968": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:middle size,woolen,brown\n"
  },
  "1969": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a door and fixed on wall."
  },
  "1970": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a storage room in a bedroom on the second floor."
  },
  "1971": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:the storage room is in a bedroom which is near a corridor and a living room."
  },
  "1972": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cloth, rectangular, white"
  },
  "1973": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the carpet, around the table, facing the glass window, first from left"
  },
  "1974": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set in a spacious dining room."
  },
  "1975": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The dining room is on the third floor, next to the balcony and kitchen and next to a livingroom."
  },
  "1976": {
    "question": "Question:what does the power switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is irony, small and square."
  },
  "1977": {
    "question": "Question:where is the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is placed on the edge of the wall next to the door."
  },
  "1978": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the power switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is placed on the edge of the wall next to the door."
  },
  "1979": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are many pictures on the wall of the living room."
  },
  "1980": {
    "question": "Question:what does the power switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is irony, small and square."
  },
  "1981": {
    "question": "Question:where is the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is placed on the edge of the wall next to the door."
  },
  "1982": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the power switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is placed on the edge of the wall next to the door."
  },
  "1983": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are many pictures on the wall of the living room."
  },
  "1984": {
    "question": "Question:what does the shelf look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:woody, tall, brown"
  },
  "1985": {
    "question": "Question:where is the shelf?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a door, in front of a small table"
  },
  "1986": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the shelf in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is settled in a small study."
  },
  "1987": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the shelf?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area is next to a study and it is on the first floor. "
  },
  "1988": {
    "question": "Question:what does the shelf look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:woody, tall, brown"
  },
  "1989": {
    "question": "Question:where is the shelf?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a door, in front of a small table"
  },
  "1990": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the shelf in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is settled in a small study."
  },
  "1991": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the shelf?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area is next to a study and it is on the first floor. "
  },
  "1992": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a white picture with green leaf.\n"
  },
  "1993": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is directly above a wooden chair and switch on the wall."
  },
  "1994": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on a wall near the door."
  },
  "1995": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The wall of this painting is relatively old.\n"
  },
  "1996": {
    "question": "Question:what does the wine look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:glass,bottle,fragile"
  },
  "1997": {
    "question": "Question:where is the wine?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a vase with a bunch of flowers ,on a black table and next to a sofa."
  },
  "1998": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the wine in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's located in a living room on the first floor."
  },
  "1999": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the wine?",
    "answer": "Answer:the living room is near a dining room ,a kitchen and a corridor."
  },
  "2000": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Curved,columnar glass vase."
  },
  "2001": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is set on a table surrounded with chairs."
  },
  "2002": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the dining room at the center of a table."
  },
  "2003": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a kitchen and a stairway."
  },
  "2004": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sign look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:yellow; warning;plastic;"
  },
  "2005": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sign?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the right of a pillar;near a white carpet and a board;"
  },
  "2006": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sign in?",
    "answer": "Answer:by side of the swimming pool;"
  },
  "2007": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sign?",
    "answer": "Answer:a hall within a swimming pool;"
  },
  "2008": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white and gray, cloth, rectangular"
  },
  "2009": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the right of a tea table, facing a long table"
  },
  "2010": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is placed in the middle of a big and bright living room."
  },
  "2011": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is on the first floor and next to a corridor."
  },
  "2012": {
    "question": "Question:what does the elevator look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:gray, hollow, stable"
  },
  "2013": {
    "question": "Question:where is the elevator?",
    "answer": "Answer:a elevator on its left, near the stairs"
  },
  "2014": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the elevator in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The elevator is located in small bar."
  },
  "2015": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the elevator?",
    "answer": "Answer:This bar has a gray trashcan and a big bar counter. "
  },
  "2016": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A small,black and metal lamp. "
  },
  "2017": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is beside the bed and is on a wooden desk."
  },
  "2018": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is placed at the corner of the bedroom and is near the wall."
  },
  "2019": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near the entrance of the bedroom."
  },
  "2020": {
    "question": "Question:what does the drawer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Wooden, wood color, slender"
  },
  "2021": {
    "question": "Question:where is the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:Appliances on one side and coffee machine above the drawer"
  },
  "2022": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the drawer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:the drawer in the kitchen"
  },
  "2023": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:the drawer pposite is the living room\n"
  },
  "2024": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a brown, new, rectangular cabinet."
  },
  "2025": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a mirror and a pot of flowers directly above it."
  },
  "2026": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in a living room."
  },
  "2027": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's beside a kitchen."
  },
  "2028": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, columniform, fragile  "
  },
  "2029": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a big yellow picture, next to three transparent and white bottle  "
  },
  "2030": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in a bedroom."
  },
  "2031": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a rectangular balcony, a cloakroom, a washroom and a toilet in the bedroom. "
  },
  "2032": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:woody, small and yellow"
  },
  "2033": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to the lamp and beneath the window."
  },
  "2034": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a chatting room on the first floor."
  },
  "2035": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chatting room is next to the hall."
  },
  "2036": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bookstore look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soild, wooden and black."
  },
  "2037": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bookstore?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bookshelf is set beside a sculpture and near a metal stair."
  },
  "2038": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bookstore in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bookshelf is in a living room."
  },
  "2039": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bookstore?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bookshelf is near a balcony and a dining room."
  },
  "2040": {
    "question": "Question:what does the power switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is square, small and white."
  },
  "2041": {
    "question": "Question:where is the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is placed on the wall between the poster and the television."
  },
  "2042": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the power switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is placed on the wall between the poster and the television."
  },
  "2043": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are two tables, a sofa and recliner in the room."
  },
  "2044": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden, green and decorated."
  },
  "2045": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in front of a telescope and near a wooden desk which has a lamp on it."
  },
  "2046": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in a narrow room."
  },
  "2047": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The narrow room is connected with an attic and stairs."
  },
  "2048": {
    "question": "Question:what does the plant look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Tall, green, round roots"
  },
  "2049": {
    "question": "Question:where is the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:Pot culture in a black flower pot, next to the mirror"
  },
  "2050": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the plant in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Pot culture  in living room"
  },
  "2051": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:The pot culture is near the stairs and opposite the kitchen"
  },
  "2052": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:soft, red and leather."
  },
  "2053": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in front of a brown platform and next to a red leather stool."
  },
  "2054": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in a big living room."
  },
  "2055": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is next to a dining room and leads to outdoors via a door."
  },
  "2056": {
    "question": "Question:what does the closestool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:ceramic, ellipse, white"
  },
  "2057": {
    "question": "Question:where is the closestool?",
    "answer": "Answer:facing a door, next to a hand sink"
  },
  "2058": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the closestool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The closestool is settled in a small washroom facing a bathroom."
  },
  "2059": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the closestool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washroom is on the second and linked with a large bathroom."
  },
  "2060": {
    "question": "Question:what does the washing machine look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A grey metal drum washing machine."
  },
  "2061": {
    "question": "Question:where is the washing machine?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on the left of another drum washing machine and under a black cabinet."
  },
  "2062": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the washing machine in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the laundry room."
  },
  "2063": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the washing machine?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near the corridor on the second floor and a bedroom."
  },
  "2064": {
    "question": "Question:what does the beach chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:gray, rectangle,  armless "
  },
  "2065": {
    "question": "Question:where is the beach chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:Standing outside the door and looking in, on its left is another same beach chair, there is a little round stool between two chair"
  },
  "2066": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the beach chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in a second-floor balcony, which facing the main bedroom"
  },
  "2067": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the beach chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The balcony is on the second floor of the villa, directly below the garden"
  },
  "2068": {
    "question": "Question:what does the wardrobe look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden, rectangle, reddish brown "
  },
  "2069": {
    "question": "Question:where is the wardrobe?",
    "answer": "Answer:face the French window, next to the toilet"
  },
  "2070": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the wardrobe in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The wardrobe is put in a spacious and bright bedroom"
  },
  "2071": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the wardrobe?",
    "answer": "Answer:The balcony is next to the bedroom. It is located in the second floor and there is a swimming pool downstairs. "
  },
  "2072": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is large, cloth and white."
  },
  "2073": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is on the carpet and beside the table."
  },
  "2074": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is in the parlor on the first floor."
  },
  "2075": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is on the carpet and beside the table."
  },
  "2076": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Big, soft and striated."
  },
  "2077": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is in the middle of two wooden stools."
  },
  "2078": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is in a small bedroom."
  },
  "2079": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom where can see a kitchen and a stairs leads to a utility room via a ladder."
  },
  "2080": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stairs look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:stepped, woody and brown"
  },
  "2081": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stairs?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is covered by a patterned carpet and under a light."
  },
  "2082": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stairs in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is the access connecting the first and second floor."
  },
  "2083": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stairs?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is between the dining hall and the living room."
  },
  "2084": {
    "question": "Question:what does the door handle look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:curvy,clean and smooth."
  },
  "2085": {
    "question": "Question:where is the door handle?",
    "answer": "Answer:Next to the door handle are glass and wall."
  },
  "2086": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the door handle in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The door handle is on the glass door."
  },
  "2087": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the door handle?",
    "answer": "Answer:The door handle is between the balcony and the living room."
  },
  "2088": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stove look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a square, black, metal stove."
  },
  "2089": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stove?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is between the two cabinets."
  },
  "2090": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stove in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in the dining room."
  },
  "2091": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stove?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to a study and kitchen."
  },
  "2092": {
    "question": "Question:what does the photo look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Colorful, rectangular and small."
  },
  "2093": {
    "question": "Question:where is the photo?",
    "answer": "Answer:The photo is set near a colorful photo, above a pink box and near a black fitness equipment."
  },
  "2094": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the photo in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The photo is in a bedroom."
  },
  "2095": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the photo?",
    "answer": "Answer:The photo is near a toilet and a corridor."
  },
  "2096": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mouse look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small,metal,black"
  },
  "2097": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mouse?",
    "answer": "Answer:behind a keyboard and a telephone and on the left side of a yellow note"
  },
  "2098": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mouse in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mouse is on a desk of a big office with a number 302."
  },
  "2099": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mouse?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is along the corridor connecting the tea room and the restaurant and in front of some meeting room."
  },
  "2100": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bedside table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle, black, wooden"
  },
  "2101": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bedside table?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a lamp on it, it's on the right side of the bed."
  },
  "2102": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bedside table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's put in a big and  bright main bedroom."
  },
  "2103": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bedside table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The master bedroom faces the balcony. Right below the room is the swimming pool."
  },
  "2104": {
    "question": "Question:what does the display look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black,rectangle,thin"
  },
  "2105": {
    "question": "Question:where is the display?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the wall,on the right of the clock and over a shell"
  },
  "2106": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the display in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The display is in a meeting room which has the number 05."
  },
  "2107": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the display?",
    "answer": "Answer:The meeting room is by the side of the vast reading area and behind the restaurant."
  },
  "2108": {
    "question": "Question:what does the washstand look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:metal,white,smooth"
  },
  "2109": {
    "question": "Question:where is the washstand?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's near some cups and 2 balls."
  },
  "2110": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the washstand in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's on a white table in the kitchen on the second floor."
  },
  "2111": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the washstand?",
    "answer": "Answer:the kitchen is near a living room and a open-balcony."
  },
  "2112": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:square, iron."
  },
  "2113": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:A tap is right above it, and a display is on its left."
  },
  "2114": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's installed in a  open kitchen."
  },
  "2115": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer: Here you can see the swimming pool, reception area and a wicket."
  },
  "2116": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Small, soild and rectangular."
  },
  "2117": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is in the first row, the first column and on the opposite side of a big picture themed with mountain and lake and tree."
  },
  "2118": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is in a living room on the second floor."
  },
  "2119": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is next to a study."
  },
  "2120": {
    "question": "Question:what does the water glass look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cylindrical,limpid,with a grey lib"
  },
  "2121": {
    "question": "Question:where is the water glass?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the edge of the desk,on the right side of the computer, in front of two white machines and behind the limpid"
  },
  "2122": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the water glass in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in the number 366 room which is so small that only allow one man working in it. "
  },
  "2123": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the water glass?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is next to a relax area placed some sofas and connects to a road leading to the tea room and locker room.\n"
  },
  "2124": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, red, fabric"
  },
  "2125": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed next to the drawer, near the chair. Three pillows on it."
  },
  "2126": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is in a bedroom."
  },
  "2127": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed faces the window."
  },
  "2128": {
    "question": "Question:what does the light look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Veined, round tabled and luminescent"
  },
  "2129": {
    "question": "Question:where is the light?",
    "answer": "Answer:It has a woody table lamp holder and there are some small holes in the lampshade."
  },
  "2130": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the light in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is beneath a pciture on the wall and beside the pillows on the bed."
  },
  "2131": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the light?",
    "answer": "Answer:This bedroom is located at the end of the right turn on the second floor, next to another bedroom and a storage room."
  },
  "2132": {
    "question": "Question:what does the gas stove look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A metal gas stove."
  },
  "2133": {
    "question": "Question:where is the gas stove?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is under a kitchen ventilator and faces a long white table with a sink."
  },
  "2134": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the gas stove in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a kitchen."
  },
  "2135": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the gas stove?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a dining room and a living room."
  },
  "2136": {
    "question": "Question:what does the desk look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small , short, woody "
  },
  "2137": {
    "question": "Question:where is the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:across from the washroom and next to the bed "
  },
  "2138": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the desk in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the bedroom"
  },
  "2139": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the corridor and another bedroom."
  },
  "2140": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:static,dark,square,soft"
  },
  "2141": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to 2 same style chairs and near a woolen desk ."
  },
  "2142": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a study room on the second floor"
  },
  "2143": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:the study room is near a balcony and there is a stair in the corner in study room"
  },
  "2144": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cup look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, black, ceramic"
  },
  "2145": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cup?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the first floor of the cup holder, on the left of the right dish "
  },
  "2146": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cup in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cup is set in a small kitchen."
  },
  "2147": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cup?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is on the first floor and next to the livingroom."
  },
  "2148": {
    "question": "Question:what does the box look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Red,small,plastic."
  },
  "2149": {
    "question": "Question:where is the box?",
    "answer": "Answer:The box is set on a yellow box in a shelf."
  },
  "2150": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the box in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The box is placed in the hall."
  },
  "2151": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the box?",
    "answer": "Answer:The box is placed near a small conference room and a big conference room."
  },
  "2152": {
    "question": "Question:what does the door look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A brown wooden curved door."
  },
  "2153": {
    "question": "Question:where is the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is at the entrance of a bedroom and near the corridor."
  },
  "2154": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the door in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a bedroom."
  },
  "2155": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near another bedroom and a toilet."
  },
  "2156": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is big, square and glass."
  },
  "2157": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The toilet is below the picture. The picture is on the wall."
  },
  "2158": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is hung on the wall above the toilet."
  },
  "2159": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a sink, toilet and mirror in the toilet."
  },
  "2160": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:fluffy,yellow,soft"
  },
  "2161": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a big round table ,3 same chairs and behind a big sofa"
  },
  "2162": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in the dining room on the first floor."
  },
  "2163": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:the dining room is near a living room and a stair"
  },
  "2164": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:ceramic,white and green,fragile,with plants"
  },
  "2165": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's below a hang lamp and a big mirror"
  },
  "2166": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's located on the stair between first floor and second floor"
  },
  "2167": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:the stair is in the corner of the study room on the second floor and in the corridor on the first floor"
  },
  "2168": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:ceramic,white and green,fragile,with plants"
  },
  "2169": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's below a hang lamp and a big mirror"
  },
  "2170": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's located on the stair between first floor and second floor"
  },
  "2171": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:the stair is in the corner of the study room on the second floor and in the corridor on the first floor"
  },
  "2172": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a trapezoidal brown wooden table lamp.\n"
  },
  "2173": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a porcelain to the right of it, and a wooden table under it.\n"
  },
  "2174": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is inside a small balcony.\n"
  },
  "2175": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a very bright balcony.\n"
  },
  "2176": {
    "question": "Question:what does the shoebox look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cuboid, stand hard by the wall, it's made of wood and its color is brown"
  },
  "2177": {
    "question": "Question:where is the shoebox?",
    "answer": "Answer:there is a photo and a vase put on the shoebox, it is put opposite the big bed "
  },
  "2178": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the shoebox in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The shoebox is placed hard by the wall , opposite the big bed close to the door of big bedroom."
  },
  "2179": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the shoebox?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are three drawers attached with the shoebox, and the bedroom is the one inside the relaxing area ,which is attached with a bathroom and work place."
  },
  "2180": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Black and beige, soild and wooden."
  },
  "2181": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is settled near a beige leather sofa, in front of a black wooden screen and near a small black bookshelf."
  },
  "2182": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in a living room."
  },
  "2183": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is on the opposite side of a corridor."
  },
  "2184": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pen look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:blue,plastic,clubbed,small"
  },
  "2185": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pen?",
    "answer": "Answer:The pen is on a white book,between two chairs and near a computer,a mouse and a keyboard."
  },
  "2186": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pen in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The pen is in a median size meeting room with the identifier of 348."
  },
  "2187": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pen?",
    "answer": "Answer:The meeting room is at the corner of the three fork road,opposite to an empty  room and has a corridor connecting to the rest area. "
  },
  "2188": {
    "question": "Question:what does the potted plant look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:green, woody, full of vigour "
  },
  "2189": {
    "question": "Question:where is the potted plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:near a massgive bed, next to the decorations"
  },
  "2190": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the potted plant in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The potted plant is put in the corner of a massage bedroom."
  },
  "2191": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the potted plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:This bedroom has a massage bed and decorations which are on the wall."
  },
  "2192": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Genuine leather\uff0cSingle sofa."
  },
  "2193": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:There have four sofas in the last row. Facing forward, It's third from left to right.It's under the projector."
  },
  "2194": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in the last row of the screening hall, facing the door direction from left to right, the third sofa."
  },
  "2195": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The nearest area is the living room."
  },
  "2196": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bowl look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, ceramic, circle"
  },
  "2197": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bowl?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of a picture, above a drawer"
  },
  "2198": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bowl in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bowl is in the corner of a kitchen with wood floor on the first floor."
  },
  "2199": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bowl?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to a small storeroom and there is a road outside."
  },
  "2200": {
    "question": "Question:what does the power switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is white, plastic and square."
  },
  "2201": {
    "question": "Question:where is the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is on the wall and under the electronic thermometer."
  },
  "2202": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the power switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is in the living room on the first floor."
  },
  "2203": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is on the wall and under the electronic thermometer."
  },
  "2204": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Meidum size, soild and rectangular."
  },
  "2205": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is above a white sink and opposite to a green painting with golden border."
  },
  "2206": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is in a toilet."
  },
  "2207": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is near a study."
  },
  "2208": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is an irregularly shaped, large, white chair."
  },
  "2209": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is beside a table and lamp."
  },
  "2210": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in the bedroom."
  },
  "2211": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is beside the corridor."
  },
  "2212": {
    "question": "Question:what does the switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:plastic, square and hanged"
  },
  "2213": {
    "question": "Question:where is the switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is facing the cabinet and the door."
  },
  "2214": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is hanging on the wall in a hall."
  },
  "2215": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is between the outdoor hall and the chatting room."
  },
  "2216": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, white, wall-mounted"
  },
  "2217": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the refrigerator, hung on the white wall"
  },
  "2218": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the kitchen. "
  },
  "2219": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a living room and a dining room next to the kitchen."
  },
  "2220": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bookshelf look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:tall,brown,wooden,with lots of books"
  },
  "2221": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bookshelf?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the right of a pillar,on the left of some black knapsacks"
  },
  "2222": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bookshelf in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bookshelf is in a big office."
  },
  "2223": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bookshelf?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is in front of a corridor door,along the road connecting the tea room and the restaurant."
  },
  "2224": {
    "question": "Question:what does the kettle look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:steel, round and grey"
  },
  "2225": {
    "question": "Question:where is the kettle?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed on a shelf at the right side of the cupboard."
  },
  "2226": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the kettle in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "2227": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the kettle?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to the chatting room and the door."
  },
  "2228": {
    "question": "Question:what does the toilet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:middle, cuboid, white"
  },
  "2229": {
    "question": "Question:where is the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:in the middle of the washstand and the glass wall, under the picture"
  },
  "2230": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the toilet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The toilet is located in the washroom."
  },
  "2231": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washroom is inside the bedroom, which is on the second floor, on the left of the stairs and in the central of the corridor."
  },
  "2232": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a wooden, huge, yellow-brown cabinet."
  },
  "2233": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to a switch and a fireplace."
  },
  "2234": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in the bedroom."
  },
  "2235": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is beside the corridor."
  },
  "2236": {
    "question": "Question:what does the armchair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown, wood and cloth,near the window"
  },
  "2237": {
    "question": "Question:where is the armchair?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a desk and another chair"
  },
  "2238": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the armchair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's at the corner of the room"
  },
  "2239": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the armchair?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a corridor outside the room"
  },
  "2240": {
    "question": "Question:what does the clock look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, golden, square                                                                                                                      "
  },
  "2241": {
    "question": "Question:where is the clock?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of a table, in the fifth layer of the shelf"
  },
  "2242": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the clock in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The clock is settled in a study."
  },
  "2243": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the clock?",
    "answer": "Answer:The study has a lot of books and connects with the outside."
  },
  "2244": {
    "question": "Question:what does the trash can look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Metal, silver and empty."
  },
  "2245": {
    "question": "Question:where is the trash can?",
    "answer": "Answer:The trash can is under the washstand and towel"
  },
  "2246": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the trash can in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Trash can in the bathroom."
  },
  "2247": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the trash can?",
    "answer": "Answer:The trash can is close to the bathroom and bedroom."
  },
  "2248": {
    "question": "Question:what does the dining-table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A medium-sized wooden table surrounded by chairs."
  },
  "2249": {
    "question": "Question:where is the dining-table?",
    "answer": "Answer:On the table are a greenplant and two containers with biscuits."
  },
  "2250": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the dining-table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the dining room."
  },
  "2251": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the dining-table?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near the kitchen."
  },
  "2252": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is wooden, rectangular and white."
  },
  "2253": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is behind the door and beside the table."
  },
  "2254": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is in the kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "2255": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is behind the door and beside the table."
  },
  "2256": {
    "question": "Question:what does the paintings look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Rectangular, papery and thin."
  },
  "2257": {
    "question": "Question:where is the paintings?",
    "answer": "Answer:The newspaper is set on the left side on five paintings and near a brassy switch."
  },
  "2258": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the paintings in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The newspaper is in a corridor on the second floor."
  },
  "2259": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the paintings?",
    "answer": "Answer:The newspaper is near a bedroom."
  },
  "2260": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cloth, gray and yellow, rectangular"
  },
  "2261": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a picture, facing a table"
  },
  "2262": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is settled in the corner of a kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "2263": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to a big dining room and there is a road outside."
  },
  "2264": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A long black cabinet with drawers."
  },
  "2265": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a lamp on the cabinet and it is below pictures."
  },
  "2266": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a living room behind a white sofa."
  },
  "2267": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a stair to a kicthen and a balcony."
  },
  "2268": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Wooden,big,red."
  },
  "2269": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is placed under a yellow table, behind a white computer."
  },
  "2270": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is set in tha hall."
  },
  "2271": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is placed near a big conference room and a tea room."
  },
  "2272": {
    "question": "Question:what does the photo look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden and glass, square, middle"
  },
  "2273": {
    "question": "Question:where is the photo?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the table, next to the vase, in the middle of two sofas, in front of a photo"
  },
  "2274": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the photo in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The photo is set in the spacious livingroom."
  },
  "2275": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the photo?",
    "answer": "Answer:The livingroom is on the first floor and next to the dining room."
  },
  "2276": {
    "question": "Question:what does the drawer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wood,big,under the cupboard"
  },
  "2277": {
    "question": "Question:where is the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's under the cupboard and switch"
  },
  "2278": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the drawer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in corridor"
  },
  "2279": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's dining room  on the left side of the drawer and kitchen on the right."
  },
  "2280": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is big, square and colorful."
  },
  "2281": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is hung on the wall facing the column."
  },
  "2282": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is hung on the wall facing the column in the living room."
  },
  "2283": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a big set of sofa, chairs and tables in the living room."
  },
  "2284": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bin look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big; having a lid; knitted;"
  },
  "2285": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bin?",
    "answer": "Answer:beside a tall cabinet; below a metal rack;"
  },
  "2286": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bin in?",
    "answer": "Answer:at the corner of the changing room;beside a shower cubicle;"
  },
  "2287": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bin?",
    "answer": "Answer:a changing room with two mirrors on the wall;"
  },
  "2288": {
    "question": "Question:what does the telephone look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Small, quadrangular and black."
  },
  "2289": {
    "question": "Question:where is the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:The telephone is settled below a painting, near two black screens and a black television."
  },
  "2290": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the telephone in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The telephone is in a bedroom."
  },
  "2291": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:The telephone is near a corridor."
  },
  "2292": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Medium size, wooden and leather and soild."
  },
  "2293": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is the fisrt one of a row from left to right and it is near a big chair and opposite to a tall mirror."
  },
  "2294": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in a reception room."
  },
  "2295": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is near a porch."
  },
  "2296": {
    "question": "Question:what does the Shower look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small ,round,white"
  },
  "2297": {
    "question": "Question:where is the Shower?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's hang on a yellow wall and near a big glass."
  },
  "2298": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the Shower in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a washroom on the first floor."
  },
  "2299": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the Shower?",
    "answer": "Answer:the washroom is near a corridor and a stair."
  },
  "2300": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:steel, rectangle and grey"
  },
  "2301": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed on the cabinet and next to a bucket."
  },
  "2302": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "2303": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to the chatting room and the door."
  },
  "2304": {
    "question": "Question:what does the oven look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:grey,standby,big"
  },
  "2305": {
    "question": "Question:where is the oven?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's on the left of the microwave oven and fridge"
  },
  "2306": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the oven in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in the kitchen"
  },
  "2307": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the oven?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is on the right of it"
  },
  "2308": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white,rectangle,wooden"
  },
  "2309": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:between two tables,on the left side of the room"
  },
  "2310": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is in a small office with the number 306."
  },
  "2311": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is at the corner of the crossroads and near the tea room and the locker room."
  },
  "2312": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cloth, black, rectangular"
  },
  "2313": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a bed, facing a chair"
  },
  "2314": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is settled in the center of a large bedroom."
  },
  "2315": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is on the second floor and has a balcony. There is a living room downstairs."
  },
  "2316": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is rectangular, hard and white."
  },
  "2317": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is below a sculpture and to the right of a switch."
  },
  "2318": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is on the first floor living room."
  },
  "2319": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is below a sculpture and to the right of a switch."
  },
  "2320": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:linen, square, and gray\n"
  },
  "2321": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:beside a table, in front of the bed"
  },
  "2322": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is put in a spacious and bright bedroom"
  },
  "2323": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The balcony is next to the bedroom. It is located in the second floor and there is a swimming pool downstairs. "
  },
  "2324": {
    "question": "Question:what does the light look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Vertical,tall,metal"
  },
  "2325": {
    "question": "Question:where is the light?",
    "answer": "Answer:The light is set in front of a window and next to a dustbin."
  },
  "2326": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the light in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The light is placed in a tearoom."
  },
  "2327": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the light?",
    "answer": "Answer:The light is placed next to  the hall and near a reading room."
  },
  "2328": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Yellow, four-legged, wooden."
  },
  "2329": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is under a yellow table with black stools on either side."
  },
  "2330": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is in the hall."
  },
  "2331": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is placed next to the gate and a conference room."
  },
  "2332": {
    "question": "Question:what does the door look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:tall, transparent, stable"
  },
  "2333": {
    "question": "Question:where is the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:between two shelves, near a printer and a box"
  },
  "2334": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the door in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The door is located in a living room."
  },
  "2335": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is in the first floor and has a tall shelf with some photos in the corner."
  },
  "2336": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black,tall,plastic and metal,with two handrails"
  },
  "2337": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of several boxes on the floor,leaning against the table,opposite to the gate"
  },
  "2338": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in a small single office."
  },
  "2339": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is next to a relaxing area and meets a road leading to the tea room and locker room and opposite to a corridor."
  },
  "2340": {
    "question": "Question:what does the shutter look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Rectangular, soild and black."
  },
  "2341": {
    "question": "Question:where is the shutter?",
    "answer": "Answer:The shutter is set in front of a white and brown bed and two small black tables."
  },
  "2342": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the shutter in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The shutter is in a bedroom."
  },
  "2343": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the shutter?",
    "answer": "Answer:The shutter is near a bathroom."
  },
  "2344": {
    "question": "Question:what does the shelf look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black, woody, two-layer"
  },
  "2345": {
    "question": "Question:where is the shelf?",
    "answer": "Answer:a printer and a box on it, against a wall"
  },
  "2346": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the shelf in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The shelf is in a living room."
  },
  "2347": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the shelf?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area has three pictures on the wall and two doors."
  },
  "2348": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is large, wooden and black."
  },
  "2349": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is between the table and the pillar."
  },
  "2350": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is beside the outdoor swimming pool."
  },
  "2351": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is between the table and the pillar."
  },
  "2352": {
    "question": "Question:what does the container look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:An old brown wooden container. "
  },
  "2353": {
    "question": "Question:where is the container?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a linen container and under the stair."
  },
  "2354": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the container in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It locates at the innermost position below the stairs"
  },
  "2355": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the container?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near the living room."
  },
  "2356": {
    "question": "Question:what does the flower look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is big, white and blossoming."
  },
  "2357": {
    "question": "Question:where is the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is put in the vase on the table."
  },
  "2358": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the flower in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is put in the vase on the table against the wall."
  },
  "2359": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a set of sofa and table outside."
  },
  "2360": {
    "question": "Question:what does the flower look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is white and blossoming."
  },
  "2361": {
    "question": "Question:where is the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is put in the vase on the table. "
  },
  "2362": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the flower in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is placed on the table against the wall facing the door."
  },
  "2363": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a set of sofa and a table outside the door."
  },
  "2364": {
    "question": "Question:what does the flower look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is white and blossoming."
  },
  "2365": {
    "question": "Question:where is the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is placed on the table against the wall."
  },
  "2366": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the flower in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is put in the vase on the table against the wall."
  },
  "2367": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stairs are on the opposite."
  },
  "2368": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:round,middle size,reflective"
  },
  "2369": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a ceramic bathtub and a shower."
  },
  "2370": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a bathroom on the second floor."
  },
  "2371": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:the bathroom is in a big bedroom which is in the end of a corridor and near a open-balcony."
  },
  "2372": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden,square and comfortable."
  },
  "2373": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is close to the desk and the glass."
  },
  "2374": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is on the balcony."
  },
  "2375": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set near the bedroom and living room."
  },
  "2376": {
    "question": "Question:what does the decorations look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Medium sizem white and silken."
  },
  "2377": {
    "question": "Question:where is the decorations?",
    "answer": "Answer:The decorations are set near a black and gray sofa and next to a brown wooden table."
  },
  "2378": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the decorations in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The decorations are in a living room."
  },
  "2379": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the decorations?",
    "answer": "Answer:The decorations are near a dining room."
  },
  "2380": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bottle look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, cylindrical, fragile"
  },
  "2381": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bottle?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the cabinet, below the cabinet"
  },
  "2382": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bottle in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the kitchen."
  },
  "2383": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bottle?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the living room and the dining room."
  },
  "2384": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bathtub look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:ceramic, white, rectangular"
  },
  "2385": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bathtub?",
    "answer": "Answer:below a picture, in front of a flower"
  },
  "2386": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bathtub in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathtub is in the corner of a large bathroom on the second floor."
  },
  "2387": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bathtub?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathroom is next to a cloakroom and has a balcony. "
  },
  "2388": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A metal upholstered chair with white cloth,a backrest and armrests."
  },
  "2389": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is close to a cabinet with flowers on it and is near the stairway."
  },
  "2390": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is set against the wall."
  },
  "2391": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a table."
  },
  "2392": {
    "question": "Question:what does the microwave look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The microwave is power-off, made of steel and big."
  },
  "2393": {
    "question": "Question:where is the microwave?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a cabinet above. There is a toaster besides."
  },
  "2394": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the microwave in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is placed next to the toaster below the cabinet near the toilet."
  },
  "2395": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the microwave?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a toilet, mirror and sink in the toilet."
  },
  "2396": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bookcase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:square ,white ,it's very big "
  },
  "2397": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bookcase?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a ladder put close to the bookcase for people to take the purpose book ,and there is a balcony opposite the bookcase."
  },
  "2398": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bookcase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bookcase is put next to the door ,which is front facing the balcony in the relaxing area."
  },
  "2399": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bookcase?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a brown cloth sofa put front facing the big white bookcase ,and a circle table put next to the balcony."
  },
  "2400": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:mental,long,and bright"
  },
  "2401": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's on a round table and in front of a big window"
  },
  "2402": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:the lamp is in the living room"
  },
  "2403": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:the living room is near the dining room ,dining room is near the kitchen"
  },
  "2404": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is glass, big and square."
  },
  "2405": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are some flowers on the table. There are many chairs under the table."
  },
  "2406": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is placed in the dining room near the kitchen."
  },
  "2407": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are many recliners and sofas in the balcony."
  },
  "2408": {
    "question": "Question:what does the computer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:standing,middle size,consisting of three parts,black"
  },
  "2409": {
    "question": "Question:where is the computer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The computer is on a white office table , in front of a black chair and at the side of a short cabinet."
  },
  "2410": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the computer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The computer is in an office that has the number 357"
  },
  "2411": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the computer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is on the side of a fork in the road and is opposite to an empty office."
  },
  "2412": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White, porcelain, cylindrical"
  },
  "2413": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:Below is the dining table with white flowers in the vase and some tableware next to it"
  },
  "2414": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:the vase between the kitchen and the living room"
  },
  "2415": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The back of vase is the living room and the front is the kitchen"
  },
  "2416": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bread maker look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:steel, square and grey"
  },
  "2417": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bread maker?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed on a cabinet and close to a vase."
  },
  "2418": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bread maker in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "2419": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bread maker?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to the chatting room and the door."
  },
  "2420": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Woody, red ,rectangular ."
  },
  "2421": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are two chairs with the same size and state on its right and two chairs with the same size and state on its left.There are four chairs with the same size and state opposite to it."
  },
  "2422": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set on a side of the corridor via the altar."
  },
  "2423": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area has a fan and lots of benches on each side of the corridor ."
  },
  "2424": {
    "question": "Question:what does the Fitness Equipment look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:metal,stand on the floor,black"
  },
  "2425": {
    "question": "Question:where is the Fitness Equipment?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's on the right of arm apparatus and treadwill"
  },
  "2426": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the Fitness Equipment in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a room at the end of the corridor"
  },
  "2427": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the Fitness Equipment?",
    "answer": "Answer:there is a small toilet"
  },
  "2428": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a white wooden chair with leather, seats and leaning against the wall."
  },
  "2429": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's on the left of a wooden table, just below a glowing table lamp."
  },
  "2430": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It faces the main entrance of the house."
  },
  "2431": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a corridor near the door of the house, and there is a study room directly behind the chair."
  },
  "2432": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:glass, circle"
  },
  "2433": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a lamp on the table and two chairs in front of the table."
  },
  "2434": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is put on the reception area."
  },
  "2435": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area faces the open kitchen, next to the pool, and dinning table on the other side."
  },
  "2436": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Brown, woody and glass-covered"
  },
  "2437": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is opposite a cabinet and at the far left side of the three pictures hung on the wall."
  },
  "2438": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a hall directly opposite the stairway."
  },
  "2439": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The hall is on the second floor."
  },
  "2440": {
    "question": "Question:what does the book look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:red,white and orange,paper,thick"
  },
  "2441": {
    "question": "Question:where is the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:under the display,in the brown shell and above a dustbin "
  },
  "2442": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the book in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is in a small meeting room with a number 02."
  },
  "2443": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:The meeting room is along a corridor leading to the lobby and between two stairway doors."
  },
  "2444": {
    "question": "Question:what does the tissue look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White, cloth, folded"
  },
  "2445": {
    "question": "Question:where is the tissue?",
    "answer": "Answer:Hanging on a metal shelf on the wall with a sink next to it"
  },
  "2446": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the tissue in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Tissue In the bathroom"
  },
  "2447": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the tissue?",
    "answer": "Answer:Tissue between the living room stairs and the bedroom"
  },
  "2448": {
    "question": "Question:what does the washstand look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Metal, clean and silver."
  },
  "2449": {
    "question": "Question:where is the washstand?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washstand is on the table, in front of the mirror."
  },
  "2450": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the washstand in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washstand is in the living room."
  },
  "2451": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the washstand?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washstand is close to the bedroom and bathroom."
  },
  "2452": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:plaid, big, soft"
  },
  "2453": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the woody desks and the woody chair"
  },
  "2454": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the bedroom"
  },
  "2455": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the corridor and another bedroom."
  },
  "2456": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:square, middle, white and black"
  },
  "2457": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the wall, facing the stairs, among six pictures and second from left"
  },
  "2458": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is set on the corridor."
  },
  "2459": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The corridor is on the second floor, has some rooms and two stairs."
  },
  "2460": {
    "question": "Question:what does the flower look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is white, round and tall."
  },
  "2461": {
    "question": "Question:where is the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is above the vase and the table."
  },
  "2462": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the flower in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is in the lounge."
  },
  "2463": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is above the vase and the table."
  },
  "2464": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:long,soft,brown and with some pillows on it"
  },
  "2465": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of some bikes,opposite to a black sofa and faces a little desk"
  },
  "2466": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in the lobby."
  },
  "2467": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in front of the service desk and behind the entrance door."
  },
  "2468": {
    "question": "Question:what does the box look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, rectangular, woody, burlywood"
  },
  "2469": {
    "question": "Question:where is the box?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a bottle and a door, above a television"
  },
  "2470": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the box in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The box is settled in a bright living room."
  },
  "2471": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the box?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room has a big sofa on the carpet and a lamp on the table."
  },
  "2472": {
    "question": "Question:what does the refrigerator look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Cuboid, soild and white."
  },
  "2473": {
    "question": "Question:where is the refrigerator?",
    "answer": "Answer:The refrigerator is set next to two sofas and a white and brown lamp."
  },
  "2474": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the refrigerator in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The refrigerator is in a living room."
  },
  "2475": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the refrigerator?",
    "answer": "Answer:The refrigerator is near a corridor."
  },
  "2476": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bush look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:green plants,lush"
  },
  "2477": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bush?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's between 2 potting trees and it's near a exit door"
  },
  "2478": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bush in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's located in a garden with a flower bed on the second floor"
  },
  "2479": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bush?",
    "answer": "Answer:the garden is near the balcony which is near a study room"
  },
  "2480": {
    "question": "Question:what does the photo look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Papery, rectangular and small."
  },
  "2481": {
    "question": "Question:where is the photo?",
    "answer": "Answer:The photo is set below a small colorful photo, on the right side of a yellow photo and near a black fitness equipment."
  },
  "2482": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the photo in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The photo is in a bedroom."
  },
  "2483": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the photo?",
    "answer": "Answer:The photo is near a toilet."
  },
  "2484": {
    "question": "Question:what does the plant look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cylindrical, small, green"
  },
  "2485": {
    "question": "Question:where is the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the table, in the middle of two sofas"
  },
  "2486": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the plant in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The plant is set in the middle of the balcony."
  },
  "2487": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:The balcony is on the third floor, next to the dining room and outside the livingroom."
  },
  "2488": {
    "question": "Question:what does the wardrobe look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle ,installed on the wall , not very big "
  },
  "2489": {
    "question": "Question:where is the wardrobe?",
    "answer": "Answer:there is another same wardrobe opposite the target, and there are several drawers under the wardrobe "
  },
  "2490": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the wardrobe in?",
    "answer": "Answer:A median size wardrobe is embedded in the cabinet in the dressing room which is placed close to the door to outdie."
  },
  "2491": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the wardrobe?",
    "answer": "Answer:The dressing room is not very big ,and there are many cabinets in it ,which is opposite a median size mirror."
  },
  "2492": {
    "question": "Question:what does the wardrobe look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle ,installed on the wall , not very big "
  },
  "2493": {
    "question": "Question:where is the wardrobe?",
    "answer": "Answer:there is another same wardrobe opposite the target, and there are several drawers under the wardrobe "
  },
  "2494": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the wardrobe in?",
    "answer": "Answer:A median size wardrobe is embedded in the cabinet in the dressing room which is placed close to the door to outdie."
  },
  "2495": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the wardrobe?",
    "answer": "Answer:The dressing room is not very big ,and there are many cabinets in it ,which is opposite a median size mirror."
  },
  "2496": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bottle glass look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:transparent,fragile"
  },
  "2497": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bottle glass?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's on a brown table and next to 6 chairs.\n"
  },
  "2498": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bottle glass in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a dining room on the second floor."
  },
  "2499": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bottle glass?",
    "answer": "Answer:the dining room is near a living room and a balcony."
  },
  "2500": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, black, bright"
  },
  "2501": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the table and next to the stove"
  },
  "2502": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the living room"
  },
  "2503": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the staircase and the corridors and on the second floor."
  },
  "2504": {
    "question": "Question:what does the tap look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:iron, silver"
  },
  "2505": {
    "question": "Question:where is the tap?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a cupboard right under it. On its left side is a big cabinet."
  },
  "2506": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the tap in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's installed in a  open kitchen."
  },
  "2507": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the tap?",
    "answer": "Answer: Here you can see the swimming pool, reception area and a wicket."
  },
  "2508": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown, small, wooden and metallic"
  },
  "2509": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:under the big table, in front of the stairs, among four stools and first from left"
  },
  "2510": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is set in the middle of kitchen."
  },
  "2511": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is on the third, facing the stairs and next to the livingroom and balcony."
  },
  "2512": {
    "question": "Question:what does the carpet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:retangle, fluffy and white"
  },
  "2513": {
    "question": "Question:where is the carpet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on the floor in front of the basin and next to the door."
  },
  "2514": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the carpet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a restroom on the second floor."
  },
  "2515": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the carpet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The restroom is on the life side of the stairs."
  },
  "2516": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Tall,yellow,wooden."
  },
  "2517": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is placed in front of a television and on the left of a stone."
  },
  "2518": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is set in a tearoom."
  },
  "2519": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is placed near a reading room and the hall."
  },
  "2520": {
    "question": "Question:what does the tissue look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:while, soft, small"
  },
  "2521": {
    "question": "Question:where is the tissue?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of a shelf, next to a lamp"
  },
  "2522": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the tissue in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The tissue is put on the table in a bedroom."
  },
  "2523": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the tissue?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is on the first floor and connects with a study. "
  },
  "2524": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is leathery, soft and white."
  },
  "2525": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is to the right of the three sofas and to the left of the door."
  },
  "2526": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in the entertainment hall."
  },
  "2527": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is to the right of the three sofas and to the left of the door."
  },
  "2528": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:woody, white and brown, light"
  },
  "2529": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a laptop and a lamp  on the table."
  },
  "2530": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is in the bedroom."
  },
  "2531": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is next to the white chair and in front of the wall painting."
  },
  "2532": {
    "question": "Question:what does the fileplace look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:stony,square,hard"
  },
  "2533": {
    "question": "Question:where is the fileplace?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's under a big mirror and it's in front of sofas"
  },
  "2534": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the fileplace in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in the living room"
  },
  "2535": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the fileplace?",
    "answer": "Answer:living room is near the dining room and the kitchen"
  },
  "2536": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:green, fragile"
  },
  "2537": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the cabinet, next to the mirror"
  },
  "2538": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the bathroom."
  },
  "2539": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the corridor and the children's room."
  },
  "2540": {
    "question": "Question:what does the towel look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular,middle size and soft"
  },
  "2541": {
    "question": "Question:where is the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's on the towel rack and  next to a dresser"
  },
  "2542": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the towel in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in the washroom on the first floor"
  },
  "2543": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:the washroom is next to a bedroom which is near the corridor"
  },
  "2544": {
    "question": "Question:what does the desk look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown,wooden and clean."
  },
  "2545": {
    "question": "Question:where is the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:The desk is close to four chairs and glass door."
  },
  "2546": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the desk in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The desk is on the balcony."
  },
  "2547": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:The desk is near the bedroom and living room."
  },
  "2548": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A double-bed with clean white sheets and several pillows."
  },
  "2549": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the center of the bedroom and there are two nightstands beside it."
  },
  "2550": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a bedroom."
  },
  "2551": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a cabinet and a toilet."
  },
  "2552": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:woody, heavy, rectangular"
  },
  "2553": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are blue quilts on the bed, The bed is between two lamps with two woody night table."
  },
  "2554": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is in the bedroom."
  },
  "2555": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is next to the stairs and the master bedroom."
  },
  "2556": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pillow look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A small blue and yellow cloth pillow."
  },
  "2557": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on a blue sofa near a bench and beside a ring table."
  },
  "2558": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pillow in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the living room."
  },
  "2559": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a stair and a storage room."
  },
  "2560": {
    "question": "Question:what does the book look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:red,small,paper"
  },
  "2561": {
    "question": "Question:where is the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:in a red box,on the white desk,on the right side of a box full of scattered stationery"
  },
  "2562": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the book in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The book is in a large office with the number 377."
  },
  "2563": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is at the corner of a junction of three roads and on the left of the stairway door."
  },
  "2564": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle,wood and standing on the tablae"
  },
  "2565": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:under the mirror and sculpter"
  },
  "2566": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in front of the bed"
  },
  "2567": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in front of the corridor"
  },
  "2568": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is small and hung on the wall."
  },
  "2569": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is hung above the lamp next to the bed."
  },
  "2570": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is placed on the wall of the bedroom."
  },
  "2571": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a big bed and some pictures in the bedroom."
  },
  "2572": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden; with two handles;brown"
  },
  "2573": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:beside a white switch; below a wall lamp;"
  },
  "2574": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:at the corner of the corridor;opposite two shower cubicles;"
  },
  "2575": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:an empty and very long hallway."
  },
  "2576": {
    "question": "Question:what does the paintings look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Rectangular, papery and black and white."
  },
  "2577": {
    "question": "Question:where is the paintings?",
    "answer": "Answer:The paintings are set on a white wall, above a brown wooden table and near the stair."
  },
  "2578": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the paintings in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The paintings are in a dining room."
  },
  "2579": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the paintings?",
    "answer": "Answer:The paintings are near a living room."
  },
  "2580": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black,long,soft"
  },
  "2581": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to 3  chairs and a big glass."
  },
  "2582": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a dining room on the second floor."
  },
  "2583": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:the dining room is near a  living room and a balcony."
  },
  "2584": {
    "question": "Question:what does the towel look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:soft, green and oblong."
  },
  "2585": {
    "question": "Question:where is the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a curtain near the towel and it is on a wooden door."
  },
  "2586": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the towel in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is in a bathroom."
  },
  "2587": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area connects with a bedroom and near a toilet."
  },
  "2588": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A long white leather sofa with two pillows."
  },
  "2589": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:It faces a black round table and is near a black sofa."
  },
  "2590": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a living room."
  },
  "2591": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a stair to a kitchen and near a balcony."
  },
  "2592": {
    "question": "Question:what does the outlet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, rectangle, white"
  },
  "2593": {
    "question": "Question:where is the outlet?",
    "answer": "Answer:There's an exact same outlet to the right of it, On its left there is a cooker and a dish with pears"
  },
  "2594": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the outlet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's installed in a  open kitchen."
  },
  "2595": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the outlet?",
    "answer": "Answer:Here you can see the swimming pool, reception area and a wicket."
  },
  "2596": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big rectangle and brown"
  },
  "2597": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to armchair and on the right side of television"
  },
  "2598": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's at the corner of bedroom"
  },
  "2599": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathroom is on the right side of it"
  },
  "2600": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:square, middle, white and black"
  },
  "2601": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the wall, above the toilet"
  },
  "2602": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is set in the washroom."
  },
  "2603": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washroom is on the first floor and next to the livingroom."
  },
  "2604": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is plastic, white and round."
  },
  "2605": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is on the ceiling and next to the door."
  },
  "2606": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is in the utility room."
  },
  "2607": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is on the ceiling and next to the door."
  },
  "2608": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is plastic, white and round."
  },
  "2609": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is on the ceiling and next to the door."
  },
  "2610": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is in the utility room."
  },
  "2611": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is on the ceiling and next to the door."
  },
  "2612": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, rattan, black"
  },
  "2613": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:surrounded by eight rattan and black chairs, under a green bush"
  },
  "2614": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is in the balcony."
  },
  "2615": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The balcony is next to the living room and face a coutyard with a swimming pool."
  },
  "2616": {
    "question": "Question:what does the towel look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is cloth, white and rectangular."
  },
  "2617": {
    "question": "Question:where is the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel hung on the cabinet and beside the sink."
  },
  "2618": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the towel in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is in the kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "2619": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel hung on the cabinet and beside the sink."
  },
  "2620": {
    "question": "Question:what does the toilet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:middle size,ceramic,smooth"
  },
  "2621": {
    "question": "Question:where is the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a bathtub and in front of  a towel rack"
  },
  "2622": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the toilet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in the washroom on the first floor"
  },
  "2623": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:the washroom is next to a bedroom which is near the corridor"
  },
  "2624": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:metal and glass,with yellow light and the thin support"
  },
  "2625": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the right of a chair,on a small table and under some posters"
  },
  "2626": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lampis in a small single room."
  },
  "2627": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The room is next to a row of lockers,behind the food bar and near the resting area."
  },
  "2628": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cloth, striated and grey."
  },
  "2629": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is near a white tap and in front of a glass door."
  },
  "2630": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is on a large balcony."
  },
  "2631": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The balcony is next to a living room and connects with a bedroom via a flagstone."
  },
  "2632": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:round, woody and yellow"
  },
  "2633": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next the window and the circular sofa."
  },
  "2634": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a chatting room on the first floor."
  },
  "2635": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chatting room is next to the hall."
  },
  "2636": {
    "question": "Question:what does the tap look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:square, porcelain, white"
  },
  "2637": {
    "question": "Question:where is the tap?",
    "answer": "Answer:On its right is another same tap, under the mirror"
  },
  "2638": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the tap in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The tap is created in a bathroom belong to the bedroom which is face the stairs"
  },
  "2639": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the tap?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is next to the toilet. It is located in the second floor and there is a swimming pool downstairs. "
  },
  "2640": {
    "question": "Question:what does the painting look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, black and white, square"
  },
  "2641": {
    "question": "Question:where is the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer: Right under it is a bed, It hangs between two windows"
  },
  "2642": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the painting in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in a small bright bedroom."
  },
  "2643": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:It has the main bedroom on one side and the laundry on the other."
  },
  "2644": {
    "question": "Question:what does the drawer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Square and wooden drawer in a cupboard."
  },
  "2645": {
    "question": "Question:where is the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is below a black TV and beside a window."
  },
  "2646": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the drawer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is set at the back of the bedroom,close to the wall."
  },
  "2647": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is near a toilet."
  },
  "2648": {
    "question": "Question:what does the flowers look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Blooming, colorful and beautiful."
  },
  "2649": {
    "question": "Question:where is the flowers?",
    "answer": "Answer:Flowers are on the table."
  },
  "2650": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the flowers in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Flowers are in the bedroom."
  },
  "2651": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the flowers?",
    "answer": "Answer:They are very close to the bathroom and living room."
  },
  "2652": {
    "question": "Question:what does the telephone look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:middle size,black and white "
  },
  "2653": {
    "question": "Question:where is the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a phone and on a yellow table."
  },
  "2654": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the telephone in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a rest room on the second floor."
  },
  "2655": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:the rest room is next to open-balcony and a living room."
  },
  "2656": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is big, wooden and square."
  },
  "2657": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is another cabinet above and some cups inside."
  },
  "2658": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is placed against the wall next to the television in the kitchen."
  },
  "2659": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are two big tables and a wine cabinet on the opposite of the cabinet."
  },
  "2660": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is big, wooden and square."
  },
  "2661": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is another cabinet above and some cups inside."
  },
  "2662": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is placed against the wall next to the television in the kitchen."
  },
  "2663": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are two big tables and a wine cabinet on the opposite of the cabinet."
  },
  "2664": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:long; black; deck chair;"
  },
  "2665": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:oppposite a rounded bar; near a white fence;"
  },
  "2666": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:the second one from right to left;"
  },
  "2667": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:a big hall with a big glass sliding door at the entrance;"
  },
  "2668": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:covered by leather ;brown and sunk."
  },
  "2669": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:beside a wall with a decorative picture. beside an identical bed .below a wooden holder."
  },
  "2670": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:in a room with marble floors and towards a sink in the corner."
  },
  "2671": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:a room with another door leading to another place."
  },
  "2672": {
    "question": "Question:what does the wardrobe look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:large, woody, rectangular"
  },
  "2673": {
    "question": "Question:where is the wardrobe?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a locker, in the corner"
  },
  "2674": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the wardrobe in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The wardrobe is located in a small washroom."
  },
  "2675": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the wardrobe?",
    "answer": "Answer:It has a black hair dryer and there is a trashcan under the hair dryer. "
  },
  "2676": {
    "question": "Question:what does the power switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is square, white and power-off."
  },
  "2677": {
    "question": "Question:where is the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is placed next to the picture facing the bed."
  },
  "2678": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the power switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is placed next to the picture facing the bed on the wall of the bedroom."
  },
  "2679": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a big bed and pictures in the bed."
  },
  "2680": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White, metal and plastic, round"
  },
  "2681": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is on the bedside table, next to the bed"
  },
  "2682": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:lamp in the bedroom"
  },
  "2683": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:lamp at the end of the corridor on the second floor on the first floor living room"
  },
  "2684": {
    "question": "Question:what does the television look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle, steel and silver."
  },
  "2685": {
    "question": "Question:where is the television?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed on a shelf next to the refrigerator."
  },
  "2686": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the television in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "2687": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the television?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to the chatting room and the door."
  },
  "2688": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden and glass, squeare, white and black"
  },
  "2689": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the wall, next to the bookshelf, among five pictures and second from left"
  },
  "2690": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is set on the left side of the corridor."
  },
  "2691": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The corridor is on the second floor, has some rooms and two stairs."
  },
  "2692": {
    "question": "Question:what does the towels look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, rectangular"
  },
  "2693": {
    "question": "Question:where is the towels?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the wall, next to the mirror"
  },
  "2694": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the towels in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the bathroom."
  },
  "2695": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the towels?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the corridor and the children's room."
  },
  "2696": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cylinder, white, cloth"
  },
  "2697": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:on a black table, next to a book"
  },
  "2698": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is settled in the corner of a study on the first floor."
  },
  "2699": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The study is next to a bashroom and facing a long corridor."
  },
  "2700": {
    "question": "Question:what does the power switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a square, new, white power switch."
  },
  "2701": {
    "question": "Question:where is the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on a wall, opposite a cabinet."
  },
  "2702": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the power switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a study.\n"
  },
  "2703": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a very neat study with many books."
  },
  "2704": {
    "question": "Question:what does the plant look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:High, green, vitality"
  },
  "2705": {
    "question": "Question:where is the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a sofa and a TV next to the attalea speciosa"
  },
  "2706": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the plant in?",
    "answer": "Answer:attalea speciosa in the living room"
  },
  "2707": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:attalea speciosa near the balcony"
  },
  "2708": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pen look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black,strip-type and standing"
  },
  "2709": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pen?",
    "answer": "Answer:in the pen holder,under the display and on the shell"
  },
  "2710": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pen in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a big meeting room whose number is 04."
  },
  "2711": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pen?",
    "answer": "Answer:The meeting room is opposite to the room that's not allow to entry and faces the lobby at a slant."
  },
  "2712": {
    "question": "Question:what does the towel look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is small, white and cotton."
  },
  "2713": {
    "question": "Question:where is the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a mirror and sink next to the towel."
  },
  "2714": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the towel in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is placed next to the mirror and sink."
  },
  "2715": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a sink, mirror and toilet in the toilet."
  },
  "2716": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pillow look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soft,green,cotton"
  },
  "2717": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:The pillow is set on a white sofa and on the right of a green pillow."
  },
  "2718": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pillow in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The pillow is set in the hall."
  },
  "2719": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:The pillow is placed near a bedroom and a tearoom."
  },
  "2720": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black, soft and leather."
  },
  "2721": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is near a big cabinet and near a wooden box."
  },
  "2722": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in a big living room."
  },
  "2723": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is next to a dining room and leads to outdoors via a door."
  },
  "2724": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:filmy, white, concise"
  },
  "2725": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to two beds and another lamp with the same color and shape, next to the window"
  },
  "2726": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is in the bedroom."
  },
  "2727": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is next to the stairs and faces the bathroom."
  },
  "2728": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soild, cuboid and white."
  },
  "2729": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is opposite to a green painting and a brassy switch."
  },
  "2730": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is in a corridor."
  },
  "2731": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is near a toilet and a bedroom."
  },
  "2732": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is grey, steel and empty."
  },
  "2733": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a water-tap above the sink and some fruit next to the sink."
  },
  "2734": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is placed next to some fruit on the table in the kitchen."
  },
  "2735": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are many sinks and cabinets in the kitchen."
  },
  "2736": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is rectangular, black and large."
  },
  "2737": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is beside the table and swimming pool."
  },
  "2738": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is beside the outdoor swimming pool."
  },
  "2739": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is beside the table and swimming pool."
  },
  "2740": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, small, cylinder"
  },
  "2741": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of a picture, next to a plate"
  },
  "2742": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is settled in the corner of a dining room on the first floor."
  },
  "2743": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The dining room is next to a kitchen and there is a road outside."
  },
  "2744": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black, small, circle"
  },
  "2745": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:under a lamp, next to a bed"
  },
  "2746": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is settled in the corner of a bedroom."
  },
  "2747": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is on the first floor and there is a garden outside."
  },
  "2748": {
    "question": "Question:what does the towel look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is soild, white and made of cloth."
  },
  "2749": {
    "question": "Question:where is the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is near a bathtub and a table with two white sinks."
  },
  "2750": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the towel in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is in a bathroom."
  },
  "2751": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is near a bedroom."
  },
  "2752": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, cloth, gray and yellow"
  },
  "2753": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the right of a picture, facing a long table"
  },
  "2754": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is hung on the edge of a kitchen."
  },
  "2755": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to a small storeroom and facing a big dining room."
  },
  "2756": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A black bedside table with a lamp some books,and a picture."
  },
  "2757": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is beside a bed and near a window."
  },
  "2758": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a bedroom."
  },
  "2759": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a toilet and an empty room."
  },
  "2760": {
    "question": "Question:what does the exhaust fan look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:square, small, white "
  },
  "2761": {
    "question": "Question:where is the exhaust fan?",
    "answer": "Answer:beside the exhaust fan is three lighting bulbs. It's installed right above the toilet."
  },
  "2762": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the exhaust fan in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's on the ceiling of the washing room."
  },
  "2763": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the exhaust fan?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washing room is built in a small bright bedroom which has the main bedroom on one side and the laundry on the other."
  },
  "2764": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:soft,purple and with four argent chair legs"
  },
  "2765": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the right side of the table and near the door and opposite to a whiteboard"
  },
  "2766": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is in a small meeting room with the number 02."
  },
  "2767": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The meeting room is along a corridor leading to the lobby and behind a stairway door."
  },
  "2768": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a medium sized, rounded, wooden chair.\n"
  },
  "2769": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The wooden chair was pressed against the curtains, to the right of a bookshelf.\n"
  },
  "2770": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:This wooden chair is by the window of the study.\n"
  },
  "2771": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a very classic study."
  },
  "2772": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:double bed,cotton,soft"
  },
  "2773": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to 2 bedside tables with 2 lamps.it's below a picture and in front of a desk"
  },
  "2774": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a bedroom on the first floor"
  },
  "2775": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:the bedroom has a washroom and is in the end of a corridor which is near another bedroom   and rest room"
  },
  "2776": {
    "question": "Question:what does the laptop look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:metal,L-type,black,foldable,small"
  },
  "2777": {
    "question": "Question:where is the laptop?",
    "answer": "Answer:The laptop is next to the newspaper , a big screen and a green stapler,on the white table and in front of lots of snacks."
  },
  "2778": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the laptop in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The laptop is in a big office that is large enough for six people to work."
  },
  "2779": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the laptop?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is at the corner is at the corner of the three fork road and next to an empty office and opposite to the room 356."
  },
  "2780": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:square, porcelain, white"
  },
  "2781": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are two washing machines nearby, Below the sink is a cabinet"
  },
  "2782": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is installed in a small laundry."
  },
  "2783": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer: The laundry is flanked by bedrooms, and there is a chandelier in front"
  },
  "2784": {
    "question": "Question:what does the tv look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle, long, LCD"
  },
  "2785": {
    "question": "Question:where is the tv?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's facing a big sofa and two chairs and a big painting."
  },
  "2786": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the tv in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is hang on the reception area."
  },
  "2787": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the tv?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area faces the open kitchen, next to the pool, and dinning table on the other side."
  },
  "2788": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pillow look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:soft, red and quadrate."
  },
  "2789": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:The pillow is next to a gray pillow and on a long sofa."
  },
  "2790": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pillow in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The pillow is in a big living room."
  },
  "2791": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is next to a dining room and leads to outdoors via a door."
  },
  "2792": {
    "question": "Question:what does the treadmill look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:metal, gray, big"
  },
  "2793": {
    "question": "Question:where is the treadmill?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of a mirror, facing a picture"
  },
  "2794": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the treadmill in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The treadmill is in a gym on the second floor."
  },
  "2795": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the treadmill?",
    "answer": "Answer:The gym is between two bashrooms and face a corridor."
  },
  "2796": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is large, rectangular and black."
  },
  "2797": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is below the painting and close to the wall."
  },
  "2798": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in the bedroom."
  },
  "2799": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is below the painting and close to the wall."
  },
  "2800": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:movable, brown, leather chair"
  },
  "2801": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a table, under a fan "
  },
  "2802": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is settled in a study."
  },
  "2803": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The study is on the first floor and it connects with a bedroom."
  },
  "2804": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A curved columnal glass transparent vase."
  },
  "2805": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is set on a desk and close to a upholstered chair."
  },
  "2806": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is situated in the dining room."
  },
  "2807": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a kitchen and a staircase."
  },
  "2808": {
    "question": "Question:what does the light look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A shining light with a lamp post but no lampshade."
  },
  "2809": {
    "question": "Question:where is the light?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is hung on a wooden board near the sloping ceiling."
  },
  "2810": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the light in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a room which has a black sofa."
  },
  "2811": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the light?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near four entrances of bedrooms."
  },
  "2812": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:mazarine, rectangular, medium"
  },
  "2813": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:between two white tables with two lamps, next to a white wall painting"
  },
  "2814": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is in the bedroom."
  },
  "2815": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is near the stairs and the bathroom."
  },
  "2816": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:yellow, round and woody"
  },
  "2817": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to a table and closest to the lamp post.\n"
  },
  "2818": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a chatting room on the first floor."
  },
  "2819": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chatting room is next to the hall."
  },
  "2820": {
    "question": "Question:what does the decorations look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soild, small and colorful."
  },
  "2821": {
    "question": "Question:where is the decorations?",
    "answer": "Answer:The decorations are settled above a brown table, a black and gray computer and near some paintings."
  },
  "2822": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the decorations in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The decorations are in a study."
  },
  "2823": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the decorations?",
    "answer": "Answer:The decorations are near a toilet and a dining room."
  },
  "2824": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, cloth, rectangular"
  },
  "2825": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the left of a chair, next to a column"
  },
  "2826": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is placed in a corridor on the first floor with wood floor."
  },
  "2827": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The corridor is in front of a white and bright living room and behind a small dining room."
  },
  "2828": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:oblong; porcelain; white;"
  },
  "2829": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer: below a mirror and next to a metal tissue box;"
  },
  "2830": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the left wall of the washroom;"
  },
  "2831": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:the washroom is opposite the door of the changing room;"
  },
  "2832": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Wooden, cuboid and white."
  },
  "2833": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is on the right side of a white and yellow bed and next to a beige and brown lamp."
  },
  "2834": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is in a bedroom."
  },
  "2835": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is near a toilet."
  },
  "2836": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:square, hairy, white"
  },
  "2837": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the right of the small table, next to the nightstand, under the picture"
  },
  "2838": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is located is spacious and bright bedroom."
  },
  "2839": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is on the second floor, on the right of the stair and there is a balcony outside and a washroom inside."
  },
  "2840": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:long,soft,black"
  },
  "2841": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a room and 2 doors."
  },
  "2842": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a storage room on the first floor."
  },
  "2843": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:the storage room is in the end of a corridor which links a living room and a corridor."
  },
  "2844": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is square, wooden and closed."
  },
  "2845": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a sink above the cabinet and two towels next to the cabinets."
  },
  "2846": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is placed below the sink next to two towels in the kitchen."
  },
  "2847": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are many cabinets and sinks in the kitchen."
  },
  "2848": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a small, smooth, small wooden table.\n"
  },
  "2849": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is between the two cabinets."
  },
  "2850": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in the kitchen.\n"
  },
  "2851": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to a study and kitchen."
  },
  "2852": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a small, smooth, small wooden table.\n"
  },
  "2853": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is between the two cabinets."
  },
  "2854": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in the kitchen.\n"
  },
  "2855": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to a study and kitchen."
  },
  "2856": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pillow look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:soft, quadrate and colorful."
  },
  "2857": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:The pillows are on a long sofa and near a fireplace."
  },
  "2858": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pillow in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The pillows are in a living room."
  },
  "2859": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is next to a dining room and leads to outdoors via a door."
  },
  "2860": {
    "question": "Question:what does the box look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Wooden,brown,cuboid\n"
  },
  "2861": {
    "question": "Question:where is the box?",
    "answer": "Answer:The box is set near a black cabinet and against a wall."
  },
  "2862": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the box in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The box is placed in the corridor."
  },
  "2863": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the box?",
    "answer": "Answer:The box is placed near a stairs and a big conference room."
  },
  "2864": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Hanged, rectangle and black"
  },
  "2865": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is in the middle of the two lamps, above the sink."
  },
  "2866": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a restroom on the second floor."
  },
  "2867": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The restroom is on the left side of the stairs."
  },
  "2868": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soild, wooden and small."
  },
  "2869": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is opposite to the same chair, before a window and on the left side of a brown table."
  },
  "2870": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in a corridor on the second floor."
  },
  "2871": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is near a living room."
  },
  "2872": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is an old, brown, square cabinet."
  },
  "2873": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to two chairs, under a silver box."
  },
  "2874": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is by the window of the study.\n"
  },
  "2875": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a very classic study."
  },
  "2876": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small; unique; oval;"
  },
  "2877": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:opposite the corner of the table;in the middle of two similar sinks"
  },
  "2878": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:at the left corner of the room"
  },
  "2879": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:a big washroom by side of a corridor leading to a swimming pool."
  },
  "2880": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown, rectangular, leather"
  },
  "2881": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of a Frence window and TV, next to a lamp"
  },
  "2882": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in the living room."
  },
  "2883": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is next to the balcony and in front of the dining room on the second floor."
  },
  "2884": {
    "question": "Question:what does the washstand look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:ceramic ,white and smooth"
  },
  "2885": {
    "question": "Question:where is the washstand?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a toilet and below a mirror."
  },
  "2886": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the washstand in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a bathroom on the second floor."
  },
  "2887": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the washstand?",
    "answer": "Answer:the bathroom is in a small bedroom which is near a corridor."
  },
  "2888": {
    "question": "Question:what does the plant look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:conical, green and leaf-like"
  },
  "2889": {
    "question": "Question:where is the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed on a brown cabinet and next to the white telephone."
  },
  "2890": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the plant in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in living roon on the first floor."
  },
  "2891": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is the room facing the door."
  },
  "2892": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden, quaint and delicate."
  },
  "2893": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is near a desk and near a wooden door."
  },
  "2894": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in a dining room."
  },
  "2895": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to a kitchen and across form a fireplace."
  },
  "2896": {
    "question": "Question:what does the towel look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:made of cloth,white and yellow,soft"
  },
  "2897": {
    "question": "Question:where is the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's on a wardrobe and next to 2 washing machines"
  },
  "2898": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the towel in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a laundry room on the first floor"
  },
  "2899": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:the laundry room is in the washroom,which is near a corridor and a rest room"
  },
  "2900": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:short, green plants and ornamental."
  },
  "2901": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a cyan carpet on the left of the vase and water pipes on the right of it."
  },
  "2902": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is outside and there is a stone dome."
  },
  "2903": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:Here connects with a narrow room by a blue door, and here has access to the outdoors."
  },
  "2904": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A small wooden bedside table."
  },
  "2905": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on the left side of a bed and there is a lamp and a white book on it."
  },
  "2906": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a bedroom with a double door."
  },
  "2907": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a bathroom and a living room."
  },
  "2908": {
    "question": "Question:what does the ventilator look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle, silver"
  },
  "2909": {
    "question": "Question:where is the ventilator?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a long cupboard directly above it and an induction cooker directly below it"
  },
  "2910": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the ventilator in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's installed in a  open kitchen."
  },
  "2911": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the ventilator?",
    "answer": "Answer:Here you can see the swimming pool, reception area and a wicket."
  },
  "2912": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White vase and green plants have long stems and many leaves."
  },
  "2913": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase was next to the door, next to the wall."
  },
  "2914": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is at the end of the corridor."
  },
  "2915": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is at the end of the corridor, next to the bedroom door."
  },
  "2916": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden, small, square"
  },
  "2917": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the bed, next to the door"
  },
  "2918": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is settled in a bedroom against a wall. "
  },
  "2919": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is next to the corridor on the second floor with a fireplace and a bathroom. "
  },
  "2920": {
    "question": "Question:what does the drawer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is small, square and closed."
  },
  "2921": {
    "question": "Question:where is the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a stove above the drawer and a carpet below the drawer."
  },
  "2922": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the drawer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is placed between the stove and the carpet in the kitchen."
  },
  "2923": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are many cabinets and sinks in the kitchen."
  },
  "2924": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:middle, brown, wooden"
  },
  "2925": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the glass door, near the stove"
  },
  "2926": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is on the left corner of livingroom facing the balcony."
  },
  "2927": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The livingroom is on the third floor, next to the dining room and there is a balcony outside."
  },
  "2928": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soild, small and rectangular."
  },
  "2929": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is in the second row and second column of the six pictures and near a cabinet with a silver ship."
  },
  "2930": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is in a living room."
  },
  "2931": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is near a study."
  },
  "2932": {
    "question": "Question:what does the calendar look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Rectangular, hanging on the wall, paper"
  },
  "2933": {
    "question": "Question:where is the calendar?",
    "answer": "Answer:The calendar is on top of a box and near a corner, hanging on the wall."
  },
  "2934": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the calendar in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The calendar is placed in the hall."
  },
  "2935": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the calendar?",
    "answer": "Answer:The calendar is set near a corner and  the gate."
  },
  "2936": {
    "question": "Question:what does the telephone look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, blue, metal"
  },
  "2937": {
    "question": "Question:where is the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:in the cabinet, next to the wall"
  },
  "2938": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the telephone in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the study."
  },
  "2939": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to the bathroom and children's bedroom."
  },
  "2940": {
    "question": "Question:what does the tap look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Metal, silver, arc"
  },
  "2941": {
    "question": "Question:where is the tap?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a window behind the tap and a sink below"
  },
  "2942": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the tap in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Tap  in the kitchen"
  },
  "2943": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the tap?",
    "answer": "Answer:Opposite the tap is the living room"
  },
  "2944": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is white, large and rectangular."
  },
  "2945": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is at the bottom left of the sink and to the right of the oven."
  },
  "2946": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is in the kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "2947": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is at the bottom left of the sink and to the right of the oven."
  },
  "2948": {
    "question": "Question:what does the telephone look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soild, small and black and silvery."
  },
  "2949": {
    "question": "Question:where is the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:The telephone is on the right side of a black toilet and near a silvery and yellow vase."
  },
  "2950": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the telephone in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The telephone is in a toilet on the first floor."
  },
  "2951": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:The telephone is near a corridor and a kitchen."
  },
  "2952": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A white leather sofa with two yellow pillows."
  },
  "2953": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a door and a black low table,and on the left side of the table if you face the projector."
  },
  "2954": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the living room."
  },
  "2955": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near other sofas."
  },
  "2956": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle,paper,black and white,on the wall"
  },
  "2957": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the right side of the room,on the left of a whiteboard and behind a chair"
  },
  "2958": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a small meeting room with the number 02."
  },
  "2959": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:Outside the meeting room there is  a corridor leading to the lobby and a stairway door in the corridor."
  },
  "2960": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle, soft and patterned"
  },
  "2961": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is facing the white cabinet and on the carpet."
  },
  "2962": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a bedroom on the second floor."
  },
  "2963": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is at the left rear corner of the stairs."
  },
  "2964": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden,brown and with four legs"
  },
  "2965": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of a long lamb and a sofa,in front of the third desk from left to right among those desks put in line"
  },
  "2966": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is in a big restaurant ."
  },
  "2967": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is back to the corridor door and the service counter."
  },
  "2968": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden,unfolded and comfortable."
  },
  "2969": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is close to the desk and the white block."
  },
  "2970": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is on the balcony."
  },
  "2971": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set near the bedroom and living room."
  },
  "2972": {
    "question": "Question:what does the painting look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, colorful,"
  },
  "2973": {
    "question": "Question:where is the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:Right under it is a cabinet and a plant."
  },
  "2974": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the painting in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in a small bright bedroom."
  },
  "2975": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:It has the main bedroom on one side and the laundry on the other."
  },
  "2976": {
    "question": "Question:what does the plant look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:green and white, small "
  },
  "2977": {
    "question": "Question:where is the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:It was placed in the middle of a white table, which surrounded by five chairs"
  },
  "2978": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the plant in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in a second-floor balcony, which facing the main bedroom."
  },
  "2979": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:The balcony is on the second floor of the villa, directly below the garden. "
  },
  "2980": {
    "question": "Question:what does the dustbin look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Tall,vertical,metal."
  },
  "2981": {
    "question": "Question:where is the dustbin?",
    "answer": "Answer:The dustbin is set on the ground and next to a tall lamp,near a cabinet."
  },
  "2982": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the dustbin in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The dustbin is placed in a tearoom."
  },
  "2983": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the dustbin?",
    "answer": "Answer:The dustbin is placed next to the hall and near a reading room."
  },
  "2984": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cooker look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:iron, black"
  },
  "2985": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cooker?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a long cupboard and an induction cooker directly above it, and three ovens on the left"
  },
  "2986": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cooker in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's installed in a  open kitchen."
  },
  "2987": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cooker?",
    "answer": "Answer:Here you can see the swimming pool, reception area and a wicket."
  },
  "2988": {
    "question": "Question:what does the shower look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:round, metallic, silver"
  },
  "2989": {
    "question": "Question:where is the shower?",
    "answer": "Answer:inside the glass door, on the wall"
  },
  "2990": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the shower in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The shower is set in the washroom."
  },
  "2991": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the shower?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washroom is inside the office, which is on the first floor and next to the livingroom and stairs."
  },
  "2992": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big size,soft"
  },
  "2993": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a big wardrobe and small round table with a small lamp"
  },
  "2994": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a bedroom with a washroom and in front of a corridor on the first floor"
  },
  "2995": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:the bedroom is next to the corridor and the corridor is near the living room"
  },
  "2996": {
    "question": "Question:what does the toilet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:porcelain, white, firm "
  },
  "2997": {
    "question": "Question:where is the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:Next to a shower room ,face a mirror\n"
  },
  "2998": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the toilet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The toilet is created in a bathroom belong to the bedroom which is face the stairs"
  },
  "2999": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is next to the toilet. It is located in the second floor and there is a swimming pool downstairs. "
  },
  "3000": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bathrobe look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White, cloth and clean."
  },
  "3001": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bathrobe?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathrobe was close to the cupboard and door."
  },
  "3002": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bathrobe in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Bathrobes are in the cloakroom."
  },
  "3003": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bathrobe?",
    "answer": "Answer:Bathrobes are close to the bedroom and toilet."
  },
  "3004": {
    "question": "Question:what does the fan look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Four-bladed, white and metal"
  },
  "3005": {
    "question": "Question:where is the fan?",
    "answer": "Answer:It hangs on the roof and there is a roof light attached to it."
  },
  "3006": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the fan in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The fan is in a bedroom and above the bed."
  },
  "3007": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the fan?",
    "answer": "Answer:This bedroom is located at the end of the right turn on the second floor, opposite a storage room."
  },
  "3008": {
    "question": "Question:what does the box look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Brown, cuboid, wooden."
  },
  "3009": {
    "question": "Question:where is the box?",
    "answer": "Answer:The box is set on the floor, next to a white bucket, against the wall."
  },
  "3010": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the box in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The box is placed in the hall."
  },
  "3011": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the box?",
    "answer": "Answer:The box is placed near a conference room and the gate."
  },
  "3012": {
    "question": "Question:what does the Wine rack look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown,big,woolen"
  },
  "3013": {
    "question": "Question:where is the Wine rack?",
    "answer": "Answer:there are 3 same kind of wine racks next to it but this one is next to a glass door on the left."
  },
  "3014": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the Wine rack in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a liquor storeroom on the first floor."
  },
  "3015": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the Wine rack?",
    "answer": "Answer: liquor storeroom is near a corridor , a living room  and a washroom."
  },
  "3016": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:hairy, square, brown and white"
  },
  "3017": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:in the middle of two nightstands, under the fan"
  },
  "3018": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is located in a bright bedroom and on the carpet."
  },
  "3019": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is on the second floor. There is a corridor and a stair outside the door. There is a washroom inside and it's on the right side of corridor."
  },
  "3020": {
    "question": "Question:what does the closet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:high, wooden and cuboid."
  },
  "3021": {
    "question": "Question:where is the closet?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a sofa in front of the closet, and a white wall on the left of it."
  },
  "3022": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the closet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The closet is on a small attic, which is on the second floor."
  },
  "3023": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the closet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The attic is above the living room, and connects with a staircase."
  },
  "3024": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Tha lamp looks like broken line and it is metal and brassy."
  },
  "3025": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is set next to a white and brown bed, on a small white bedside table and near two skateboards."
  },
  "3026": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is in a bedroom on a second floor."
  },
  "3027": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is near a toilet."
  },
  "3028": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown,collapsible,short,triangle"
  },
  "3029": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is behind the door,at the back of the black chair,against the wall and is opposite to the cabinet."
  },
  "3030": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in a small two person office full of document and its number is 349."
  },
  "3031": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is along the corridor and opposite to a big empty office and is close to the junction of three corridor."
  },
  "3032": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:middle, wooden, black"
  },
  "3033": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:under the desk, in front of the bed"
  },
  "3034": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set in the small bedroom."
  },
  "3035": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is in the end of the corridor and on the right of the end."
  },
  "3036": {
    "question": "Question:what does the goblet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, round and yellow"
  },
  "3037": {
    "question": "Question:where is the goblet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on a cabinet and next to a lamp."
  },
  "3038": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the goblet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a chatting room on the first floor."
  },
  "3039": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the goblet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chatting room is next to the hall."
  },
  "3040": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Medium size, rectangular, film theme"
  },
  "3041": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a table in front of the picture, and there are candies on the table"
  },
  "3042": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:picture is hanging on the living room wall"
  },
  "3043": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:picture near the corridor connecting the gym"
  },
  "3044": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cloth, rectangular, gray"
  },
  "3045": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the glass door, on the right of the table, there are two pillows on it"
  },
  "3046": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is located in a sunny balcony."
  },
  "3047": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The balcony is on the third floor, next to the dining room and outside the livingroom."
  },
  "3048": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soild, medium size and red and beige."
  },
  "3049": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is the third one in a row of chairs from left to right, on the opposite side of a door."
  },
  "3050": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in a reception room on the first floor."
  },
  "3051": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is opposite to a porch."
  },
  "3052": {
    "question": "Question:what does the TV look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Not running, black and square."
  },
  "3053": {
    "question": "Question:where is the TV?",
    "answer": "Answer:The TV is in the cabinet, facing the bed."
  },
  "3054": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the TV in?",
    "answer": "Answer:TV is set in the bedroom."
  },
  "3055": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the TV?",
    "answer": "Answer:The TV is close to the toilet and living room."
  },
  "3056": {
    "question": "Question:what does the desk look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Cloth, blue and rectangular ."
  },
  "3057": {
    "question": "Question:where is the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:The desk is near to two stone statues. Two candles are on the desk."
  },
  "3058": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the desk in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The desk is set at the corner of the hall and close to the wall."
  },
  "3059": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area has a range of metal fences."
  },
  "3060": {
    "question": "Question:what does the light look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Tall,black,metal"
  },
  "3061": {
    "question": "Question:where is the light?",
    "answer": "Answer:The light is placed in the left corner of the staircase and to the left of a brown box."
  },
  "3062": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the light in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The light is set in a tearoom."
  },
  "3063": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the light?",
    "answer": "Answer:The light is set next to the hall and a reading room."
  },
  "3064": {
    "question": "Question:what does the television look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Black and white, metal and big."
  },
  "3065": {
    "question": "Question:where is the television?",
    "answer": "Answer:The television is set on the opposite side of a colorful painting and a big beige sofa."
  },
  "3066": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the television in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The television is in a living room."
  },
  "3067": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the television?",
    "answer": "Answer:The television is near a corridor."
  },
  "3068": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cylindrical, glass and transparent"
  },
  "3069": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on a cabinet and next to a ."
  },
  "3070": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "3071": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to the chatting room and the door."
  },
  "3072": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:squared; wooden; short;"
  },
  "3073": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:in the middle of two deck chairs; mear the swimming pool;"
  },
  "3074": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:the far right  one of these similar tables;"
  },
  "3075": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:an empty space in front of the table;"
  },
  "3076": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white and black, cylindrical, reaationary"
  },
  "3077": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the brown sofa, in front of the wall painting"
  },
  "3078": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is in the living room."
  },
  "3079": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is in front of the dining room and next to the stairs."
  },
  "3080": {
    "question": "Question:what does the wall look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Vertical, square and white."
  },
  "3081": {
    "question": "Question:where is the wall?",
    "answer": "Answer:The wall is beside the door, on the commode."
  },
  "3082": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the wall in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The wall is in the toilet."
  },
  "3083": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the wall?",
    "answer": "Answer:The wall is close to the bedroom and bathroom."
  },
  "3084": {
    "question": "Question:what does the plant look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:green,small,wooden"
  },
  "3085": {
    "question": "Question:where is the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:on second the shell of the cabinet,on the right side of the display"
  },
  "3086": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the plant in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The plant is in a big resting area."
  },
  "3087": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is near the balcony outside,next to a meeting office and behind the restaurant."
  },
  "3088": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cylindrical, green and white"
  },
  "3089": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the bed and another lamp with the same shape and color, face the door of the bathroom"
  },
  "3090": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is in the master bedroom."
  },
  "3091": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The master bedroom is next to the stairs with a bathroom and a cloakroom in it."
  },
  "3092": {
    "question": "Question:what does the plant look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, white and black"
  },
  "3093": {
    "question": "Question:where is the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:It was placed next to a long cabinet, Right above it is a big picture."
  },
  "3094": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the plant in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in a small bright bedroom."
  },
  "3095": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:It has the main bedroom on one side and the laundry on the other."
  },
  "3096": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is brown, wooden and closed."
  },
  "3097": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a microwave oven below the cabinet. There is a television next to the cabinet."
  },
  "3098": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is placed against the wall in the kitchen."
  },
  "3099": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are two big tables and a wine cabinet on the opposite."
  },
  "3100": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:stone, black and potted"
  },
  "3101": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed on the shelf next to the refrigerator."
  },
  "3102": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "3103": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to the chatting room and the door."
  },
  "3104": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is colorful, big and square."
  },
  "3105": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is placed on the wall facing the table."
  },
  "3106": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is placed on the wall facing the table."
  },
  "3107": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are many pictures on the wall of the living room."
  },
  "3108": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cylindrical, artistic, white"
  },
  "3109": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:on a table of glass, next to a sofa"
  },
  "3110": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is in the living room."
  },
  "3111": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is face the TV and living room is next to the balcony and kitchen."
  },
  "3112": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is big, wooden and closed."
  },
  "3113": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is another cabinet below and some lights shining on it."
  },
  "3114": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is placed high against the ceiling in the kitchen."
  },
  "3115": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are two big tables and a wine cabinet on the opposite of the cabinet."
  },
  "3116": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is big, wooden and closed."
  },
  "3117": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is another cabinet below and some lights shining on it."
  },
  "3118": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is placed high against the ceiling in the kitchen."
  },
  "3119": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are two big tables and a wine cabinet on the opposite of the cabinet."
  },
  "3120": {
    "question": "Question:what does the Microwave oven look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle,hanged,grey"
  },
  "3121": {
    "question": "Question:where is the Microwave oven?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's behind the fridge and on the right of the oven"
  },
  "3122": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the Microwave oven in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in the kitchen"
  },
  "3123": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the Microwave oven?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is on its right"
  },
  "3124": {
    "question": "Question:what does the towel look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is white, soft and rectangular."
  },
  "3125": {
    "question": "Question:where is the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is in the middle of the two pools."
  },
  "3126": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the towel in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is inside the bathroom."
  },
  "3127": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is in the middle of the two pools."
  },
  "3128": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:gray, big, rectangular"
  },
  "3129": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the glass door, on the left of the table, there are three pillows on it"
  },
  "3130": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is located in a bright balcony.\n"
  },
  "3131": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The balcony is on the third floor, outside the livingroom, next to the kitchen."
  },
  "3132": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A glass clean mirror with a wooden support."
  },
  "3133": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on a desk which has many drawers and next to a window."
  },
  "3134": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the bedroom."
  },
  "3135": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a toilet."
  },
  "3136": {
    "question": "Question:what does the books look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:paper, rectangle"
  },
  "3137": {
    "question": "Question:where is the books?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's put on a bench, It face the bed, Right above it is a picture"
  },
  "3138": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the books in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's put in a big and  bright main bedroom."
  },
  "3139": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the books?",
    "answer": "Answer:The master bedroom faces the balcony. Right below the room is the swimming pool."
  },
  "3140": {
    "question": "Question:what does the massage bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, rectangular, soft"
  },
  "3141": {
    "question": "Question:where is the massage bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:under the decorations, in the center of a bedroom "
  },
  "3142": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the massage bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The masssge bed is put in a small bedroom."
  },
  "3143": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the massage bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom has decorations on the wall and it is in fornt of another bedroom."
  },
  "3144": {
    "question": "Question:what does the display look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black,rectangle and big"
  },
  "3145": {
    "question": "Question:where is the display?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the wall,above the shell and on the right side of the clock"
  },
  "3146": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the display in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The display is in a big meeting room with the number 04."
  },
  "3147": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the display?",
    "answer": "Answer:The meeting room is opposite to the room that's not allow to entry and faces the lobby at a slant."
  },
  "3148": {
    "question": "Question:what does the plant look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:with many long leaves,green and short"
  },
  "3149": {
    "question": "Question:where is the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:on a wooden shell,on the left of a leather sofa and on the right of a blue model."
  },
  "3150": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the plant in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The plant is in a big dining area."
  },
  "3151": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:The plant is towards the gate of the corridor and faces the service desk at a slant."
  },
  "3152": {
    "question": "Question:what does the door look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:glass and wooden, rectangular, white"
  },
  "3153": {
    "question": "Question:where is the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the window, next to the stool, next to the table"
  },
  "3154": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the door in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The door is set in the bright and spacious livingroom."
  },
  "3155": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:The livingroom is on the first floor and next to the kitchen."
  },
  "3156": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabniet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A wooden cabinet with many drawers."
  },
  "3157": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabniet?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a mirror on the cabinet and a upholstered chair beside it."
  },
  "3158": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabniet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is situated near the wall in a bedroom."
  },
  "3159": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabniet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a toilet."
  },
  "3160": {
    "question": "Question:what does the plant look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Green, straight, flaky leaves."
  },
  "3161": {
    "question": "Question:where is the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:The plant is set in a pot on a yellow table with many yellow and black chairs around it."
  },
  "3162": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the plant in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The plant is set in the hall."
  },
  "3163": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:The plant  is placed next to a conference room and next to the gate."
  },
  "3164": {
    "question": "Question:what does the trashcan look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, gray, hollow"
  },
  "3165": {
    "question": "Question:where is the trashcan?",
    "answer": "Answer:under the hair dryer, against a wall "
  },
  "3166": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the trashcan in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in a man washroom."
  },
  "3167": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the trashcan?",
    "answer": "Answer:The man washroom has a door and a laundry basket."
  },
  "3168": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown ,big,woody"
  },
  "3169": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's between two paintings"
  },
  "3170": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's hanged on the wall of corridor"
  },
  "3171": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:there a bedroom ,a bath room and a room around the corridor"
  },
  "3172": {
    "question": "Question:what does the display look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black and blue, small"
  },
  "3173": {
    "question": "Question:where is the display?",
    "answer": "Answer:To the left is a jar, a glass jar and two plants."
  },
  "3174": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the display in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's put in a  open kitchen."
  },
  "3175": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the display?",
    "answer": "Answer:Here you can see the swimming pool, reception area and a wicket."
  },
  "3176": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cotton, brown and round"
  },
  "3177": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed on a carpet and closest to the chair next to the piano."
  },
  "3178": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a chatting room on the first floor."
  },
  "3179": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chatting room is next to the hall."
  },
  "3180": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Rectangular , woody, red."
  },
  "3181": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are  one chair with the same size and state on its left and three chairs with the same shape, material on its right .There are four chairs with the same shape, material opposite to it."
  },
  "3182": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set on one side of the corridor via the altar."
  },
  "3183": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area has a fan and lots of benches on each side of the corridor ."
  },
  "3184": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white and transparent, columniform, illuminability "
  },
  "3185": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the white bed, stand on the bedside table"
  },
  "3186": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the bedroom."
  },
  "3187": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a rectangular balcony, a washroom and a toilet in the bedroom."
  },
  "3188": {
    "question": "Question:what does the laundry look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Cuboid, soild and gray and black."
  },
  "3189": {
    "question": "Question:where is the laundry?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washing machine is set near a silvery sink and under the white cabinet."
  },
  "3190": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the laundry in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washing machine is in a laundry."
  },
  "3191": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the laundry?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washing machine is near a toilet and a bedroom."
  },
  "3192": {
    "question": "Question:what does the paintings look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, wall-mounted"
  },
  "3193": {
    "question": "Question:where is the paintings?",
    "answer": "Answer:hung on the wall, above the toilet"
  },
  "3194": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the paintings in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the toilet."
  },
  "3195": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the paintings?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is in a corner which is next to the dining room."
  },
  "3196": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, wooden and leather, brown"
  },
  "3197": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:under the table, among four stools and second from right"
  },
  "3198": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is set in the bright kitchen."
  },
  "3199": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is on the second floor and next to the dining room."
  },
  "3200": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Leather, medium size and white."
  },
  "3201": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is on the right side of a small white sofa and near a stove."
  },
  "3202": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in a rest room."
  },
  "3203": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is near a corridor and a bedroom on the second floor."
  },
  "3204": {
    "question": "Question:what does the phone look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, balck, electronic"
  },
  "3205": {
    "question": "Question:where is the phone?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the table, in front of a door"
  },
  "3206": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the phone in?",
    "answer": "Answer: The phone is put in a study."
  },
  "3207": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the phone?",
    "answer": "Answer:The study has a long table and the table has two penholders on it."
  },
  "3208": {
    "question": "Question:what does the towel look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cloth,medium size and white."
  },
  "3209": {
    "question": "Question:where is the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is facing the mirror and on the towel rack."
  },
  "3210": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the towel in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Towels in the toilet."
  },
  "3211": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:Towels are close to the living room and bathroom."
  },
  "3212": {
    "question": "Question:what does the closestool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, ceramic, white "
  },
  "3213": {
    "question": "Question:where is the closestool?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a door, below a hand sink"
  },
  "3214": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the closestool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The closestool is placed in the corner of a bashroom."
  },
  "3215": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the closestool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bashroom is next to a bedroom and a study on the first floor."
  },
  "3216": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a brown, brand new, square cabinet."
  },
  "3217": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is directly under a table lamp and a porcelain."
  },
  "3218": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in the bedroom."
  },
  "3219": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is beside the corridor."
  },
  "3220": {
    "question": "Question:what does the carpet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A small yellow patterned carpet."
  },
  "3221": {
    "question": "Question:where is the carpet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a black sofa and glass bricks."
  },
  "3222": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the carpet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on the wooden floor."
  },
  "3223": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the carpet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a cabinet and a stair."
  },
  "3224": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black, rectangle and hanged"
  },
  "3225": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is hanging on the wall besides the tall white cabinet."
  },
  "3226": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a restroom on the second floor."
  },
  "3227": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The restroom is on the life side of the stairs."
  },
  "3228": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black and white, stable, rectangular"
  },
  "3229": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:under the dome lights, near a carpet"
  },
  "3230": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:This bed is located in a bedroom."
  },
  "3231": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom connects with a sauna and has dome lights."
  },
  "3232": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is tall, black and rectangular."
  },
  "3233": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is under the vase and there is a switch next to it."
  },
  "3234": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is in the lounge."
  },
  "3235": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is under the vase and there is a switch next to it."
  },
  "3236": {
    "question": "Question:what does the dining-table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, white "
  },
  "3237": {
    "question": "Question:where is the dining-table?",
    "answer": "Answer:above the chair, next to another dining-table"
  },
  "3238": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the dining-table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the dining room"
  },
  "3239": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the dining-table?",
    "answer": "Answer:Th area is next to the garden and on the first floor."
  },
  "3240": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is rectangular, silver and transparent."
  },
  "3241": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is on the top of the flower and the pool."
  },
  "3242": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is in the bathroom."
  },
  "3243": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is on the top of the flower and the pool."
  },
  "3244": {
    "question": "Question:what does the poster look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The poster is square, big and black."
  },
  "3245": {
    "question": "Question:where is the poster?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is on the opposite. There are other posters besides. "
  },
  "3246": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the poster in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The poster is placed on the opposite of the power switch next to the door. "
  },
  "3247": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the poster?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are many posters in the corridor."
  },
  "3248": {
    "question": "Question:what does the poster look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The poster is square, big and black."
  },
  "3249": {
    "question": "Question:where is the poster?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is on the opposite. There are other posters besides. "
  },
  "3250": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the poster in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The poster is placed on the opposite of the power switch next to the door. "
  },
  "3251": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the poster?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are many posters in the corridor."
  },
  "3252": {
    "question": "Question:what does the paintings look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soild, rectangular and papery."
  },
  "3253": {
    "question": "Question:where is the paintings?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is next to a brassy switch and opposite to some cabinets."
  },
  "3254": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the paintings in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is in a corridor."
  },
  "3255": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the paintings?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is near a bedroom and a toilet."
  },
  "3256": {
    "question": "Question:what does the fruit look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:apple, red and green."
  },
  "3257": {
    "question": "Question:where is the fruit?",
    "answer": "Answer:The fruit is on a desk and there has some chairs around the desk."
  },
  "3258": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the fruit in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The fruit is in a dining room."
  },
  "3259": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the fruit?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to a kitchen and across from a fireplace."
  },
  "3260": {
    "question": "Question:what does the whiteboard look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:tall,metal,white,"
  },
  "3261": {
    "question": "Question:where is the whiteboard?",
    "answer": "Answer:behind a chair, next to the curtain and under the pipeline"
  },
  "3262": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the whiteboard in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is placed in a small meeting room with the number 02."
  },
  "3263": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the whiteboard?",
    "answer": "Answer:The meeting room is connected with a corridor leading to the lobby and behind a stairway door."
  },
  "3264": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White, square, cloth."
  },
  "3265": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are many pillows on the sofa, on the gray carpet."
  },
  "3266": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in the study."
  },
  "3267": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is near the balcony, near the bookcase."
  },
  "3268": {
    "question": "Question:what does the closestool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white\uff0c normal size"
  },
  "3269": {
    "question": "Question:where is the closestool?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the doors, below the mirror"
  },
  "3270": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the closestool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the bathroom"
  },
  "3271": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the closestool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is in a bedroom which is on the third floor"
  },
  "3272": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A small black upholstered chair with a backrest."
  },
  "3273": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is by a wooden cabinet and close to a stone wall."
  },
  "3274": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is set in the bedroom near a toilet and it is not far close to the corner."
  },
  "3275": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near another bedroom."
  },
  "3276": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Cylindrical, white and steel"
  },
  "3277": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed on a piano and next to some candles."
  },
  "3278": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in living roon on the first floor."
  },
  "3279": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is the room facing the door."
  },
  "3280": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Red, soild and round."
  },
  "3281": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is on a red carpet and near a brown rectangular wooden desk."
  },
  "3282": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in a reception room."
  },
  "3283": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is near a porch."
  },
  "3284": {
    "question": "Question:what does the window look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black frame,glass,square"
  },
  "3285": {
    "question": "Question:where is the window?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the wall,next to the brown shell and between the balcony and the meeting area."
  },
  "3286": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the window in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The window belongs to the meeting area."
  },
  "3287": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the window?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is near the balcony outdoors and behind the restaurant."
  },
  "3288": {
    "question": "Question:what does the door look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, white, tall"
  },
  "3289": {
    "question": "Question:where is the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the woody wall, next to the living room"
  },
  "3290": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the door in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the corner which is between the living room and the toilet."
  },
  "3291": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:The corner is between the living room and the toilet."
  },
  "3292": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:circle, wood, black"
  },
  "3293": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a white chair, below a ceiling lamp"
  },
  "3294": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is settled in a small dining room."
  },
  "3295": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The dining room is next to a stair case and is next to a big dining room."
  },
  "3296": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wood, circle, black "
  },
  "3297": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a chair, under a flowerpot"
  },
  "3298": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is in the center of a small dining room with wood floor."
  },
  "3299": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The dining room is next to another big dining room and a stair case."
  },
  "3300": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black, big, wood"
  },
  "3301": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a white chair, below a ceiling lamp "
  },
  "3302": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is settled in a small dining room on the first floor."
  },
  "3303": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The dining room is facing a big and white living room and is next to a staircase."
  },
  "3304": {
    "question": "Question:what does the washing machine look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big size,white and metal"
  },
  "3305": {
    "question": "Question:where is the washing machine?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's under another same washing machine and next to 2 wardrobes"
  },
  "3306": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the washing machine in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a laundry room on the first floor"
  },
  "3307": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the washing machine?",
    "answer": "Answer:the laundry room is in the washroom,which is near a corridor and a rest room"
  },
  "3308": {
    "question": "Question:what does the toilet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small , white , ceramic"
  },
  "3309": {
    "question": "Question:where is the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:between the window and the sink"
  },
  "3310": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the toilet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The toilet is located at a corner of the bathroom."
  },
  "3311": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathroom is inside of the bedroom."
  },
  "3312": {
    "question": "Question:what does the toilet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small , white , ceramic"
  },
  "3313": {
    "question": "Question:where is the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:between the window and the sink"
  },
  "3314": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the toilet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The toilet is located at a corner of the bathroom."
  },
  "3315": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathroom is inside of the bedroom."
  },
  "3316": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Vertical,rectangular,glass."
  },
  "3317": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is set next to a book shelf and near the stairs."
  },
  "3318": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is set in the hall."
  },
  "3319": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is placed next to a bedroom and a tearoom."
  },
  "3320": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Leather, rectangular, brown."
  },
  "3321": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a woody desk next to the chair and lots of benches in front of it."
  },
  "3322": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The desk is set near the central corridor of the hall."
  },
  "3323": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area has a woody door and lots of benches."
  },
  "3324": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A white linen chair with no armrests. "
  },
  "3325": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on the right side of a bed and beisde a window."
  },
  "3326": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a bedroom with a double door."
  },
  "3327": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is close to a bathroom and near a living room."
  },
  "3328": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The balcony is on the second floor of the villa, directly below the garden. "
  },
  "3329": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is facing the window. There is another chair in front of the chair"
  },
  "3330": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in a second-floor balcony, which facing the main bedroom."
  },
  "3331": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The balcony is on the second floor of the villa, directly below the garden. "
  },
  "3332": {
    "question": "Question:what does the painting look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black and yellow, rectangle"
  },
  "3333": {
    "question": "Question:where is the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:On it's right side is a sofa, and on it's left side is a  plant."
  },
  "3334": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the painting in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's hangs on the work room."
  },
  "3335": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:Work room face the dinning room."
  },
  "3336": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cloth, black and white, rectangular"
  },
  "3337": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:above two sofa, next to a plant"
  },
  "3338": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is settled in a small living room on the first floor."
  },
  "3339": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is facing a big and white living room and is next to a long corridor."
  },
  "3340": {
    "question": "Question:what does the box look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:empty; with a brown lining; open;"
  },
  "3341": {
    "question": "Question:where is the box?",
    "answer": "Answer:below a wall lamp and a white telephone;"
  },
  "3342": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the box in?",
    "answer": "Answer:beside a big washroom;"
  },
  "3343": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the box?",
    "answer": "Answer:The corner of the hallway has three deck chairs."
  },
  "3344": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Round, black and with five pieces of decorative pattern."
  },
  "3345": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is on the blue carpet with pink flowers and golden border, near the blue sofa and near a tiger skin rug."
  },
  "3346": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is in the bedroom."
  },
  "3347": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is near a corridor with a stair and a study."
  },
  "3348": {
    "question": "Question:what does the fireplace look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a gray, rectangular, marble fireplace.\n"
  },
  "3349": {
    "question": "Question:where is the fireplace?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are several porcelains on it, and a sofa chair on its right."
  },
  "3350": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the fireplace in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the living room.\n"
  },
  "3351": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the fireplace?",
    "answer": "Answer:This living room is very neat and white.\n"
  },
  "3352": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Porcelainous, hollow and white."
  },
  "3353": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is set on a beige table, in front of a big mirror and on the left side of a same sink."
  },
  "3354": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is in a bathroom."
  },
  "3355": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is near a bedroom."
  },
  "3356": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Plastic, black, rotatable."
  },
  "3357": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set under a yellow table surrounded by three chairs around it and a white bucket next to it."
  },
  "3358": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set in the hall."
  },
  "3359": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is placed next to the gate and near a wall."
  },
  "3360": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stairs look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, stable, stepped"
  },
  "3361": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stairs?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a bookshelf, in front of decorations"
  },
  "3362": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stairs in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stairs are in the corner of the bar."
  },
  "3363": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stairs?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bar connects with a gymnasium and has two chairs."
  },
  "3364": {
    "question": "Question:what does the flower look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A flower with green leaves in a white pot."
  },
  "3365": {
    "question": "Question:where is the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on a wooden table and under a chandelier."
  },
  "3366": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the flower in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a dining room."
  },
  "3367": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a kitchen and a stair."
  },
  "3368": {
    "question": "Question:what does the windows look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A small closed window which frame is wooden."
  },
  "3369": {
    "question": "Question:where is the windows?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is over a wooden platform and a chair and near a cupboard."
  },
  "3370": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the windows in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is embeded in the back wall of the bedroom,in the corner."
  },
  "3371": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the windows?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a toilet."
  },
  "3372": {
    "question": "Question:what does the wall look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Vertical, square and white."
  },
  "3373": {
    "question": "Question:where is the wall?",
    "answer": "Answer:The wall is beside the door."
  },
  "3374": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the wall in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Wall in the living room."
  },
  "3375": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the wall?",
    "answer": "Answer:The wall is close to the toilet and bathroom."
  },
  "3376": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White,medium and curved lamppost"
  },
  "3377": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed on one side of the bed which is closest to the door and on a table."
  },
  "3378": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table lamp is placed in a bright bedroom with grey-green walls."
  },
  "3379": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:This bedroom is located at the end of the right turn on the second floor, next to another bedroom and a storage room."
  },
  "3380": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soild, rectangular and wooden."
  },
  "3381": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is near a black box and under a ceiling lamp with yellow light."
  },
  "3382": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is in a storeroom."
  },
  "3383": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is near a corridor with a stair and a empty room."
  },
  "3384": {
    "question": "Question:what does the computer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black,square adn small."
  },
  "3385": {
    "question": "Question:where is the computer?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's next to microphone and under the cupboard"
  },
  "3386": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the computer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's at the corner of the room"
  },
  "3387": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the computer?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is the bedroom outside the room"
  },
  "3388": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle, white, porcelain"
  },
  "3389": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's right under a mirror and a tap."
  },
  "3390": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It was installed in the toilet in the workshop."
  },
  "3391": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:Work room face the dinning room."
  },
  "3392": {
    "question": "Question:what does the armchair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:with pillows on it,medium-size,brown"
  },
  "3393": {
    "question": "Question:where is the armchair?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the left side of globe and table"
  },
  "3394": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the armchair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in study"
  },
  "3395": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the armchair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's dinning room outside the study"
  },
  "3396": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:modern, grey, thin"
  },
  "3397": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:set on a woody night table and next to a woody bed,  near a blue and green wall painting"
  },
  "3398": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is in the bedroom."
  },
  "3399": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is next to the stairs and the master bedroom."
  },
  "3400": {
    "question": "Question:what does the remote control look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, white, electronic"
  },
  "3401": {
    "question": "Question:where is the remote control?",
    "answer": "Answer:between a switch and a television, near a door"
  },
  "3402": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the remote control in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The remote control is on the wall in a small living room."
  },
  "3403": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the remote control?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area has a tall shelf with some photos and there are two doors."
  },
  "3404": {
    "question": "Question:what does the door look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A narrow glass door with a metal handle."
  },
  "3405": {
    "question": "Question:where is the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is between two black trashes and is behind a cooktop."
  },
  "3406": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the door in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is embeded in the wall and there is a  fence outside the door."
  },
  "3407": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is between a kitchen and a balcony."
  },
  "3408": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bar counter look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wide, black, useful"
  },
  "3409": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bar counter?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of two elevators, next to a door"
  },
  "3410": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bar counter in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bar counter is located in a bar."
  },
  "3411": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bar counter?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bar has stairs in the corner and a small trashcan."
  },
  "3412": {
    "question": "Question:what does the closestool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:circle, ceramic, white"
  },
  "3413": {
    "question": "Question:where is the closestool?",
    "answer": "Answer:facing a window, next to a door"
  },
  "3414": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the closestool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The closestool is settled in the corner of a bathroom on the second floor."
  },
  "3415": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the closestool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathroom is in front of a gym and is behind a bedroom."
  },
  "3416": {
    "question": "Question:what does the carbinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Rectangular, big, red."
  },
  "3417": {
    "question": "Question:where is the carbinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a small desk with books near the cabinet and a glasses door close to it."
  },
  "3418": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the carbinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is set close to a corridior of the hall."
  },
  "3419": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the carbinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area has some red cabinets and brown desks."
  },
  "3420": {
    "question": "Question:what does the towel look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white and gray, rectangular, soft"
  },
  "3421": {
    "question": "Question:where is the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:hung on the wall, next to the door"
  },
  "3422": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the towel in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the bathroom."
  },
  "3423": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is in a corner which is next to the dining room."
  },
  "3424": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:static , brown , woody"
  },
  "3425": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:below a mirror , next to a toilet"
  },
  "3426": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is located at a corner of the bathroom."
  },
  "3427": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathroom is inside of the bedroom."
  },
  "3428": {
    "question": "Question:what does the washbasin look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:orbicular, small, white"
  },
  "3429": {
    "question": "Question:where is the washbasin?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washbasin is under the mirror and face the door of the bathroom."
  },
  "3430": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the washbasin in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washbasin is in the bathroom."
  },
  "3431": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the washbasin?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathroom is next to the stairs and six bedrooms on the third floor."
  },
  "3432": {
    "question": "Question:what does the book look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, rectangular, black and gray"
  },
  "3433": {
    "question": "Question:where is the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:on a black table, next to a vase"
  },
  "3434": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the book in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed in the middle of a small and bright living room. "
  },
  "3435": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the first floor, next to a washroom and connect with a dining room. "
  },
  "3436": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bookshelf look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden, small, brown"
  },
  "3437": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bookshelf?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the stairs, next to the switch"
  },
  "3438": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bookshelf in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bookshelf is located on the corridor."
  },
  "3439": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bookshelf?",
    "answer": "Answer:The corridor is on the second floor and facing the stairs."
  },
  "3440": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Woody, hanged and square"
  },
  "3441": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to the light and the mirror."
  },
  "3442": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a restroom on the second floor."
  },
  "3443": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The restroom is on the life side of the stairs."
  },
  "3444": {
    "question": "Question:what does the book look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:red and black,thick,paper"
  },
  "3445": {
    "question": "Question:where is the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the left of the baffle,in the cabinet drawer and under the display and some pens"
  },
  "3446": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the book in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a big meeting room."
  },
  "3447": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:The meeting room is opposite to a room that's not allow to entry and faces the lobby at a slant."
  },
  "3448": {
    "question": "Question:what does the massage bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, soft, rectangular"
  },
  "3449": {
    "question": "Question:where is the massage bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a bar, near a massage bed"
  },
  "3450": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the massage bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The massage bed is put in a gymnasium."
  },
  "3451": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the massage bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area has a large swimming pool and a bath."
  },
  "3452": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, black and white, cloth"
  },
  "3453": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:facing a sofa, next to a lamp"
  },
  "3454": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is in the center of a large and bright bedroom on the second floor."
  },
  "3455": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is next to a long corridor, and there is a living room downstairs."
  },
  "3456": {
    "question": "Question:what does the window look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:glass and metallic, square, transparent"
  },
  "3457": {
    "question": "Question:where is the window?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the glass door, on the left of the picture"
  },
  "3458": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the window in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The window is set in the bedroom."
  },
  "3459": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the window?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is on the second floor and on the left of the corridor when go upstairs."
  },
  "3460": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black; with marble surface; glossy;"
  },
  "3461": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:beside a hair dryer on the wall and a brown basket on the floor; below a long mirror with black rims;"
  },
  "3462": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:in the middle of two lockers;below a long mirror with black rims;"
  },
  "3463": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:in the hallway of a changing room with many lockers around it;"
  },
  "3464": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown, rectangular, small "
  },
  "3465": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:under the table, behind the sofa"
  },
  "3466": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is set in the kitchen."
  },
  "3467": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to the livingroom and next to the dining room."
  },
  "3468": {
    "question": "Question:what does the light bulb look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:transparent,globular,fragile"
  },
  "3469": {
    "question": "Question:where is the light bulb?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's above a long white table and some cups."
  },
  "3470": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the light bulb in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a kitchen on the second floor."
  },
  "3471": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the light bulb?",
    "answer": "Answer:the kitchen is near a living room and open-balcony."
  },
  "3472": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's made of stainless steel, it's reflective, it's the shape of rectangle"
  },
  "3473": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:there is a crooked tap installed above the sink, and the target is embedded in a white cabinet"
  },
  "3474": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is embedded in a white cabinet, close to a crooked tap in the small hovel."
  },
  "3475": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a washing machine placed and a lot of impurities placed in the hovel."
  },
  "3476": {
    "question": "Question:what does the case look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, fragile, cylindrical"
  },
  "3477": {
    "question": "Question:where is the case?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the cabinet, next to the rectangular painting"
  },
  "3478": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the case in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the study."
  },
  "3479": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the case?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to the bathroom and children's bedroom."
  },
  "3480": {
    "question": "Question:what does the telephone look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black,square,lots of button on it"
  },
  "3481": {
    "question": "Question:where is the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:The telephone is on a short grey desk that is under a whiteboard ,next to a socket and in front of a big grass wall."
  },
  "3482": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the telephone in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The telephone is in an office whose number is 359."
  },
  "3483": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:The telephone is facing directly the gate and the corridor and is oppoiste to an empty office."
  },
  "3484": {
    "question": "Question:what does the plant look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Tall, green and vibrant"
  },
  "3485": {
    "question": "Question:where is the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:Pot culture  in a white flower pot with a lamp above"
  },
  "3486": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the plant in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Pot culture  plants at the end of the corridor"
  },
  "3487": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:pot culture next to the pot is the bedroom, which connects the bedroom and the stairs"
  },
  "3488": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stairs look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Metal, silvery and stair-stepping."
  },
  "3489": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stairs?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stair is behind a transparent table surrounded by transparent chairs and near a brown wooden table."
  },
  "3490": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stairs in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stair is in a dining room."
  },
  "3491": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stairs?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stair is near a living room."
  },
  "3492": {
    "question": "Question:what does the thermostat look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:plastic, small, rectangle, white and blue"
  },
  "3493": {
    "question": "Question:where is the thermostat?",
    "answer": "Answer:face a sofa, right above the switch."
  },
  "3494": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the thermostat in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's installed at the first floor where face the stair."
  },
  "3495": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the thermostat?",
    "answer": "Answer:On it's right side is the dinning table, and on it's left side is a garden."
  },
  "3496": {
    "question": "Question:what does the book look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle, blue and shabby"
  },
  "3497": {
    "question": "Question:where is the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to the vase and on another white book."
  },
  "3498": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the book in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a bedroom on the second floor."
  },
  "3499": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is facing the stairs."
  },
  "3500": {
    "question": "Question:what does the massage bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, soft, rectangular"
  },
  "3501": {
    "question": "Question:where is the massage bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a massage bed, near a class cabinet"
  },
  "3502": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the massage bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The massage bed is put in a sauna."
  },
  "3503": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the massage bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area has a laundry basket and a storage cabinet."
  },
  "3504": {
    "question": "Question:what does the book look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:blue, oblong and papery."
  },
  "3505": {
    "question": "Question:where is the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:The books are on a table and near a sofa."
  },
  "3506": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the book in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The books are in a big living room."
  },
  "3507": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is next to a dining room and leads to outdoors via a door."
  },
  "3508": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White, fabric, double"
  },
  "3509": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:the sofa there are four pillows on it and a small table in front"
  },
  "3510": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:sofa In the living room"
  },
  "3511": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:sofa next to the balcony"
  },
  "3512": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is brown, small and round."
  },
  "3513": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is above the table and carpet."
  },
  "3514": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is in the living room."
  },
  "3515": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is above the table and carpet."
  },
  "3516": {
    "question": "Question:what does the painting look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Rectangular, green and blue and soild."
  },
  "3517": {
    "question": "Question:where is the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is set opposite to a green and blue painting and near a white and beige stair."
  },
  "3518": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the painting in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is in a corridor."
  },
  "3519": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is near a laundry."
  },
  "3520": {
    "question": "Question:what does the towel look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, long, gray"
  },
  "3521": {
    "question": "Question:where is the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel hangs under another blue towel. The towel hangs left to another blue towel."
  },
  "3522": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the towel in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is in a bathroom."
  },
  "3523": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel hangs in front of a shower room. Opposite to the towel is the glass washbasin with two small sinks."
  },
  "3524": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bottle look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:transparent, glass and fragile."
  },
  "3525": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bottle?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bottle is near a wooden salver and behind of a red sofa."
  },
  "3526": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bottle in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bottle is in a big living room."
  },
  "3527": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bottle?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is next to a dining room and leads to outdoors via a door."
  },
  "3528": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, glass, tall"
  },
  "3529": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:hung on the door, next to some clothes rack"
  },
  "3530": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the cloakroom."
  },
  "3531": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is located in a bedroom which has a rectangular balcony, a washroom and a toilet, and the cloakroom is next to the washroom and toilet."
  },
  "3532": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black,hard and elegant"
  },
  "3533": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's near a stony and round table and in front of many plants"
  },
  "3534": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it is located in the balcony on the second floor"
  },
  "3535": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The balcony is next to a study room and a garden "
  },
  "3536": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a paper, white, square painting."
  },
  "3537": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is inside a wooden picture frame next to a door."
  },
  "3538": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a corridor."
  },
  "3539": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is beside a staircase."
  },
  "3540": {
    "question": "Question:what does the storage cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:woody, brown, rectangular"
  },
  "3541": {
    "question": "Question:where is the storage cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a laundry basket, near a class cabinet "
  },
  "3542": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the storage cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:This storage cabinet is in a sauna."
  },
  "3543": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the storage cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are two massage beds and a carpet in the sauna."
  },
  "3544": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Wooden, white and big."
  },
  "3545": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is set near a black table under a black sculpture and a black lamp and near a white and brown bed."
  },
  "3546": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is in a bedroom."
  },
  "3547": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is near a corridor and a bathroom."
  },
  "3548": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small,yellow and with four argent legs"
  },
  "3549": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:in the first position of the left side of the desk,under the decoration on the wall"
  },
  "3550": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is in a small meeting room with the number of 03."
  },
  "3551": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The meeting room is opposite to the gate of a big meeting room and next to a room forbidden to entry."
  },
  "3552": {
    "question": "Question:what does the toilet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:oval, white and on the floor"
  },
  "3553": {
    "question": "Question:where is the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed beneath a picture and next to the basin."
  },
  "3554": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the toilet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a restroom on the second floor."
  },
  "3555": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The restroom is at the left rear corner of the stairs."
  },
  "3556": {
    "question": "Question:what does the drawer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big,wood,brown"
  },
  "3557": {
    "question": "Question:where is the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:there is a sculpter on it and a sofa on the left"
  },
  "3558": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the drawer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in front of the bed and on the right of the sofa"
  },
  "3559": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:there is a laundry across the road."
  },
  "3560": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, circle, small"
  },
  "3561": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a picture, in front of a mirror"
  },
  "3562": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is in a wide bashroom on the second floor."
  },
  "3563": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bashroom is next to a bedroom and a gym."
  },
  "3564": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cylindrical, blue and graceful "
  },
  "3565": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the blue bed and another lamp with the same color, shape and near the door of the bedroom"
  },
  "3566": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is in the bedroom."
  },
  "3567": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is next to the stairs and behind the blue wall painting."
  },
  "3568": {
    "question": "Question:what does the decoration look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:slender cylindrical shape, high"
  },
  "3569": {
    "question": "Question:where is the decoration?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's on the right of the TV, and it's next to the pool."
  },
  "3570": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the decoration in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It was placed in the hallway between the open kitchen and the pool."
  },
  "3571": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the decoration?",
    "answer": "Answer:There's a pool on one side and an open kitchen on the other."
  },
  "3572": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black,tall,metal and plastic,two handrails and five wheels"
  },
  "3573": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is back against the windowsill ,on the right side of a chair and on the left side of two chairs and faces the gate."
  },
  "3574": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in an empty room 345."
  },
  "3575": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The room is at the end of the corridor,opposite to another empty room and connects to the rest area through a road."
  },
  "3576": {
    "question": "Question:what does the flower look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is small, red and blossoming."
  },
  "3577": {
    "question": "Question:where is the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is placed on the table facing the sofa."
  },
  "3578": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the flower in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is placed on the table facing the sofa in the living room."
  },
  "3579": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a big sofa and table in the living room."
  },
  "3580": {
    "question": "Question:what does the flower look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is small, red and blossoming."
  },
  "3581": {
    "question": "Question:where is the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is placed on the table facing the sofa."
  },
  "3582": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the flower in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is placed on the table facing the sofa in the living room."
  },
  "3583": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a big sofa and table in the living room."
  },
  "3584": {
    "question": "Question:what does the display look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black,oblong,thin"
  },
  "3585": {
    "question": "Question:where is the display?",
    "answer": "Answer:over the shell,on the left of the black wall and behind a chair"
  },
  "3586": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the display in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The display is on the wall in a small meeting room signed 03. "
  },
  "3587": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the display?",
    "answer": "Answer:The room is opposite to the gate of a big showing room and on the left side of the road of the lobby."
  },
  "3588": {
    "question": "Question:what does the towel look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cylindrical, white, soft"
  },
  "3589": {
    "question": "Question:where is the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's put in a wooden cask, next to a bathtub."
  },
  "3590": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the towel in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's put in a bathroom."
  },
  "3591": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathroom is built in the main room which  faces the balcony. Right below the room is the swimming pool."
  },
  "3592": {
    "question": "Question:what does the toilet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:middle size,white,remanic"
  },
  "3593": {
    "question": "Question:where is the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a sink and a bathtub"
  },
  "3594": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the toilet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a washroom on the first floor"
  },
  "3595": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:the washroom is in the bedroom which is in the end of a coriidor that is near a another bedroom and rest room."
  },
  "3596": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Wooden, wood color, metal handle"
  },
  "3597": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a cooktop next to the cabinet, and there are knives below"
  },
  "3598": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Cabinet  in the kitchen"
  },
  "3599": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is opposite the cabinet"
  },
  "3600": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is large, rectangular and dark."
  },
  "3601": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is beside the lamp and bed."
  },
  "3602": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is in the bedroom."
  },
  "3603": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is beside the lamp and bed."
  },
  "3604": {
    "question": "Question:what does the windows look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle, latticed and transluscent"
  },
  "3605": {
    "question": "Question:where is the windows?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed above the toilet and facing the restroom door."
  },
  "3606": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the windows in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a restroom on the second floor."
  },
  "3607": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the windows?",
    "answer": "Answer:The restroom is on the life side of the stairs."
  },
  "3608": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown, woody, small"
  },
  "3609": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the bed,next to the balcony door"
  },
  "3610": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is settled in the corner of a bedroom with a balcony."
  },
  "3611": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is next to the corridor on the second floor with a fireplace and a bathroom."
  },
  "3612": {
    "question": "Question:what does the modem look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black, small, rectangular"
  },
  "3613": {
    "question": "Question:where is the modem?",
    "answer": "Answer:under the television and the DVD, next to some photos"
  },
  "3614": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the modem in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The modem is in a small living room."
  },
  "3615": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the modem?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is on the first floor and next to a study."
  },
  "3616": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Big, yellow and white frame."
  },
  "3617": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is in a big cabinet and is around by many books."
  },
  "3618": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is in a big living room."
  },
  "3619": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is next to a dining room and leads to outdoors via a door."
  },
  "3620": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cotton,sofe,double bed,white"
  },
  "3621": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to 2 bedside tables with 2 lamps on,and near 2 white chairs."
  },
  "3622": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a big bedroom on the second floor."
  },
  "3623": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:the big bedroom has 1 bathroom and a dressing room and it is near a open-balcony."
  },
  "3624": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Big, leather and beige."
  },
  "3625": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is on the left side of a brown rectangular table and two cuboid chairs."
  },
  "3626": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in a living room."
  },
  "3627": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is near a corridor."
  },
  "3628": {
    "question": "Question:what does the toilet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The toilet is white, ceramic and oval."
  },
  "3629": {
    "question": "Question:where is the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The toilet is under the towel and to the right of the pool."
  },
  "3630": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the toilet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The toilet is in the bathroom of the bedroom."
  },
  "3631": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The toilet is under the towel and to the right of the pool."
  },
  "3632": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, brown, circular"
  },
  "3633": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:above the washbasin, over against the bed"
  },
  "3634": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is settled in the corner of a bedroom. "
  },
  "3635": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is next to the corridor on the second floor with a fireplace and a bathroom. "
  },
  "3636": {
    "question": "Question:what does the yoga mat look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black, small, cloth"
  },
  "3637": {
    "question": "Question:where is the yoga mat?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a plant, next to a treadmill"
  },
  "3638": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the yoga mat in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The yogamat is in a gym facing a long corridor."
  },
  "3639": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the yoga mat?",
    "answer": "Answer:The gym is between two bashrooms on the second floor."
  },
  "3640": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is rectangular, large and black."
  },
  "3641": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is above the washing machine and opposite the window."
  },
  "3642": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is inside the laundry room."
  },
  "3643": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is above the washing machine and opposite the window."
  },
  "3644": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden, brown and oblong."
  },
  "3645": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are two books on the table and two sofas near it."
  },
  "3646": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is in a big living room."
  },
  "3647": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is next to a dining room and leads to outdoors via a door."
  },
  "3648": {
    "question": "Question:what does the light look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Round, white and attached to a fan"
  },
  "3649": {
    "question": "Question:where is the light?",
    "answer": "Answer:The light is attached to a fan hanging on the roof."
  },
  "3650": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the light in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a bedroom and above the bed."
  },
  "3651": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the light?",
    "answer": "Answer:This bedroom is located at the end of the right turn on the second floor, next to another bedroom and a storage room."
  },
  "3652": {
    "question": "Question:what does the closestool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white; ceramic; closed;"
  },
  "3653": {
    "question": "Question:where is the closestool?",
    "answer": "Answer:beside a trash bin made of stainless steel; oppposite a washing sink;"
  },
  "3654": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the closestool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the hallway, beside another similar washroom;"
  },
  "3655": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the closestool?",
    "answer": "Answer:a narrow washroom by side of the hallway;"
  },
  "3656": {
    "question": "Question:what does the fan look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Metal, tall, round."
  },
  "3657": {
    "question": "Question:where is the fan?",
    "answer": "Answer:The fan is set  near to a metal statue and next to a red bench."
  },
  "3658": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the fan in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The fan is located on a corridor via a small room."
  },
  "3659": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the fan?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area is close to the wall with some pictures ."
  },
  "3660": {
    "question": "Question:what does the light look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small , glass , light"
  },
  "3661": {
    "question": "Question:where is the light?",
    "answer": "Answer:above the mirror , facing the window"
  },
  "3662": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the light in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lights are located at a corner of the bathroom.\n"
  },
  "3663": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the light?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathroom is inside of the bedroom.\n"
  },
  "3664": {
    "question": "Question:what does the towel look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is square, white and small."
  },
  "3665": {
    "question": "Question:where is the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is hung on the cabinet below the flower."
  },
  "3666": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the towel in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is hung on the cabinet below the flower in the kitchen."
  },
  "3667": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are many cabinets and sinks in the kitchen."
  },
  "3668": {
    "question": "Question:what does the towel look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is square, white and small."
  },
  "3669": {
    "question": "Question:where is the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is hung on the cabinet below the flower."
  },
  "3670": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the towel in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is hung on the cabinet below the flower in the kitchen."
  },
  "3671": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are many cabinets and sinks in the kitchen."
  },
  "3672": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cupboard look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle, long, wooden"
  },
  "3673": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cupboard?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a tap right above it. On its left side is a big cabinet."
  },
  "3674": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cupboard in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's installed in a  open kitchen."
  },
  "3675": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cupboard?",
    "answer": "Answer:Here you can see the swimming pool, reception area and a wicket."
  },
  "3676": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Brown, medium size and and leather."
  },
  "3677": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is near a black television, opposite to a small gray sofa and near a brown wooden table."
  },
  "3678": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in a bedroom."
  },
  "3679": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is near a corridor and a storage room."
  },
  "3680": {
    "question": "Question:what does the oven look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle, closed and grey"
  },
  "3681": {
    "question": "Question:where is the oven?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is embedded in a cabinet and beneath a glass bowl."
  },
  "3682": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the oven in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "3683": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the oven?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to the chatting room and the door."
  },
  "3684": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white; rectangular;porcelain;"
  },
  "3685": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:below a mirror and next to a metal tissue box;"
  },
  "3686": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the right wall of the washroom;"
  },
  "3687": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:a small space used as a restroom. "
  },
  "3688": {
    "question": "Question:what does the desk look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle,big,brown"
  },
  "3689": {
    "question": "Question:where is the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's behind the table and the chair"
  },
  "3690": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the desk in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in study"
  },
  "3691": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's dinning room outside the study"
  },
  "3692": {
    "question": "Question:what does the plant look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Tall,flaky leaf,green."
  },
  "3693": {
    "question": "Question:where is the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:The plant is set in a basin on a black box and near a black chair."
  },
  "3694": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the plant in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The plant is placed in the hall."
  },
  "3695": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:The plant is set next to a big conference room and next to a bedroom."
  },
  "3696": {
    "question": "Question:what does the book look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:papery, small, blue and yellow"
  },
  "3697": {
    "question": "Question:where is the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the second row of the bookcase, on the right of the television"
  },
  "3698": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the book in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The book is set in the small bedroom. "
  },
  "3699": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is in the end of the corridor and on the right of the end."
  },
  "3700": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:gray, square, short"
  },
  "3701": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:in the middle of two sofas, there is a plant on it"
  },
  "3702": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is set in the middle of the balcony."
  },
  "3703": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The balcony is next to dining room, on the third floor and outside the livingroom."
  },
  "3704": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle, black, iron"
  },
  "3705": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a tap right above it. On its left side is a big cabinet. The tap is next to it."
  },
  "3706": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's installed in a  open kitchen."
  },
  "3707": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:Here you can see the swimming pool, reception area and a wicket."
  },
  "3708": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black, tall, rectangular"
  },
  "3709": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:face the black table and laptop, next to the window"
  },
  "3710": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The carbinet is in the study."
  },
  "3711": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The study is next to the dining roon and the bathroom on the second floor."
  },
  "3712": {
    "question": "Question:what does the piano look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle, brown and woody"
  },
  "3713": {
    "question": "Question:where is the piano?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in front of the storage room and some switchs."
  },
  "3714": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the piano in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a chatting room on the first floor."
  },
  "3715": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the piano?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chatting room is next to the hall."
  },
  "3716": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A round galss mirror on the brown wall.\n"
  },
  "3717": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is beside two sofas and faces a table."
  },
  "3718": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a bedroom with a balcony."
  },
  "3719": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a corridor."
  },
  "3720": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Rectangular, red, woody."
  },
  "3721": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:There  are some light bulbs upon the chairs and a red carpet under them."
  },
  "3722": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chairs are set  near the corridor via the altar."
  },
  "3723": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area has is a small room with a brown chair and a red carpet."
  },
  "3724": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:round, erret and brown"
  },
  "3725": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed on a carpet and close to another stool."
  },
  "3726": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a chatting room on the first floor."
  },
  "3727": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chatting room is next to the hall."
  },
  "3728": {
    "question": "Question:what does the photo look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:glass and wooden, square, small"
  },
  "3729": {
    "question": "Question:where is the photo?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the table, beside the vase, behind a photo"
  },
  "3730": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the photo in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The photo is set in the bright livingroom."
  },
  "3731": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the photo?",
    "answer": "Answer:The livingroom is on the first floor and next to the kitchen."
  },
  "3732": {
    "question": "Question:what does the television look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big,black,mental"
  },
  "3733": {
    "question": "Question:where is the television?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's hang on a wall and above a brown desk and in front of the bedroom door."
  },
  "3734": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the television in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a bedroom on the second floor."
  },
  "3735": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the television?",
    "answer": "Answer:the bedroom is near the corridor and a stair."
  },
  "3736": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a silver, square, new sink."
  },
  "3737": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:It was between the two cabinets."
  },
  "3738": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:This sink is in the study."
  },
  "3739": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a white long table and many white chairs in this study."
  },
  "3740": {
    "question": "Question:what does the photo look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Colorful, soild and small."
  },
  "3741": {
    "question": "Question:where is the photo?",
    "answer": "Answer:The photo is set in a bookcase, below a blue photo and near a fitness equipment."
  },
  "3742": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the photo in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The photo is in a bedroom."
  },
  "3743": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the photo?",
    "answer": "Answer:The photo is near a toilet and a corridor."
  },
  "3744": {
    "question": "Question:what does the windows look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A clean transparent window with wooden frame."
  },
  "3745": {
    "question": "Question:where is the windows?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is over a cabinet and below a TV."
  },
  "3746": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the windows in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a small bedroom and faces the entrance of it."
  },
  "3747": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the windows?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a toilet."
  },
  "3748": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a medium-sized, square, brown table."
  },
  "3749": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is under a lamp and flower."
  },
  "3750": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is in a living room.\n"
  },
  "3751": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a clean, tidy and spacious living room.\n"
  },
  "3752": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A four-leg black wooden chair."
  },
  "3753": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is beside a wardrobe and a yellow chair."
  },
  "3754": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed in the corner of the room,front of a glass wall."
  },
  "3755": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a table in the dining hall."
  },
  "3756": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is h-shaped, black and leather."
  },
  "3757": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set between two paintings, near a brown and black drawer and a lamp and opposite to a gray and black bed."
  },
  "3758": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in a bedroom."
  },
  "3759": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is near a corridor and a living room."
  },
  "3760": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big,wooden,rectangle"
  },
  "3761": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of the shell,close to the glass wall and the gate"
  },
  "3762": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is in a big meeting room."
  },
  "3763": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The meeting room is opposite to a room that's not allow to entry and faces the lobby at a slant."
  },
  "3764": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chandelier look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:circular, transparent, bright"
  },
  "3765": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chandelier?",
    "answer": "Answer:near the decorations, near a treadmill"
  },
  "3766": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chandelier in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chandelier is located in a gymnasium."
  },
  "3767": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chandelier?",
    "answer": "Answer:The gymnasium connects with a bedroom which is used to massage and two washrooms."
  },
  "3768": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, rectangular, gray and white"
  },
  "3769": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:facing a long table, next to a lamp"
  },
  "3770": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is placed in a white and big living room on the first floor."
  },
  "3771": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is next to a small living room and in front of a corridor with wood floor."
  },
  "3772": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, bright "
  },
  "3773": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the small desk, next to the bed"
  },
  "3774": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the bedroom"
  },
  "3775": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the corridor and on the second floor."
  },
  "3776": {
    "question": "Question:what does the washbasin look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:metallic, rectangular, medium"
  },
  "3777": {
    "question": "Question:where is the washbasin?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of a window with three bushs on it, face the microwave oven"
  },
  "3778": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the washbasin in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washbasin is in the kitchen."
  },
  "3779": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the washbasin?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to the living room and the dining room."
  },
  "3780": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White and brown, umbelliform and small."
  },
  "3781": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is near two beige sofa and near a big beige desk."
  },
  "3782": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is in a living room."
  },
  "3783": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is near a corridor."
  },
  "3784": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:tall, rectangular, flimy"
  },
  "3785": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the window with white curtain, face the bed"
  },
  "3786": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is in the bedroom."
  },
  "3787": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is near the stairs and the bathroom."
  },
  "3788": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is black, stick-shaped and tall."
  },
  "3789": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is beside the sofa and in the corner."
  },
  "3790": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is in the bedroom."
  },
  "3791": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is beside the sofa and in the corner."
  },
  "3792": {
    "question": "Question:what does the book look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:paper books, thick, lots of "
  },
  "3793": {
    "question": "Question:where is the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of a table, on the second layer of the shelf"
  },
  "3794": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the book in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The books are settled in a small study."
  },
  "3795": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:The study is next to a bedroom and a living room."
  },
  "3796": {
    "question": "Question:what does the closestool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, big, porcellanous"
  },
  "3797": {
    "question": "Question:where is the closestool?",
    "answer": "Answer:over against the bathtub, next to the door"
  },
  "3798": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the closestool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The closestool is settled in the corner of the toilet. "
  },
  "3799": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the closestool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The toilet is next to a warm child-bedroom on the second floor. "
  },
  "3800": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A white porcelain sink with a tap."
  },
  "3801": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in front of a big mirror and  near a bulkhead."
  },
  "3802": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the bathroom on the second floor."
  },
  "3803": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is a little farther form the entrance of the bathroom than another sink."
  },
  "3804": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is white, square and wooden."
  },
  "3805": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is under the vase and next to the chair."
  },
  "3806": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is in the lounge."
  },
  "3807": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is under the vase and next to the chair."
  },
  "3808": {
    "question": "Question:what does the hand sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:ceramic, small, white"
  },
  "3809": {
    "question": "Question:where is the hand sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of a mirror, next to a flower"
  },
  "3810": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the hand sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The hand sink is settled in the corner of a bashroom."
  },
  "3811": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the hand sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bashroom is between a bedroom and a study and there is a road outside."
  },
  "3812": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown, wooden, tall"
  },
  "3813": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the cabinet which is on the left of the furnace, next to a photo"
  },
  "3814": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is located in the bright livingroom."
  },
  "3815": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The livingroom is on the first floor and next to the kitchen."
  },
  "3816": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bin look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black, wooden."
  },
  "3817": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bin?",
    "answer": "Answer:there is a toilet on it's left, and it's right under the plant."
  },
  "3818": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bin in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's put in the toilet."
  },
  "3819": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bin?",
    "answer": "Answer:The toilet is on the first floor of the villa, on its left is the garden and on its right is the swimming pool."
  },
  "3820": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cup look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cylindrical, black, small"
  },
  "3821": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cup?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the first floor of the cup holder, on the right the cup holder, next to a dish"
  },
  "3822": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cup in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cup is set in a small kitchen."
  },
  "3823": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cup?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to the livingroom and on the first floor."
  },
  "3824": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Blue and white, cuboid and big."
  },
  "3825": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is behind a green sofa, near a beige and brown lamp and opposite to a black television."
  },
  "3826": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is in a bedroom."
  },
  "3827": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is near a corridor and a storage room."
  },
  "3828": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black, rectangular, ratten"
  },
  "3829": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:face the French door, next to the rectangular, ratten and black table and seven chairs with the same color and shape."
  },
  "3830": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in the balcony."
  },
  "3831": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The balcony is next to the living room and in front of the coutyard with a swimming pool."
  },
  "3832": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wide; with four cabinet doors; wooden;"
  },
  "3833": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:beside a switch on the right wall of this room; opposite another small cabinet below an advertising board;"
  },
  "3834": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the glass door in a store selling bath products;"
  },
  "3835": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:there are many advertising board and shelves used for displaying the bath products;"
  },
  "3836": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a small white square painting."
  },
  "3837": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to a cabinet and a stool."
  },
  "3838": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is in a living room.\n"
  },
  "3839": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a clean, tidy and spacious living room.\n"
  },
  "3840": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:square, silver, glass"
  },
  "3841": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the wall, above the washstand"
  },
  "3842": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is set in the washroom."
  },
  "3843": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washroom is inside a bedroom, which is on the second floor, on the left of the stairs and in the central of the corridor."
  },
  "3844": {
    "question": "Question:what does the furnace look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:stone, rectangular, white"
  },
  "3845": {
    "question": "Question:where is the furnace?",
    "answer": "Answer:under the television, facing the table"
  },
  "3846": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the furnace in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The furnace is located in the spacious livingroom."
  },
  "3847": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the furnace?",
    "answer": "Answer:The livingroom is on the first floor and next to the kitchen."
  },
  "3848": {
    "question": "Question:what does the washbasin look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, white, ceramic"
  },
  "3849": {
    "question": "Question:where is the washbasin?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a closestool, in front of the towels"
  },
  "3850": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the washbasin in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washbasin is in the bathroom."
  },
  "3851": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the washbasin?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathroom is next to the stairs and six bedrooms on the third floor."
  },
  "3852": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:long, glass"
  },
  "3853": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are many utensils on the table, There are many chairs near the table."
  },
  "3854": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's put on the first floor."
  },
  "3855": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:You can see the stairs next to it.  It has a garden on one side and a swimming pool on the other."
  },
  "3856": {
    "question": "Question:what does the fan look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown, triangular, metallic"
  },
  "3857": {
    "question": "Question:where is the fan?",
    "answer": "Answer:above the bed, next to a long window"
  },
  "3858": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the fan in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The fan is located at the ceiling of the bedroom."
  },
  "3859": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the fan?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is on the second floor, on the left of the corridor when go upstairs and in the end of the corridor."
  },
  "3860": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:metallic, black, square"
  },
  "3861": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the carpet, in front of the sofa, facing the balcony on the left, there are three books and a comport on it"
  },
  "3862": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is located in the bright and spacious livingroom."
  },
  "3863": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The livingroom is next to the dining room, on the third floor and there is a balcony outside."
  },
  "3864": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:narrow;covered by white quilts and a grey cushion."
  },
  "3865": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:below four spotlights;back up to a shower room and a cabinet;"
  },
  "3866": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:in the center of the rectangular room;"
  },
  "3867": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's a room equipped with a shower room."
  },
  "3868": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle, hanged and grey"
  },
  "3869": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is hanged on the wall above the towels and next to the toilet."
  },
  "3870": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a restroom on the first floor."
  },
  "3871": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The restroom is in the bedroom which is at the right turn of the gate."
  },
  "3872": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pillow look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A small yellow pillow on a white leather sofa."
  },
  "3873": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near another yellow pillow which is the closest to the door and next to a white sofa where a light yellow pillow and a dark red pillow lie on."
  },
  "3874": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pillow in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the living room near the narrow side of the low table."
  },
  "3875": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a carpet."
  },
  "3876": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Black, round, ceramic"
  },
  "3877": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:vase On the round table with a bunch of flowers inside"
  },
  "3878": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:vase In the living room"
  },
  "3879": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:vase next to the balcony"
  },
  "3880": {
    "question": "Question:what does the curtain look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:gray ,long ,made of cloth"
  },
  "3881": {
    "question": "Question:where is the curtain?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's near a bed and a television on the wall."
  },
  "3882": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the curtain in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a big bedroom on the second floor."
  },
  "3883": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the curtain?",
    "answer": "Answer:the bedroom has a bathroom,a dressing room and is next to a open-balcony.\n"
  },
  "3884": {
    "question": "Question:what does the exhaust fan look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:square, small, white "
  },
  "3885": {
    "question": "Question:where is the exhaust fan?",
    "answer": "Answer:Surrounded by three light bulbs. Beside the exhaust fan are cabinets."
  },
  "3886": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the exhaust fan in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's on the ceiling of the laundry room."
  },
  "3887": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the exhaust fan?",
    "answer": "Answer: The laundry is flanked by bedrooms, and there is a chandelier in front."
  },
  "3888": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white,slender and metal."
  },
  "3889": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is on a square table and near the curtain."
  },
  "3890": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is in a corner of the living room."
  },
  "3891": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is close to the balcony and facing the bedroom."
  },
  "3892": {
    "question": "Question:what does the power switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is square, small and white."
  },
  "3893": {
    "question": "Question:where is the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is on the edge of the wall next to the door."
  },
  "3894": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the power switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is placed on the edge of the wall next to the door."
  },
  "3895": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a big bed in the bedroom. "
  },
  "3896": {
    "question": "Question:what does the power switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is square, small and white."
  },
  "3897": {
    "question": "Question:where is the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is on the edge of the wall next to the door."
  },
  "3898": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the power switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is placed on the edge of the wall next to the door."
  },
  "3899": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a big bed in the bedroom. "
  },
  "3900": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:woody, yellow and round"
  },
  "3901": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to a table and closest to a stool."
  },
  "3902": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a chatting room on the first floor."
  },
  "3903": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chatting room is next to the hall."
  },
  "3904": {
    "question": "Question:what does the desk look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:oval,glass and brown."
  },
  "3905": {
    "question": "Question:where is the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:The desk is near the white sofa and the grey sofa."
  },
  "3906": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the desk in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The desk is set in the living room."
  },
  "3907": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:The desk is near the balcony and bedroom."
  },
  "3908": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bathtub look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white,china and metal,clean"
  },
  "3909": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bathtub?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's under the mirror and on the right of another mirror"
  },
  "3910": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bathtub in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's at the center of the room"
  },
  "3911": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bathtub?",
    "answer": "Answer:thereis a bedroom behind it"
  },
  "3912": {
    "question": "Question:what does the light look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A white candlestick-shaped lamp with metal base."
  },
  "3913": {
    "question": "Question:where is the light?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on a wooden pillar and near a hook."
  },
  "3914": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the light in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It lies at the corner of stairs on the ground floor."
  },
  "3915": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the light?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near the living room."
  },
  "3916": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cupboard look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, wooden, brown"
  },
  "3917": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cupboard?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the oven, next to the coffee maker, facing the lamp "
  },
  "3918": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cupboard in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cupboard is set in the kitchen."
  },
  "3919": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cupboard?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is on the first floor and next to the livingroom."
  },
  "3920": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a black, old, lit lamp."
  },
  "3921": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is above an exhaust vent and a row of switches."
  },
  "3922": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is in a living room.\n"
  },
  "3923": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a clean, tidy and spacious living room.\n"
  },
  "3924": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pillow look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soft,striped,rectangular"
  },
  "3925": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:The pillow is set on a red sofa and at the left of another striped pillow. "
  },
  "3926": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pillow in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The pillow is placed in a reading room."
  },
  "3927": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:The pillow is placed near a tearoom."
  },
  "3928": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:hexagon, brown and soft"
  },
  "3929": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed on a carpet next to the piano."
  },
  "3930": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a chatting room on the first floor."
  },
  "3931": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chatting room is next to the hall."
  },
  "3932": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is white, hard and rectangular."
  },
  "3933": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is on the top of the three chairs and to the left of the wall."
  },
  "3934": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is in the living room on the first floor."
  },
  "3935": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is on the top of the three chairs and to the left of the wall."
  },
  "3936": {
    "question": "Question:what does the toilet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, white."
  },
  "3937": {
    "question": "Question:where is the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:There was a roll of paper on the toilet. It's face the washroom door."
  },
  "3938": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the toilet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It was installed in the toilet in the workshop."
  },
  "3939": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:Work room face the dinning room."
  },
  "3940": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A square picture with a frame and blank space."
  },
  "3941": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is at the top of the three pictures on the wall over the yellow table."
  },
  "3942": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on the second floor and near the corridor."
  },
  "3943": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a stair and a black chair."
  },
  "3944": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:square,big,unframed"
  },
  "3945": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's over the washstand and in front of the bathtub"
  },
  "3946": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's on the side of the washroom"
  },
  "3947": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:there is a bedroom across the corridor"
  },
  "3948": {
    "question": "Question:what does the book look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:paper, brown, rectangular"
  },
  "3949": {
    "question": "Question:where is the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:on a black table, next to a vase"
  },
  "3950": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the book in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The book is settled in a bright and tiny living room on the first floor."
  },
  "3951": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is next to a washroom and connected with a dining room through a corridor."
  },
  "3952": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Metal, umbelliform and golden."
  },
  "3953": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is set on a beige drawer and near two small beige sofas."
  },
  "3954": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is in a rest room.\n"
  },
  "3955": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is near a corridor on the second floor."
  },
  "3956": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Large, brown and wooden."
  },
  "3957": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is near the bed and TV."
  },
  "3958": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Cabinet is in the bedroom."
  },
  "3959": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is close to the living room and bathroom."
  },
  "3960": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Large, brown and wooden."
  },
  "3961": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is near the bed and TV."
  },
  "3962": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Cabinet is in the bedroom."
  },
  "3963": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is close to the living room and bathroom."
  },
  "3964": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:round, small and glass"
  },
  "3965": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed on a cabinet and close to a stove.\n"
  },
  "3966": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "3967": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to the chatting room and the door."
  },
  "3968": {
    "question": "Question:what does the plant look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden,with errct leaves,green"
  },
  "3969": {
    "question": "Question:where is the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:between two long white desks,around a door of a single room and behind a big brown book shelf"
  },
  "3970": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the plant in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The plant is in a corridor."
  },
  "3971": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:The corridor links the resting area with the food bar and opposite to a row of boothes."
  },
  "3972": {
    "question": "Question:what does the oven look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The oven is big, square and power-off."
  },
  "3973": {
    "question": "Question:where is the oven?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a cabinet above the oven. There is a microwave next to the oven."
  },
  "3974": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the oven in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The oven is placed below the cabinet next to the microwave in the kitchen."
  },
  "3975": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the oven?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are two big tables and a wine cabinet on the opposite."
  },
  "3976": {
    "question": "Question:what does the telephone look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:grey;plastic;traditional;"
  },
  "3977": {
    "question": "Question:where is the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:below a wall lamp; beside a door and two white shirts."
  },
  "3978": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the telephone in?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the left wall of the room;"
  },
  "3979": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:a room within a cabinet, a sink and a big bed with leather cushions."
  },
  "3980": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bench look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bench is black, square and leather."
  },
  "3981": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bench?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bench is placed against the wall below the picture."
  },
  "3982": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bench in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bench is placed against the wall below the picture facing the door."
  },
  "3983": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bench?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathroom is on the opposite of the bench."
  },
  "3984": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, wooden, brown"
  },
  "3985": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the left of the television, facing the sofa"
  },
  "3986": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is set in the bright and spacious livingroom."
  },
  "3987": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The livingroom is next to the kitchen, next to the dining room and on the first floor."
  },
  "3988": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, wooden, brown"
  },
  "3989": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the left of the television, facing the sofa"
  },
  "3990": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is set in the bright and spacious livingroom."
  },
  "3991": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The livingroom is next to the kitchen, next to the dining room and on the first floor."
  },
  "3992": {
    "question": "Question:what does the towel look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, blue, dry."
  },
  "3993": {
    "question": "Question:where is the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel hangs on the handrail of the door. Right to a gray towel and another blue towel.  "
  },
  "3994": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the towel in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is in a bathroom."
  },
  "3995": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:Behind the towel is a shower room. Right to the towel is a corridor."
  },
  "3996": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Blue, metal and glass, square"
  },
  "3997": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is another picture on one side of the picture, and the steps are below"
  },
  "3998": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Picture on the stairs from the first floor to the second"
  },
  "3999": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:Picture connects the first floor living room and the second floor terrace"
  },
  "4000": {
    "question": "Question:what does the oven look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:silver and black, rectangular, big"
  },
  "4001": {
    "question": "Question:where is the oven?",
    "answer": "Answer:under the cabinet, on the right of the stove"
  },
  "4002": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the oven in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The oven is set in the kitchen."
  },
  "4003": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the oven?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is on the first floor and next to the livingroom."
  },
  "4004": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a white, rectangular, huge cabinet."
  },
  "4005": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is directly opposite a desk and wooden chair.\n"
  },
  "4006": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a study."
  },
  "4007": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to a kitchen and dining room."
  },
  "4008": {
    "question": "Question:what does the tree look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:potting,green ,small"
  },
  "4009": {
    "question": "Question:where is the tree?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a white pillar and a roiling."
  },
  "4010": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the tree in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's located on a balcony on the second floor."
  },
  "4011": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the tree?",
    "answer": "Answer:the balcony is near a stair ,a living room and a dining room"
  },
  "4012": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:glass, streamlined and transparent"
  },
  "4013": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are some white flowers in the vase and the vase is on the brown cabinet."
  },
  "4014": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a bedroom on the second floor."
  },
  "4015": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is facing the stairs."
  },
  "4016": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wood, small, hard"
  },
  "4017": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a small table, near stairs"
  },
  "4018": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set at a corner of the living room, on the second floor."
  },
  "4019": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is surrounded by a kitchen and two bedrooms."
  },
  "4020": {
    "question": "Question:what does the refrigerator look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle, silver and smooth"
  },
  "4021": {
    "question": "Question:where is the refrigerator?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is embedded in the wall and facing the table."
  },
  "4022": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the refrigerator in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "4023": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the refrigerator?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to the chatting room and the door."
  },
  "4024": {
    "question": "Question:what does the decorations look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:circular, golden, useful"
  },
  "4025": {
    "question": "Question:where is the decorations?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the wall, near a small bed"
  },
  "4026": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the decorations in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The decorations are hanging in a small bedroom."
  },
  "4027": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the decorations?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom has two beds and connects with a gymnasium."
  },
  "4028": {
    "question": "Question:what does the water dispenser look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, useful, heavy"
  },
  "4029": {
    "question": "Question:where is the water dispenser?",
    "answer": "Answer:near a counter, against a wall"
  },
  "4030": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the water dispenser in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The water dispenser is located in a gymnasium."
  },
  "4031": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the water dispenser?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area has a large swimming pool and a small bath."
  },
  "4032": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Small, beige and brown and umbelliform."
  },
  "4033": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is on the right side of a blue and white bed, next to a guitar and on a beige drawer."
  },
  "4034": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is in a bedroom."
  },
  "4035": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is near a corridor and a storage room."
  },
  "4036": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Square, white and brown and wooden."
  },
  "4037": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is under a vase with red roses and on the left side of a red leather chair."
  },
  "4038": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is in a bedroom."
  },
  "4039": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is on the opposite side of a corridor."
  },
  "4040": {
    "question": "Question:what does the washbasin look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, stable, white"
  },
  "4041": {
    "question": "Question:where is the washbasin?",
    "answer": "Answer:against a wall, next to a washbasin"
  },
  "4042": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the washbasin in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washbasin is located in a man washroom."
  },
  "4043": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the washbasin?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area has a trashcan and a laundry basket. "
  },
  "4044": {
    "question": "Question:what does the tv look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black, rectangular"
  },
  "4045": {
    "question": "Question:where is the tv?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the small lamp and above the stove "
  },
  "4046": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the tv in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the bedroom"
  },
  "4047": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the tv?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the  corridor and on the second floor"
  },
  "4048": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bush look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:green, alive, cuspidal"
  },
  "4049": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bush?",
    "answer": "Answer:set in blue and brown flowerpot, near the door of the bathroom, above the white table"
  },
  "4050": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bush in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bush is in the master bedroom."
  },
  "4051": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bush?",
    "answer": "Answer:The master bedroom is next to the stairs and has a bathroom and a cloakroom in it."
  },
  "4052": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:ceramic, circle, white"
  },
  "4053": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of a mirror, above a drawer"
  },
  "4054": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is settled in the corner of a bathroom on the second floor."
  },
  "4055": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathroom is next to a corridor and there is a kitchen downstairs."
  },
  "4056": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, circle, black"
  },
  "4057": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a long sofa on it's left, a book is put on it."
  },
  "4058": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's put in the reception area where next to the stairs."
  },
  "4059": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's next to the garden. "
  },
  "4060": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamps look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Porcelainous, beige and soild."
  },
  "4061": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamps?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamps are above a table with a silvery sink and opposite to a gray cabinet."
  },
  "4062": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamps in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamps are in a kitchen."
  },
  "4063": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamps?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamps are near a rest room and a corridor."
  },
  "4064": {
    "question": "Question:what does the trash bin look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black,plastic,cylindrical"
  },
  "4065": {
    "question": "Question:where is the trash bin?",
    "answer": "Answer:under the display and the shell,on the left of a pillar"
  },
  "4066": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the trash bin in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is in a small meeting room with the number 02."
  },
  "4067": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the trash bin?",
    "answer": "Answer:The meeting room is along a corridor leading to the lobby and behind a stairway door."
  },
  "4068": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A black cabinet serving as a nightstand."
  },
  "4069": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on the left side of a bed and under a picture , a book and a lamp."
  },
  "4070": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a bedroom."
  },
  "4071": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to a small window."
  },
  "4072": {
    "question": "Question:what does the telephone look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:grey;traditional;plastic shells."
  },
  "4073": {
    "question": "Question:where is the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the wall in the middle of the door and a dresser.near a brown cabinet;"
  },
  "4074": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the telephone in?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the door of this room"
  },
  "4075": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:a small room equipped with two washing sinks and a narrow bed."
  },
  "4076": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is rectangular, glass and white."
  },
  "4077": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture leaned against the wall and to the left of the sofa."
  },
  "4078": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is in the lounge."
  },
  "4079": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture leaned against the wall and to the left of the sofa."
  },
  "4080": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:transparent, big, glass"
  },
  "4081": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:in the middle of six chairs, on the carpet, under the chandelier"
  },
  "4082": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is located in the middle of the dining room."
  },
  "4083": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The dining room is on the third floor, next to a balcony and the kitchen and facing the washroom."
  },
  "4084": {
    "question": "Question:what does the recline look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, rectangular, gray"
  },
  "4085": {
    "question": "Question:where is the recline?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the right of the table, in front of the bush"
  },
  "4086": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the recline in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The recline is located in the spacious courtyard."
  },
  "4087": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the recline?",
    "answer": "Answer:The courtyard is on the first floor and outside the livingroom."
  },
  "4088": {
    "question": "Question:what does the doll look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:short, hairy, white"
  },
  "4089": {
    "question": "Question:where is the doll?",
    "answer": "Answer:under the window, next to the bed, next to the washroom's door"
  },
  "4090": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the doll in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The doll is located in the bedroom.\n"
  },
  "4091": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the doll?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is on the second floor, on the left of the stairs and in the central of the corridor."
  },
  "4092": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:middle, white and black, square "
  },
  "4093": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the wall, next to the stairs, among five pictures and third from left"
  },
  "4094": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is set on the left side of the corridor."
  },
  "4095": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The corridor is on the second floor and has two stairs and some rooms."
  },
  "4096": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, brown, small"
  },
  "4097": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:under the table, behind the sofa, among four stools and first from left"
  },
  "4098": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is set in the kitchen."
  },
  "4099": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is on the first floor and next to the dining room."
  },
  "4100": {
    "question": "Question:what does the desk look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular,wooden,long"
  },
  "4101": {
    "question": "Question:where is the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of the cooking table,under a ceiling lamp"
  },
  "4102": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the desk in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The desk is in the kitchen."
  },
  "4103": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen faces the pool directly,and there is a living room and balcony downstairs."
  },
  "4104": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soild, red and brown and wooden and leather."
  },
  "4105": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is on the right side of a black bookshelf, on the left side of a black thin table under a black full-length sculpture and below two pictures."
  },
  "4106": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in a study."
  },
  "4107": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is near a bathroom."
  },
  "4108": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown,square and with pillows on it"
  },
  "4109": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are some pillows on the bed and two  night table near the bed"
  },
  "4110": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's on the center of the room"
  },
  "4111": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a corridor outside the room"
  },
  "4112": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cap look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Brown, foldable, fibrous"
  },
  "4113": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cap?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cap is placed on some books,on a yellow table surrounded by three  chairs."
  },
  "4114": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cap in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cap is set in the hall."
  },
  "4115": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cap?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cap is placed near a wall and the gate."
  },
  "4116": {
    "question": "Question:what does the door look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Big, wooden and vitreous and brown and white."
  },
  "4117": {
    "question": "Question:where is the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:The door is near a beige and metal sink and a gray washing machine."
  },
  "4118": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the door in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The door is in a laundry."
  },
  "4119": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:The door is near a bedroom and a toilet."
  },
  "4120": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's put hard by the wall, a big one ,cloth sofa "
  },
  "4121": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:there are several different pillows put on the target, and two glass made tea table put in front of it "
  },
  "4122": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The big cloth sofa is put hard by the wall and there is a median size mirror installed on the wall, two same glass made tea table are in front of it."
  },
  "4123": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a big glass door to the balcony close to the sofa in the big living room."
  },
  "4124": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, rectangular, soft"
  },
  "4125": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the green sofa, opposite to the yellow picture"
  },
  "4126": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the bedroom."
  },
  "4127": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a rectangular balcony, a washroom and a toilet in the bedroom. "
  },
  "4128": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big,rectangle,soft"
  },
  "4129": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:below the white lamp and across from the stove "
  },
  "4130": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is settled in a spacious and bright bedroom."
  },
  "4131": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the corridor and on the second floor."
  },
  "4132": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big,rectangle,soft"
  },
  "4133": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:below the white lamp and across from the stove "
  },
  "4134": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is settled in a spacious and bright bedroom."
  },
  "4135": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the corridor and on the second floor."
  },
  "4136": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big,glass,fragile"
  },
  "4137": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's near a bedroom and a Laundry room."
  },
  "4138": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a corridor on the second floor."
  },
  "4139": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:the corridor links a bedroom ,a Laundry room and a living room."
  },
  "4140": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a yellow, square bed filled with cotton."
  },
  "4141": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:It was sandwiched between a desk lamp and a table."
  },
  "4142": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in the bedroom."
  },
  "4143": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is beside the corridor."
  },
  "4144": {
    "question": "Question:what does the toilet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:ceramic,white and smooth"
  },
  "4145": {
    "question": "Question:where is the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's near a window and a rack."
  },
  "4146": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the toilet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a washroom on the second  floor."
  },
  "4147": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:the washroom is near a bedroom and a stair."
  },
  "4148": {
    "question": "Question:what does the gas stove look like?",
    "answer": "Answer: big,square,grey"
  },
  "4149": {
    "question": "Question:where is the gas stove?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's under the cupboard and on the drawer"
  },
  "4150": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the gas stove in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in the kitchen"
  },
  "4151": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the gas stove?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is on its right side."
  },
  "4152": {
    "question": "Question:what does the book look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:paper books, thick, old"
  },
  "4153": {
    "question": "Question:where is the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a sculpture, in front of a table"
  },
  "4154": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the book in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The books are on the fourth layer of the shelf in a study."
  },
  "4155": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area has a big table and there are two laptops on the table. "
  },
  "4156": {
    "question": "Question:what does the tv look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A black LCD TV."
  },
  "4157": {
    "question": "Question:where is the tv?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is close to the corner of the bedroom but it is closer to the toilet's door frame than the corner of the bedroom."
  },
  "4158": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the tv in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is over a cabinet and a chair."
  },
  "4159": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the tv?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a toilet."
  },
  "4160": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, circle, transparent."
  },
  "4161": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is set in a glass washbasin, under a mirror, left to a screen."
  },
  "4162": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is in a bathroom."
  },
  "4163": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink faces several shower rooms."
  },
  "4164": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:tall,woody,brown and black"
  },
  "4165": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The two stools are under the white desk,next to the woody table with eight black chairs."
  },
  "4166": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stools are at the juncture of the kitchen and the living room."
  },
  "4167": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stools are next to the French door which lead to the balcony."
  },
  "4168": {
    "question": "Question:what does the box look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, rectangular, light"
  },
  "4169": {
    "question": "Question:where is the box?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a phone, in the corner of the table"
  },
  "4170": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the box in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The box is settled in a study."
  },
  "4171": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the box?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a fan in the center of the study and the study is next to a living room."
  },
  "4172": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Black,rectangular\uff0crotatable"
  },
  "4173": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is placed under a yellow table ,in front  of a screen and next to the glass of a big conference room."
  },
  "4174": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is placed in the hall."
  },
  "4175": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is placed near a tea room and a big conference room."
  },
  "4176": {
    "question": "Question:what does the door look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A yellow wooden chair with a metal handle."
  },
  "4177": {
    "question": "Question:where is the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is at the entrance of a room whose toilet is bright. "
  },
  "4178": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the door in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed near the corridoer."
  },
  "4179": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near another bedroom."
  },
  "4180": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a wooden white round table."
  },
  "4181": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:It has a porcelain on it and a few chairs under it."
  },
  "4182": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in a balcony."
  },
  "4183": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's beside a living room."
  },
  "4184": {
    "question": "Question:what does the trash can look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Metal, silver and empty."
  },
  "4185": {
    "question": "Question:where is the trash can?",
    "answer": "Answer:The trash can is under the table, beside the chair."
  },
  "4186": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the trash can in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Trash can is in the bedroom."
  },
  "4187": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the trash can?",
    "answer": "Answer:The trash can is close to the bathroom and living room."
  },
  "4188": {
    "question": "Question:what does the flower look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a fibrous, round, white flower."
  },
  "4189": {
    "question": "Question:where is the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's on a cabinet next to a bowl."
  },
  "4190": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the flower in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in a living room."
  },
  "4191": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's beside a kitchen."
  },
  "4192": {
    "question": "Question:what does the washbasin look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, hollow, white"
  },
  "4193": {
    "question": "Question:where is the washbasin?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a washbasin, against a wall"
  },
  "4194": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the washbasin in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washbasin is seated in a small washroom."
  },
  "4195": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the washbasin?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are two washbasins and a hair drayer in this area."
  },
  "4196": {
    "question": "Question:what does the guitar look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown, wooden, big"
  },
  "4197": {
    "question": "Question:where is the guitar?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the door, under the picture"
  },
  "4198": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the guitar in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The guitar is set in the small and bright bedroom."
  },
  "4199": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the guitar?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is in the end of the corridor and on the right of the end."
  },
  "4200": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:square, big, brown"
  },
  "4201": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:under the chandelier, next to fridge"
  },
  "4202": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is located in the kitchen."
  },
  "4203": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is on the first floor, next to the dining room and next to the livingroom."
  },
  "4204": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soild, big and red and golden."
  },
  "4205": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is on the right side of the same chair, on the second stage and near a row of medium size chairs."
  },
  "4206": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in a reception room on the first floor."
  },
  "4207": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is near a porch."
  },
  "4208": {
    "question": "Question:what does the clothes look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rolled up,grey,cotton cloth sweater"
  },
  "4209": {
    "question": "Question:where is the clothes?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cloth is above a white box,on the right of the cabinet and on the left of a desk."
  },
  "4210": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the clothes in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in a small two person office of number 349 full of document. "
  },
  "4211": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the clothes?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is along the corridor and opposite to a big empty office and is close to the junction of three corridor."
  },
  "4212": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, square, silver"
  },
  "4213": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the wall, above the washstand"
  },
  "4214": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is set in the washroom."
  },
  "4215": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washroom is on the third floor, next to the stairs and facing the dining room."
  },
  "4216": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:green, glass and cylindrical"
  },
  "4217": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:IT is on a cabinet close to two galss cups."
  },
  "4218": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a chatting room on the first floor."
  },
  "4219": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chatting room is next to the hall."
  },
  "4220": {
    "question": "Question:what does the wardrobe look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The wardrobe is white, big and square."
  },
  "4221": {
    "question": "Question:where is the wardrobe?",
    "answer": "Answer:The poster and the television is next to the wardrobe."
  },
  "4222": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the wardrobe in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The wardrobe is placed next to the poster and the television against the wall in the room."
  },
  "4223": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the wardrobe?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are two tables, sofa and recliner in the room."
  },
  "4224": {
    "question": "Question:what does the wardrobe look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The wardrobe is white, big and square."
  },
  "4225": {
    "question": "Question:where is the wardrobe?",
    "answer": "Answer:The poster and the television is next to the wardrobe."
  },
  "4226": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the wardrobe in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The wardrobe is placed next to the poster and the television against the wall in the room."
  },
  "4227": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the wardrobe?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are two tables, sofa and recliner in the room."
  },
  "4228": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:long, cloth, white"
  },
  "4229": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the carpet, facing the balcony, behind two tables"
  },
  "4230": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is located in the bright livingroom."
  },
  "4231": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The livingroom is on the third floor, next to the dining room and there is a balcony outside."
  },
  "4232": {
    "question": "Question:what does the massage bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, rectangular, soft"
  },
  "4233": {
    "question": "Question:where is the massage bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a same massage bed, in the corner"
  },
  "4234": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the massage bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The massage bed is put in a small bedroom."
  },
  "4235": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the massage bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area connects with a gymnasium and has some decorations."
  },
  "4236": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:metal,small"
  },
  "4237": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:at the top right of a blue pianting,on the red wall and the one nearest to the food bar counter"
  },
  "4238": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is in the food bar."
  },
  "4239": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp faces the door of the corridor at a slant and along the corridor leading to counter. "
  },
  "4240": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is large, white and tiled."
  },
  "4241": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:Some eggs and food are put on the table."
  },
  "4242": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is in the kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "4243": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:Some eggs and food are put on the table."
  },
  "4244": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden and leather, small, brown"
  },
  "4245": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:under the table, among four stools and first from right"
  },
  "4246": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is set in the bright kitchen."
  },
  "4247": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to the livingroom and on the first floor."
  },
  "4248": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a small, square, white chair."
  },
  "4249": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to a cabinet and a stool."
  },
  "4250": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the living room.\n"
  },
  "4251": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:This living room is very neat and white.\n"
  },
  "4252": {
    "question": "Question:what does the trash look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A small black plastic trash."
  },
  "4253": {
    "question": "Question:where is the trash?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on the right side of a door and is facing an oven."
  },
  "4254": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the trash in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed in a kitchen and behind a cooktop."
  },
  "4255": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the trash?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a wardrobe and the dining hall."
  },
  "4256": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, filmy, long"
  },
  "4257": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:above a washbasin and a carbinet, under the window"
  },
  "4258": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is in the bathroom."
  },
  "4259": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathroom is next to the stairs and six bedrooms on the third floor."
  },
  "4260": {
    "question": "Question:what does the glass look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:glassy, transparent, triangular"
  },
  "4261": {
    "question": "Question:where is the glass?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the furnace, next to anothe glass"
  },
  "4262": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the glass in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The glass is in the corner in a study."
  },
  "4263": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the glass?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area has a fan in the center and two pictures on the wall."
  },
  "4264": {
    "question": "Question:what does the display look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Black,big,rectangle"
  },
  "4265": {
    "question": "Question:where is the display?",
    "answer": "Answer:The display is embedded in the wall, and in front of it is a brown table surrounded by six transparent chairs."
  },
  "4266": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the display in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The display is set in a small conference room."
  },
  "4267": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the display?",
    "answer": "Answer:The display is placed near a bigger conference and next to the hall."
  },
  "4268": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chandelier look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:hanged,irregular,turned-on"
  },
  "4269": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chandelier?",
    "answer": "Answer:over the table and flowers"
  },
  "4270": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chandelier in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in the kitchen"
  },
  "4271": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chandelier?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's close to the living room"
  },
  "4272": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bathtub look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:large, white and rectangle"
  },
  "4273": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bathtub?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is facing the toilet opposite the window."
  },
  "4274": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bathtub in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a restroom on the second floor."
  },
  "4275": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bathtub?",
    "answer": "Answer:The restroom is on the life side of the stairs."
  },
  "4276": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white; rectangular; shallow;"
  },
  "4277": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:beside a switch;below a mirror with double frames."
  },
  "4278": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:at the entrance of a small room used for massage."
  },
  "4279": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:There's a small squared hall out of the room."
  },
  "4280": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular; sheeny;white;"
  },
  "4281": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:embed in a marble surface; beside a switch and a metal tissue box on the wall;"
  },
  "4282": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the far left of this table;"
  },
  "4283": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:a well-decorated room within sinks, toilets and  two shower cubicles."
  },
  "4284": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Rectangular, soild and brown."
  },
  "4285": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is set on a brown wooden carbinet, near a small red leather chair and behind a vase with some pink flowers."
  },
  "4286": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is in a bedroom."
  },
  "4287": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is near a empty room."
  },
  "4288": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a brown, moderately sized, round table.\n"
  },
  "4289": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:It was sandwiched between two chairs.\n"
  },
  "4290": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in a living room.\n"
  },
  "4291": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a clean, tidy and spacious living room.\n"
  },
  "4292": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stove look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big,cuboid,brown and woolen"
  },
  "4293": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stove?",
    "answer": "Answer:there is a bouch of flowers on it and a chair near it"
  },
  "4294": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stove in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a bedroom on the first floor"
  },
  "4295": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stove?",
    "answer": "Answer:the bedroom has a washroom and is in the end of a corridor which is near another bedroom   and rest room"
  },
  "4296": {
    "question": "Question:what does the screen look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Big,liquid crystal,displayable"
  },
  "4297": {
    "question": "Question:where is the screen?",
    "answer": "Answer:The screen is placed on a yellow table and in front of a black chair,near a white calculator."
  },
  "4298": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the screen in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The screen is placed in the hall."
  },
  "4299": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the screen?",
    "answer": "Answer:The screen is set near a big conference room and a tea room. "
  },
  "4300": {
    "question": "Question:what does the photo look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Papery, small and white and yellow."
  },
  "4301": {
    "question": "Question:where is the photo?",
    "answer": "Answer:The photo is set below a black television, on a beige cabinet and near a green sofa."
  },
  "4302": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the photo in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The photo is in a bedroom."
  },
  "4303": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the photo?",
    "answer": "Answer:The photo is near a corridor and a storage room."
  },
  "4304": {
    "question": "Question:what does the box look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, cloth, white"
  },
  "4305": {
    "question": "Question:where is the box?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the table, in front of a shelf"
  },
  "4306": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the box in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The box is put in a study."
  },
  "4307": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the box?",
    "answer": "Answer:The study connects with the outside and is next to a bedroom."
  },
  "4308": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, soft, in black and white check"
  },
  "4309": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the black lamp and the door"
  },
  "4310": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the bedroom"
  },
  "4311": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the living room and on the second floor."
  },
  "4312": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cloth, white, big"
  },
  "4313": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:facing a table, next to a chair"
  },
  "4314": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is settled in the center of a dining room on the first floor."
  },
  "4315": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The dining room is next to a kitchen and there is a road on one side."
  },
  "4316": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Porcelainous, big and white and golden."
  },
  "4317": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is near a big brown table and on the right side of a big vase."
  },
  "4318": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is in a dining room."
  },
  "4319": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is near a kitchen."
  },
  "4320": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a porcelain, rectangular, white sink.\n"
  },
  "4321": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is directly above a cupboard, opposite a window."
  },
  "4322": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in the kitchen.\n"
  },
  "4323": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to the study."
  },
  "4324": {
    "question": "Question:what does the books look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, colorful "
  },
  "4325": {
    "question": "Question:where is the books?",
    "answer": "Answer:in the cabinet, next to the wall"
  },
  "4326": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the books in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the study."
  },
  "4327": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the books?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to the bathroom and children's bedroom."
  },
  "4328": {
    "question": "Question:what does the book look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:papery, yellow, square"
  },
  "4329": {
    "question": "Question:where is the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the table, next to the vase"
  },
  "4330": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the book in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The book is set in the spacious livingroom."
  },
  "4331": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:The livingroom is on the first floor and next to the kitchen."
  },
  "4332": {
    "question": "Question:what does the towel look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Cloth, soild and white."
  },
  "4333": {
    "question": "Question:where is the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is set near a shutter and in front of two white sinks."
  },
  "4334": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the towel in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is in a bathroom."
  },
  "4335": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is near a bedroom."
  },
  "4336": {
    "question": "Question:what does the curtain look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, yellow and white, soft"
  },
  "4337": {
    "question": "Question:where is the curtain?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the toilet and the cabinet"
  },
  "4338": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the curtain in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the bathroom."
  },
  "4339": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the curtain?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the corridor and the children's room."
  },
  "4340": {
    "question": "Question:what does the jar look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Yellow,plastic,big."
  },
  "4341": {
    "question": "Question:where is the jar?",
    "answer": "Answer:The jar is set on a yellow table ,in front of a sofa."
  },
  "4342": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the jar in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The jar is placed in the hall."
  },
  "4343": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the jar?",
    "answer": "Answer:The jar is placed near a bedroom and a tearoom."
  },
  "4344": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Color, oil painting, square"
  },
  "4345": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a bed under the picture and two table lamps"
  },
  "4346": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:picture in the bedroom"
  },
  "4347": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:picture next to the living room, opposite the yard"
  },
  "4348": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a large, transparent ceiling light with lights on."
  },
  "4349": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:It has a roof above it and a floor-to-ceiling window next to it."
  },
  "4350": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in a corridor."
  },
  "4351": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a spacious, green corridor."
  },
  "4352": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is irony, white and standing."
  },
  "4353": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is placed below the table and the vase."
  },
  "4354": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is placed below the table and the vase in the kitchen."
  },
  "4355": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are many cabinets and sinks in the kitchen."
  },
  "4356": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle, silver, "
  },
  "4357": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's right above the sink, plant and the toilet,"
  },
  "4358": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's installed in the toilet."
  },
  "4359": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The toilet is on the first floor of the villa, on its left is the garden and on its right is the swimming pool."
  },
  "4360": {
    "question": "Question:what does the washing machine look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big,metal"
  },
  "4361": {
    "question": "Question:where is the washing machine?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a washstand and a white table."
  },
  "4362": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the washing machine in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a laundry room on the second floor."
  },
  "4363": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the washing machine?",
    "answer": "Answer:the laundry room is near a corridor and a bedroom/"
  },
  "4364": {
    "question": "Question:what does the photo look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black and white, wooden and glass, square"
  },
  "4365": {
    "question": "Question:where is the photo?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the wall, next to the door, among two photos and on the right of them"
  },
  "4366": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the photo in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The photo is set in the bright bedroom."
  },
  "4367": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the photo?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is on the second floor and on the left of the corridor when go upstairs."
  },
  "4368": {
    "question": "Question:what does the closestool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:circle, big, white"
  },
  "4369": {
    "question": "Question:where is the closestool?",
    "answer": "Answer:facing a door, below a window"
  },
  "4370": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the closestool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The closestool is in the corner of a large bathroom."
  },
  "4371": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the closestool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathroom is next to a storeroom on the second floor and has a tiny balcony."
  },
  "4372": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, soft, white and green"
  },
  "4373": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the white lamp, across from the mirror "
  },
  "4374": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the children's bedroom."
  },
  "4375": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the study and the bathroom."
  },
  "4376": {
    "question": "Question:what does the drawer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:metal and wood, rectangular, big"
  },
  "4377": {
    "question": "Question:where is the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:under a washbasin, facing a gas stove"
  },
  "4378": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the drawer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is in the center of a kitchen with wood floor."
  },
  "4379": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to a tiny storeroom and is next to a dining room on the first floor."
  },
  "4380": {
    "question": "Question:what does the salver look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, woody, rectangular"
  },
  "4381": {
    "question": "Question:where is the salver?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the sofa, in front of a television, under a lamp "
  },
  "4382": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the salver in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The salver is settled in the center of the living room."
  },
  "4383": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the salver?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a big sofa on a carpet and a small lamp in the corner in the living room."
  },
  "4384": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is black, rectangular and iron."
  },
  "4385": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is beside the vase and the window."
  },
  "4386": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is in the kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "4387": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is beside the vase and the window."
  },
  "4388": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:short, black, rectangular"
  },
  "4389": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:under the picture, next to a small table, next to the washroom's door"
  },
  "4390": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set in the corner of the spacious office."
  },
  "4391": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is on the first floor and next to the livingroom and stairs."
  },
  "4392": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Black, leather, rectangular"
  },
  "4393": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a remote on the table, in front of the sofa"
  },
  "4394": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Table in living room"
  },
  "4395": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:Table near the balcony"
  },
  "4396": {
    "question": "Question:what does the photo look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, wooden and glass, square"
  },
  "4397": {
    "question": "Question:where is the photo?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the wall, next to the door, among two photos and on the left of them"
  },
  "4398": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the photo in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The photo is set in the bedroom."
  },
  "4399": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the photo?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is on the second floor and on the left of the corridor when go upstairs."
  },
  "4400": {
    "question": "Question:what does the screen look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Black, rectangular and small."
  },
  "4401": {
    "question": "Question:where is the screen?",
    "answer": "Answer:The screen is set on the right side of a black screen and near a black fitness equipment."
  },
  "4402": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the screen in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The screen is in a bedroom."
  },
  "4403": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the screen?",
    "answer": "Answer:The screen is near a corridor."
  },
  "4404": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stairs look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white,stony and hard"
  },
  "4405": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stairs?",
    "answer": "Answer:they are near a black table and a vase."
  },
  "4406": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stairs in?",
    "answer": "Answer:they are next to a corridor."
  },
  "4407": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stairs?",
    "answer": "Answer:the corridor is on the first floor and near a living room."
  },
  "4408": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:square, silver, glass"
  },
  "4409": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the wall, above the washstand"
  },
  "4410": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is set in the washroom. "
  },
  "4411": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washroom is inside the office, which is on the first floor and next to the livingroom."
  },
  "4412": {
    "question": "Question:what does the painting look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:yellow ,red ,green,bright"
  },
  "4413": {
    "question": "Question:where is the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a big window and a woolen door."
  },
  "4414": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the painting in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's hang on a wall in a corridor on the first floor."
  },
  "4415": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:the corridor is near  a living room , a stair and a storage room."
  },
  "4416": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A white leather sofa with a red and a white pillow on it."
  },
  "4417": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on the right of a wooden short desk if you face the projector."
  },
  "4418": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the living room."
  },
  "4419": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near other sofas."
  },
  "4420": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A white cabinet with several drawers in a kitchen and there are some bottles on it"
  },
  "4421": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is under a cabinet and next to a gas stove"
  },
  "4422": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a kitchen."
  },
  "4423": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a living room and a dining room."
  },
  "4424": {
    "question": "Question:what does the book look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:square, papery, blue"
  },
  "4425": {
    "question": "Question:where is the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the first row of the bookcase, next to the door"
  },
  "4426": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the book in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The book is set in the small and bright bedroom."
  },
  "4427": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is in the end of the corridor and on the right of the end."
  },
  "4428": {
    "question": "Question:what does the flower look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is blossoming, big and colorful."
  },
  "4429": {
    "question": "Question:where is the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is placed on the table next to the sink."
  },
  "4430": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the flower in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is placed on the table next to the sink in the kitchen."
  },
  "4431": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a big table on the opposite and some cabinets around."
  },
  "4432": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is big, square and irony."
  },
  "4433": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is on the table. The chairs are under the table."
  },
  "4434": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is placed on the opposite of the stove."
  },
  "4435": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a cabinet, shelf and stove in the living room."
  },
  "4436": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is big, square and irony."
  },
  "4437": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is on the table. The chairs are under the table."
  },
  "4438": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is placed on the opposite of the stove."
  },
  "4439": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a cabinet, shelf and stove in the living room."
  },
  "4440": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is big, square and irony."
  },
  "4441": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is on the table. The chairs are under the table."
  },
  "4442": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is placed on the opposite of the stove."
  },
  "4443": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a cabinet, shelf and stove in the living room."
  },
  "4444": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is big, square and irony."
  },
  "4445": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is on the table. The chairs are under the table."
  },
  "4446": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is placed on the opposite of the stove."
  },
  "4447": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a cabinet, shelf and stove in the living room."
  },
  "4448": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rounded; porcelain; with yellow patterns and many small holes."
  },
  "4449": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:embeded in a wooden table; faced with a small wooden door inside a room."
  },
  "4450": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:set in a dull corner of the room."
  },
  "4451": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:A room with two identical bed and a small door in the shadows."
  },
  "4452": {
    "question": "Question:what does the computer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soild, cuboid and black and gray."
  },
  "4453": {
    "question": "Question:where is the computer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The computer is set on a brown and white table and near a tall brown cabinet."
  },
  "4454": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the computer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The computer is in a study."
  },
  "4455": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the computer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The computer is near a toilet and a dining room."
  },
  "4456": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black;tall; with a backrest"
  },
  "4457": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:below a TV hung on the ceiling; beside a huge pilar;"
  },
  "4458": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:back up to a row of deck chairs;"
  },
  "4459": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:a big hall within a swimming pool"
  },
  "4460": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bathing room look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:large, white and empty.\n"
  },
  "4461": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bathing room?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathing room is near the commode and bathtub."
  },
  "4462": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bathing room in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathing room is in the lavatory."
  },
  "4463": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bathing room?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathing room is close to the toilet and bedroom."
  },
  "4464": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:ceramic, rectangular, white"
  },
  "4465": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:under the mirror, next to the toilet"
  },
  "4466": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is set in the washroom."
  },
  "4467": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washroom is inside the office, which is on the first floor and next to the livingroom."
  },
  "4468": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:oval;white; unique."
  },
  "4469": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:faces the flank of a table;in the middle of two sinks at the corner of the room."
  },
  "4470": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the right and at the short side of this room"
  },
  "4471": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:a big room specially used for washing"
  },
  "4472": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:long,yellow and fragile"
  },
  "4473": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in front of a stair and the roiling."
  },
  "4474": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a corridor on the second floor."
  },
  "4475": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:the corridor is near a living room and a washroom."
  },
  "4476": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bread look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:made by wheat,strip-shaped,yellow"
  },
  "4477": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bread?",
    "answer": "Answer:in a glass box,on the bar counter and between some snacks."
  },
  "4478": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bread in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bread is in the food bar."
  },
  "4479": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bread?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bar is in front of the vast resting area and towards the service desk."
  },
  "4480": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:ceramic, brown, elliptical"
  },
  "4481": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:on a black table, next to a black book"
  },
  "4482": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is settled in a small and bright living room."
  },
  "4483": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living is next to a washroom and there is a bedroom upstairs."
  },
  "4484": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:ceramic, brown, elliptical"
  },
  "4485": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:on a black table, next to a black book"
  },
  "4486": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is settled in a small and bright living room."
  },
  "4487": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living is next to a washroom and there is a bedroom upstairs."
  },
  "4488": {
    "question": "Question:what does the window look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:glass, transparent"
  },
  "4489": {
    "question": "Question:where is the window?",
    "answer": "Answer:Right above the bathtub, face the shower head."
  },
  "4490": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the window in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's installed in a bathroom."
  },
  "4491": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the window?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathroom is built in the main room which  faces the balcony. Right below the room is the swimming pool."
  },
  "4492": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cylindrical, artistic, white"
  },
  "4493": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to two sofas, in front of a mirror"
  },
  "4494": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is in the living room."
  },
  "4495": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is next to the French window and face to the door."
  },
  "4496": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:short; wooden; without handles."
  },
  "4497": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:in the middle of two different baskets; near three deck chairs."
  },
  "4498": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:at the turning of a corridor."
  },
  "4499": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:opposite the mirror in the middle of two doors of the men's and women's changing rooms."
  },
  "4500": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown, big, cylinder"
  },
  "4501": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a bed, next to a plant"
  },
  "4502": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is placed in a big bedroom on the second floor."
  },
  "4503": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is next to a bashroom and is next to a balcony."
  },
  "4504": {
    "question": "Question:what does the drawer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Blue and beige, small and cuboid."
  },
  "4505": {
    "question": "Question:where is the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is set near a black and brown chair and a brown cabinet and under a small vase."
  },
  "4506": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the drawer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is in a corridor."
  },
  "4507": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is near a bedroom and a bathroom."
  },
  "4508": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden and metallic, brown, small"
  },
  "4509": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer: under the stone table, next to the cabinet, among the three stools and first from left"
  },
  "4510": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is set in the bright and spacious kitchen."
  },
  "4511": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is facing the stairs, next to the balcony and next to the dining room."
  },
  "4512": {
    "question": "Question:what does the class cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:transparent, tall, glass"
  },
  "4513": {
    "question": "Question:where is the class cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of a storage cabinet, near a massage bed"
  },
  "4514": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the class cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a sauna."
  },
  "4515": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the class cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a storage cabinet and a laundry basket in the corner of the sauna."
  },
  "4516": {
    "question": "Question:what does the drawer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is wooden, rectangular and white."
  },
  "4517": {
    "question": "Question:where is the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is under the table and cabinet."
  },
  "4518": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the drawer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is in the kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "4519": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is under the table and cabinet."
  },
  "4520": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:square, red and white, small"
  },
  "4521": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the washbasin, over against the door"
  },
  "4522": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is settled in a toilet. "
  },
  "4523": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The toilet is next to a warm child-bedroom on the second floor. "
  },
  "4524": {
    "question": "Question:what does the dustbin look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:plastic,cuboid,with a plastic bag,black"
  },
  "4525": {
    "question": "Question:where is the dustbin?",
    "answer": "Answer:under the desk,behind the door,in front of the chair"
  },
  "4526": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the dustbin in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the number 361 small office."
  },
  "4527": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the dustbin?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is connected to the corridor leading to the exit and at the corner of a junction of three roads."
  },
  "4528": {
    "question": "Question:what does the carbinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Woody, rectangular, brown."
  },
  "4529": {
    "question": "Question:where is the carbinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are some red cabinet opposite to this cabinet and a brown desk near it."
  },
  "4530": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the carbinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is set near a woody door."
  },
  "4531": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the carbinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area is located on the corner of the hall and has a glasses door of the hall."
  },
  "4532": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Small, leather and beige and brown."
  },
  "4533": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is on the right side of a wooden table under a wooden box, near a beige, floriated sofa and near a red chair."
  },
  "4534": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in a living room."
  },
  "4535": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is near a study."
  },
  "4536": {
    "question": "Question:what does the kettle look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:glass, transparent and cylindrical"
  },
  "4537": {
    "question": "Question:where is the kettle?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed on a cabinet and close to the sink."
  },
  "4538": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the kettle in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "4539": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the kettle?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to the chatting room and the door."
  },
  "4540": {
    "question": "Question:what does the toilet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White, ladder shaped and porcelainous."
  },
  "4541": {
    "question": "Question:where is the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The toilet is set near a small vase with pink flowers and near a brown cabinet."
  },
  "4542": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the toilet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The toilet is in a toilet."
  },
  "4543": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The toilet is near a bedroom and a corridor."
  },
  "4544": {
    "question": "Question:what does the tap look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:silver, iron"
  },
  "4545": {
    "question": "Question:where is the tap?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is an identical tap on its right, right above it is a mirror."
  },
  "4546": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the tap in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's installed in a bathroom."
  },
  "4547": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the tap?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathroom is built in the main room which  faces the balcony. Right below the room is the swimming pool."
  },
  "4548": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A middle-sized clean mirror with a wooden base."
  },
  "4549": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on a cupboard with many drawers and is near a window."
  },
  "4550": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the bedroom and under the ceiling."
  },
  "4551": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a toilet."
  },
  "4552": {
    "question": "Question:what does the flower look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:green, wood, small"
  },
  "4553": {
    "question": "Question:where is the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:in a vase, in front of a picture"
  },
  "4554": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the flower in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is placed in the corner of a kitchen with wood floor on the first floor."
  },
  "4555": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to a storeroom and there is a cloakroom upstairs."
  },
  "4556": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden, big, square"
  },
  "4557": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the washbasin, over against the bed"
  },
  "4558": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is settled in the corner of a bedroom. "
  },
  "4559": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is next to the corridor on the second floor with a fireplace and a bathroom. "
  },
  "4560": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is made of cloth, rectangular and white."
  },
  "4561": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is under the table and to the right of a chair."
  },
  "4562": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in the living room on the first floor."
  },
  "4563": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is under the table and to the right of a chair."
  },
  "4564": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Wooden and vitreous, rectangular and brown."
  },
  "4565": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is set opposite to a white and red bed and two paintings and above a black shelf."
  },
  "4566": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is in a bedroom."
  },
  "4567": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is near a toilet."
  },
  "4568": {
    "question": "Question:what does the towel look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:piled, white and cotton"
  },
  "4569": {
    "question": "Question:where is the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed on a cabinet and close to a sink."
  },
  "4570": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the towel in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "4571": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to the chatting room and the door."
  },
  "4572": {
    "question": "Question:what does the windows look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Rectangle, white window with lattice"
  },
  "4573": {
    "question": "Question:where is the windows?",
    "answer": "Answer:This window is at the far right of the entire window, above the fluffy stool."
  },
  "4574": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the windows in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed in a bedroom beside a bed."
  },
  "4575": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the windows?",
    "answer": "Answer:This bedroom is located at the end of the right turn on the second floor, opposite a storage room.\n"
  },
  "4576": {
    "question": "Question:what does the washstand look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:marble\uff0clarge and smooth."
  },
  "4577": {
    "question": "Question:where is the washstand?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a trash can under the washstand with a mirror on it."
  },
  "4578": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the washstand in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Washstand is set in the toilet."
  },
  "4579": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the washstand?",
    "answer": "Answer:Washstand is close to the living room and bathroom."
  },
  "4580": {
    "question": "Question:what does the washbasin look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:porcellanous, green and white, big"
  },
  "4581": {
    "question": "Question:where is the washbasin?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the bathtub, below the mirror"
  },
  "4582": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the washbasin in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washbasin is settled in the corner of the toilet. "
  },
  "4583": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the washbasin?",
    "answer": "Answer:The toilet is next to a warm child-bedroom on the second floor. "
  },
  "4584": {
    "question": "Question:what does the flower look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a pot of white, white flowers that are made of plant cells."
  },
  "4585": {
    "question": "Question:where is the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is directly above a table, in the middle of two candles."
  },
  "4586": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the flower in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a study.\n"
  },
  "4587": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a very neat study with many books."
  },
  "4588": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, armless"
  },
  "4589": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It was facing an identical chair with its back to the wall."
  },
  "4590": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It was placed in the hallway between the open kitchen and the pool."
  },
  "4591": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:There's a pool on one side and an open kitchen on the other"
  },
  "4592": {
    "question": "Question:what does the fan look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Silvery, round, tall."
  },
  "4593": {
    "question": "Question:where is the fan?",
    "answer": "Answer:There  is a  red bench next to it and a sign near it."
  },
  "4594": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the fan in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The fan is set  on a corridor which is along the wall."
  },
  "4595": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the fan?",
    "answer": "Answer:This  area has lots of red benches and is located on the central  hall."
  },
  "4596": {
    "question": "Question:what does the Potted plants look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:green,tall"
  },
  "4597": {
    "question": "Question:where is the Potted plants?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a chair and near the rest room door."
  },
  "4598": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the Potted plants in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it' s in the corner of a living room on the second floor."
  },
  "4599": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the Potted plants?",
    "answer": "Answer:the living room is next to a rest room and a balcony."
  },
  "4600": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:An old brown wooden chair."
  },
  "4601": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is set by a table,on a carpet."
  },
  "4602": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Behind it there is a tall cupboard and it is near the downstairs."
  },
  "4603": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near stairs and a door."
  },
  "4604": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown, very small, wooden, Two-door cabinet"
  },
  "4605": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer: Right under it is a washing machine, There is a bigger cabinet on it's left."
  },
  "4606": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is installed in a small laundry."
  },
  "4607": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer: The laundry is flanked by bedrooms, and there is a chandelier in front."
  },
  "4608": {
    "question": "Question:what does the piano look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A small ,old ,wooden ,classic piano."
  },
  "4609": {
    "question": "Question:where is the piano?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is beside a two-wheeled trolley and a black bench."
  },
  "4610": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the piano in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is under the stairs and against the stone wall."
  },
  "4611": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the piano?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near the living room."
  },
  "4612": {
    "question": "Question:what does the painting look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Big, rectangular and papery."
  },
  "4613": {
    "question": "Question:where is the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is above a black and golden table and near a vitreous vase."
  },
  "4614": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the painting in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is in a corridor."
  },
  "4615": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is near a living room on the first floor."
  },
  "4616": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soild, black and metal."
  },
  "4617": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is set under a green painting, near a brassy switch and opposite to a cabinet."
  },
  "4618": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is in a corridor."
  },
  "4619": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is near a toilet and a bedroom."
  },
  "4620": {
    "question": "Question:what does the windows look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Rectangle, white window with lattice"
  },
  "4621": {
    "question": "Question:where is the windows?",
    "answer": "Answer:The window is in the middle of the entire window, above the fluffy stool."
  },
  "4622": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the windows in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed in a bedroom and beside a wardrobe."
  },
  "4623": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the windows?",
    "answer": "Answer:This bedroom is located at the end of the right turn on the second floor, opposite a storage room.\n"
  },
  "4624": {
    "question": "Question:what does the washbasin look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, hollow, white"
  },
  "4625": {
    "question": "Question:where is the washbasin?",
    "answer": "Answer:near a hair drayer, next to another washbasin"
  },
  "4626": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the washbasin in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washbasin is located in a washroom."
  },
  "4627": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the washbasin?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area has a black hair dryer and a door."
  },
  "4628": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:yellow, round and woody"
  },
  "4629": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to the table which is close to the door."
  },
  "4630": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a chatting room on the first floor."
  },
  "4631": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chatting room is next to the hall."
  },
  "4632": {
    "question": "Question:what does the flower look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:woody, green, tall"
  },
  "4633": {
    "question": "Question:where is the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:in a white vase, on a long table"
  },
  "4634": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the flower in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is placed in a bright living room on the first floor."
  },
  "4635": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is next to another small living room and next to a corridor"
  },
  "4636": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Rectangular, small, red."
  },
  "4637": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are one chair with the same size and state on its right and three chairs with the same size and state on its left.There are four chairs with the same size and state opposite to it."
  },
  "4638": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set on a side of the corridor via the altar."
  },
  "4639": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area has a fan and lots of benches on each side of the corridor ."
  },
  "4640": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle,big,framed"
  },
  "4641": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's over the bathtub and in front of the shower cubicle"
  },
  "4642": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's at the center of room."
  },
  "4643": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:there is a bedroom in front of it"
  },
  "4644": {
    "question": "Question:what does the screen look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Closed, liquid crystal, displayable"
  },
  "4645": {
    "question": "Question:where is the screen?",
    "answer": "Answer:The screen is set on a yellow table, near the stairs,next to a shelf."
  },
  "4646": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the screen in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The screen is placed in the front desk."
  },
  "4647": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the screen?",
    "answer": "Answer:The screen is set near the stairs and the hall."
  },
  "4648": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle,tall,dark brown"
  },
  "4649": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the door, next to the fireplace"
  },
  "4650": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is settled in the corner of a bedroom."
  },
  "4651": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is next to the corridor on the second floor with a fireplace and a bathroom."
  },
  "4652": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Wooden, golden and soild. "
  },
  "4653": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is in the second row and the first column of the six pictures, before a white wall and near a cabinet."
  },
  "4654": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is in a living room."
  },
  "4655": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is near a study."
  },
  "4656": {
    "question": "Question:what does the telephone look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soild, quadrangular and black."
  },
  "4657": {
    "question": "Question:where is the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:The telephone is next to a metal lamp and opposite to a electronic keyboard."
  },
  "4658": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the telephone in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The telephone is in a living room."
  },
  "4659": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:The telephone is near a bedroom and a toilet."
  },
  "4660": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a new, wooden, white chair."
  },
  "4661": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to a sofa chair and a stool."
  },
  "4662": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is in a living room.\n"
  },
  "4663": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a clean, tidy and spacious living room.\n"
  },
  "4664": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle, woody and brown"
  },
  "4665": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is above the cabinet and facing the bed."
  },
  "4666": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a bedroom on the first floor."
  },
  "4667": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is at the right turn of the gate."
  },
  "4668": {
    "question": "Question:what does the telephone look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black and white,square,metal"
  },
  "4669": {
    "question": "Question:where is the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the left of the printer,in front of a cream and on the right of the computer"
  },
  "4670": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the telephone in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a big office with the number 377."
  },
  "4671": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is around the corner of a junction of three corridors and on the left of the stairway door."
  },
  "4672": {
    "question": "Question:what does the fan look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White, hanging on the roof and five fan blades"
  },
  "4673": {
    "question": "Question:where is the fan?",
    "answer": "Answer:It hangs on the roof and there is a roof light attached to it."
  },
  "4674": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the fan in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The fan is in a bedroom and above the bed."
  },
  "4675": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the fan?",
    "answer": "Answer:This bedroom is located at the end of the right turn on the second floor, next to another bedroom and a storage room."
  },
  "4676": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:made of porcelain;with wooden frames; white; circle;"
  },
  "4677": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:below a tap; faced with a narrow bed used for massage;"
  },
  "4678": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:a small and long room with wooden floors."
  },
  "4679": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:kind of cramped and dim."
  },
  "4680": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black,plastic and metal,tall,with five wheels"
  },
  "4681": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of a desk,between two same chairs and on the right of a cabinet"
  },
  "4682": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in the middle seat of the left side of small office."
  },
  "4683": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is at the corner of the crossroads and near the tea room and the locker room."
  },
  "4684": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, black, plastic"
  },
  "4685": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's put on a table, next to a bed."
  },
  "4686": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in a small bright bedroom."
  },
  "4687": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:It has the main bedroom on one side and the laundry on the other."
  },
  "4688": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:tall and big, cylindrical, brown"
  },
  "4689": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the floor, next to the sofa, next to the window"
  },
  "4690": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is located in the bright bedroom."
  },
  "4691": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is on the first floor and next to the kitchen."
  },
  "4692": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Wooden, brown and tall."
  },
  "4693": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is on the left side of a red and brown chair and opposite to a wooden table."
  },
  "4694": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is in a bedroom."
  },
  "4695": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is on the opposite side of a corridor with a wooden stair."
  },
  "4696": {
    "question": "Question:what does the hand door look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Silver, small and metal."
  },
  "4697": {
    "question": "Question:where is the hand door?",
    "answer": "Answer:The hand door was close to the bathtub and cabinet."
  },
  "4698": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the hand door in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The hand door is in the bathroom."
  },
  "4699": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the hand door?",
    "answer": "Answer:The hand door is close to the bedroom and toilet."
  },
  "4700": {
    "question": "Question:what does the painting look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, colorful "
  },
  "4701": {
    "question": "Question:where is the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a chair under the painting. On it's left is a big cabinet."
  },
  "4702": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the painting in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in a small bright bedroom."
  },
  "4703": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:It has the main bedroom on one side and the laundry on the other."
  },
  "4704": {
    "question": "Question:what does the painting look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:square, colorful, abstract"
  },
  "4705": {
    "question": "Question:where is the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a big sofa right under it. It's facing a LCD TV."
  },
  "4706": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the painting in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is hang on the reception area."
  },
  "4707": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area faces the open kitchen, next to the pool, and dinning table on the other side."
  },
  "4708": {
    "question": "Question:what does the door handle look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:silver, metal, door-mounted "
  },
  "4709": {
    "question": "Question:where is the door handle?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the window, on the door"
  },
  "4710": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the door handle in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the study."
  },
  "4711": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the door handle?",
    "answer": "Answer:The study is next to the bathroom and children's bedroom."
  },
  "4712": {
    "question": "Question:what does the towel look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cloth,medium size and white."
  },
  "4713": {
    "question": "Question:where is the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is on the towel rack and bathtub."
  },
  "4714": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the towel in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Towels in the bathroom."
  },
  "4715": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:Towels are close to the bedroom and toilet."
  },
  "4716": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black, rectangle and woody"
  },
  "4717": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is between two sofas and beneath the light hanging on the ceiling."
  },
  "4718": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:\nIt is in living roon on the first floor."
  },
  "4719": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is the room facing the door."
  },
  "4720": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, rectangular, white"
  },
  "4721": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are quilts which be decorated by many flowers on the double bed and the double bed is between two lamps."
  },
  "4722": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The double bed is set in the master bedroom."
  },
  "4723": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The master bedroom has a bathroom, a cloakroom and a window."
  },
  "4724": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:green, wooden, square"
  },
  "4725": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:below the TV, over against the bed"
  },
  "4726": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is settled in a warm child-bedroom. "
  },
  "4727": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The child-bedroom is next to the corridor on the second floor with a fireplace and a bathroom."
  },
  "4728": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big,long,soft"
  },
  "4729": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in front of a round table and next to a window."
  },
  "4730": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a rest room on the second floor."
  },
  "4731": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:the rest room is next to a dining room and a living room."
  },
  "4732": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Four-leg wooden chair with a cloth on it."
  },
  "4733": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It locates beside the wall and under a window,near a wooden closet."
  },
  "4734": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed in the corner in a bed room. "
  },
  "4735": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is near a toilet."
  },
  "4736": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Medium size, soild and leather."
  },
  "4737": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is near a big beige sofa, near a small lamp and near a wooden and vitreous desk."
  },
  "4738": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in a living room."
  },
  "4739": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is near a corridor."
  },
  "4740": {
    "question": "Question:what does the light look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White, metallic and electronic."
  },
  "4741": {
    "question": "Question:where is the light?",
    "answer": "Answer:The light is in front of a fan and there is the same light on the left of it."
  },
  "4742": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the light in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The light is on the ceiling of a big living room."
  },
  "4743": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the light?",
    "answer": "Answer:The light is above the living room and near a attic."
  },
  "4744": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pillow look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cloth, black and white, small"
  },
  "4745": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the wooden table, next to the doll, under the window"
  },
  "4746": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pillow in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The pillow is set in the bedroom."
  },
  "4747": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is on the second floor and on the left of the corridor when go upstairs."
  },
  "4748": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:circle, black, wood"
  },
  "4749": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:under a lamp, next to a bed"
  },
  "4750": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is in the corner of a bedroom on the first floor."
  },
  "4751": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is next to a bashroom and there is a bashroom upstairs."
  },
  "4752": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a square, paper, white painting."
  },
  "4753": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is inside a wooden picture frame next to a door."
  },
  "4754": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a corridor."
  },
  "4755": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is beside a staircase."
  },
  "4756": {
    "question": "Question:what does the printer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white,small,metal"
  },
  "4757": {
    "question": "Question:where is the printer?",
    "answer": "Answer:between a screen and a receipt printer,at the edge of a desk and in front of a elastic"
  },
  "4758": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the printer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The printer is in a big office."
  },
  "4759": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the printer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is in front of a corridor door and next to the tea room."
  },
  "4760": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, white, solid"
  },
  "4761": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:under the mirror, next to a white vase"
  },
  "4762": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the washroom."
  },
  "4763": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is located in a bedroom which has a rectangular balcony, a washroom and a toilet, and the cloakroom is next to the washroom and toilet."
  },
  "4764": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp post look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:galss, erect and blue"
  },
  "4765": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp post?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to some chairs and the piano."
  },
  "4766": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp post in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a chatting room on the first floor."
  },
  "4767": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp post?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chatting room is next to the hall."
  },
  "4768": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bathtub look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathtub is white, large and ceramic."
  },
  "4769": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bathtub?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathtub is beside the toilet and the window."
  },
  "4770": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bathtub in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathtub is in the bathroom of the bedroom."
  },
  "4771": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bathtub?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathtub is beside the toilet and the window."
  },
  "4772": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:dark,sponge,soft"
  },
  "4773": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a round same style stool , a same kind of chair and a woolen desk "
  },
  "4774": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a study room on the second floor"
  },
  "4775": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:the study room is near a balcony and a stair"
  },
  "4776": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is an old wooden brown cabinet."
  },
  "4777": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:He was directly under the sink and diagonally below a ceiling light."
  },
  "4778": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:This cupboard is in the study."
  },
  "4779": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a white long table and many white chairs in this study."
  },
  "4780": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black,bright,metal"
  },
  "4781": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's on a round small table,next to a chair and a painting"
  },
  "4782": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a corridor which is in front of the stair on the first floor"
  },
  "4783": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:corridor links a living room , 2 bedrooms and a rest room"
  },
  "4784": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, wooden, white"
  },
  "4785": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the right of the door, next to the safe"
  },
  "4786": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is located in the cloakroom."
  },
  "4787": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cloakroom is inside the bedroom, on the floor and next to the kitchen."
  },
  "4788": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:woody, big, soft "
  },
  "4789": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the white lamps and the window"
  },
  "4790": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the bedroom "
  },
  "4791": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the corridor and on the second floor."
  },
  "4792": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, graceful and cylindrical "
  },
  "4793": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:near the mazarine bed and another lamp with the same color and shape, next to a window with white curtain"
  },
  "4794": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:This lamp is in the bedroom."
  },
  "4795": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is near the stairs and the bathroom."
  },
  "4796": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:light, woody and white"
  },
  "4797": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed on a white cabinet next to a green plant."
  },
  "4798": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a bedroom on the second floor."
  },
  "4799": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is at the left rear corner of the stairs."
  },
  "4800": {
    "question": "Question:what does the architecture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Medium size, capitate and white."
  },
  "4801": {
    "question": "Question:where is the architecture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sculpture is on a brown table, near a gray curtain and a transparent table."
  },
  "4802": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the architecture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sculpture is in a dining room."
  },
  "4803": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the architecture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sculpture is near a kitchen."
  },
  "4804": {
    "question": "Question:what does the towel look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A plaid soft wet towel."
  },
  "4805": {
    "question": "Question:where is the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is hanging on a handle,next to an oven."
  },
  "4806": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the towel in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the kitchen,under the cooktop."
  },
  "4807": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near the dining room."
  },
  "4808": {
    "question": "Question:what does the power switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The switch is square, irony and small."
  },
  "4809": {
    "question": "Question:where is the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is placed next to the flower and the table."
  },
  "4810": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the power switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is placed next to the flower and the table facing the stairs."
  },
  "4811": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a set of sofa and table outside the door."
  },
  "4812": {
    "question": "Question:what does the power switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The switch is square, irony and small."
  },
  "4813": {
    "question": "Question:where is the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is placed next to the flower and the table."
  },
  "4814": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the power switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is placed next to the flower and the table facing the stairs."
  },
  "4815": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a set of sofa and table outside the door."
  },
  "4816": {
    "question": "Question:what does the electronic keyboard look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Black, soild and medium size."
  },
  "4817": {
    "question": "Question:where is the electronic keyboard?",
    "answer": "Answer:The electronic keyboard is next to a black bookcase and opposite to a telephone and a lamp."
  },
  "4818": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the electronic keyboard in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The electronic keyboard is in a living room."
  },
  "4819": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the electronic keyboard?",
    "answer": "Answer:The electronic keyboard is near a bedroom and a toilet."
  },
  "4820": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:metal,yellow"
  },
  "4821": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a television and a same chair."
  },
  "4822": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a rest room on the second floor."
  },
  "4823": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:the rest room is in a big bedroom which is in the end of a corridor and near a open-balcony."
  },
  "4824": {
    "question": "Question:what does the potted plant look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:green, woody, erect"
  },
  "4825": {
    "question": "Question:where is the potted plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:against the wall, between two bedrooms"
  },
  "4826": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the potted plant in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The potted plant is put in a corner."
  },
  "4827": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the potted plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:The corner is between two bedrooms and connects with a gymnasium."
  },
  "4828": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is rectangular, white and wooden."
  },
  "4829": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is in the lower left corner of the towel and brush."
  },
  "4830": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is inside the bathroom."
  },
  "4831": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is in the lower left corner of the towel and brush."
  },
  "4832": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bathtub look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big,white,rounded"
  },
  "4833": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bathtub?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's between window and washstand"
  },
  "4834": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bathtub in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in the bathroom"
  },
  "4835": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bathtub?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's bedroom outside the bathroom"
  },
  "4836": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A small silver sink."
  },
  "4837": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is under a circular mirror and on a granite board."
  },
  "4838": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is set on a wooden desk."
  },
  "4839": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a stair and entrances to bedrooms."
  },
  "4840": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Tall,wooden,white."
  },
  "4841": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is placed on the ground ,next to a black dustbin and a black chair."
  },
  "4842": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is set in a small conference room."
  },
  "4843": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is set near a bigger conference room and next to the hall."
  },
  "4844": {
    "question": "Question:what does the oven look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A black square oven with many buttons."
  },
  "4845": {
    "question": "Question:where is the oven?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a big white table and is surrounded by drawers."
  },
  "4846": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the oven in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the kitchen."
  },
  "4847": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the oven?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near the dining hall."
  },
  "4848": {
    "question": "Question:what does the telephone look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Small, black and metal."
  },
  "4849": {
    "question": "Question:where is the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:The telephone is next to a beige and brown lamp and near a blue and white bed."
  },
  "4850": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the telephone in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The telephone is in a bedroom."
  },
  "4851": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:The telephone is near a corridor and a storage room."
  },
  "4852": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, white, small"
  },
  "4853": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a tall plant, facing a small table"
  },
  "4854": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is placed in the middle of a small room facing a white and big living room."
  },
  "4855": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is facing another big and bright living room and is next to a corridor on the first floor."
  },
  "4856": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:ceramic, rounded and with red flowers."
  },
  "4857": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is in front of a stone dome and near some grass."
  },
  "4858": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is outdoors."
  },
  "4859": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area connects house and outdoors with a stone dome."
  },
  "4860": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sculpture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:tall,stony and hard"
  },
  "4861": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sculpture?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a glass door ,2 chairs and a round transparent table with a ball."
  },
  "4862": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sculpture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a living room on the second floor."
  },
  "4863": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sculpture?",
    "answer": "Answer:the living room is next to a open-balcony and a dining room."
  },
  "4864": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:plastic cement and metal,tall,black,owning five wheels and two handrails"
  },
  "4865": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in front of the white office desk and is near two smaller foldable chairs."
  },
  "4866": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in a small working office of the number 365 that only has the room for one person working."
  },
  "4867": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is nearly at the end of the corridor and faces the tea room at a slant."
  },
  "4868": {
    "question": "Question:what does the desk look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:woody, small, rectangular"
  },
  "4869": {
    "question": "Question:where is the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the staircase and the big black toy bear"
  },
  "4870": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the desk in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the living room"
  },
  "4871": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is on the second floor and next to the staircase and corridor."
  },
  "4872": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a square, wooden black cabinet."
  },
  "4873": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a box and a few flowers on it."
  },
  "4874": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in the bedroom."
  },
  "4875": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is beside the corridor."
  },
  "4876": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a white square sofa filled with cotton."
  },
  "4877": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is beside a table and a stool."
  },
  "4878": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the living room.\n"
  },
  "4879": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:This living room is very neat and white.\n"
  },
  "4880": {
    "question": "Question:what does the desk look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:made of wood, with one desk leg, it's black"
  },
  "4881": {
    "question": "Question:where is the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a big book put on the desk, and a single sofa is next to it "
  },
  "4882": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the desk in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The small desk is placed close to a single sofa at the coner in the living room."
  },
  "4883": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a balcony outside  the living room and a big mirror inside ,but there is no TV. "
  },
  "4884": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, small-sized, white and green "
  },
  "4885": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer: next to another bed with the same color and shape and in front of a black and white wall painting, near the armoire"
  },
  "4886": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is in the bedroom."
  },
  "4887": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is in front of the bathroom on the third floor and next to the stairs."
  },
  "4888": {
    "question": "Question:what does the switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, rectangular, plastic"
  },
  "4889": {
    "question": "Question:where is the switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:between a tall shelf and a door, in front of a table"
  },
  "4890": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The switch is on the wall in a study."
  },
  "4891": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are a big table and two chairs in the center of the study."
  },
  "4892": {
    "question": "Question:what does the recline look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cloth, gray, rectangular"
  },
  "4893": {
    "question": "Question:where is the recline?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the left of the table, in front of the bush"
  },
  "4894": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the recline in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The recline is located in a sunny coutryard."
  },
  "4895": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the recline?",
    "answer": "Answer:The courtyard is on the first floor and outside the livingroom."
  },
  "4896": {
    "question": "Question:what does the door locker look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, golden, metallic"
  },
  "4897": {
    "question": "Question:where is the door locker?",
    "answer": "Answer:on a door, against the wall"
  },
  "4898": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the door locker in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The door locker is located in a washroom."
  },
  "4899": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the door locker?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area has a door and a large wardrobe."
  },
  "4900": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is long, black and glows."
  },
  "4901": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is above the table and flowers."
  },
  "4902": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is in the kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "4903": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is on the table and flowers."
  },
  "4904": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is black, big and long."
  },
  "4905": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is on the ceiling and above the vase."
  },
  "4906": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is in the kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "4907": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is above the flowers and the table."
  },
  "4908": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is black, long and metallic."
  },
  "4909": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is above the flowers and the table."
  },
  "4910": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is on the ground floor kitchen."
  },
  "4911": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is above the table and flowers."
  },
  "4912": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is long, large and black."
  },
  "4913": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is on the table and flowers."
  },
  "4914": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is in the kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "4915": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is on the ceiling and above the vase."
  },
  "4916": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is long, large and black."
  },
  "4917": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is above the flowers and the table."
  },
  "4918": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is in the kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "4919": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is above the flowers and the table."
  },
  "4920": {
    "question": "Question:what does the massage bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, soft, rectangular"
  },
  "4921": {
    "question": "Question:where is the massage bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a treadmill, near a massage bed"
  },
  "4922": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the massage bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is put in a gymnaisum."
  },
  "4923": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the massage bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area connects with washrooms and a bar."
  },
  "4924": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:made by stainless steel,crooked,argent"
  },
  "4925": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:over the water channel,opposite to the locker and on the right of the liquid soap"
  },
  "4926": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is in the tea room."
  },
  "4927": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The tea room is next to an exit and opposite to a small resting area."
  },
  "4928": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White, wooden and cuboid."
  },
  "4929": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a washing machine and a dryer under the cabinet."
  },
  "4930": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is on a laundry."
  },
  "4931": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is connected with a kitchen and the cabinet faces a bigger cabinet."
  },
  "4932": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa/seat look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Genuine leather\uff0cSingle sofa."
  },
  "4933": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa/seat?",
    "answer": "Answer:There have four sofas in the last row. Facing forward, It's first from left to right.It's under the projector."
  },
  "4934": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa/seat in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in the last row of the screening hall, facing the door direction from left to right, the first sofa."
  },
  "4935": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa/seat?",
    "answer": "Answer:The nearest area is the living room."
  },
  "4936": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pot look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:stone, round and black"
  },
  "4937": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pot?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed between the lamp post and the door."
  },
  "4938": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pot in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a chatting room on the first floor."
  },
  "4939": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pot?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chatting room is next to the hall."
  },
  "4940": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bench look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:stony,curved,white,hard"
  },
  "4941": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bench?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in front of a lawn and between 2 sculptures"
  },
  "4942": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bench in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's on a balcony on the second floor"
  },
  "4943": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bench?",
    "answer": "Answer:the balcony is near a garden and a study room with a stair"
  },
  "4944": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is large, wooden and brown."
  },
  "4945": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is on the carpet and around the chair."
  },
  "4946": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is in the parlor on the first floor."
  },
  "4947": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is on the carpet and around the chair."
  },
  "4948": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A small wooden black chair with a restback."
  },
  "4949": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is beside a wooden cabinet which has flowers on it and is front of fake grass."
  },
  "4950": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed close to a glass and stone wall."
  },
  "4951": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near stairs and a table surrounded by eight chairs."
  },
  "4952": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the night table,medium-size and near a box"
  },
  "4953": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's near a box and on the night table"
  },
  "4954": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the side of the room"
  },
  "4955": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a corridor outside the room"
  },
  "4956": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:sponge,soft,long"
  },
  "4957": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a window and 2 curtains."
  },
  "4958": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a big bedroom on the second floor."
  },
  "4959": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:the bedroom is in the end of a corridor and  next to a open -balcony."
  },
  "4960": {
    "question": "Question:what does the drawer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, wood, rectangular"
  },
  "4961": {
    "question": "Question:where is the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a drawer, next to a hand sink"
  },
  "4962": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the drawer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is settled in a kitchen with wood floor on the first floor."
  },
  "4963": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to a small storeroom and there is a cloakroom upstairs."
  },
  "4964": {
    "question": "Question:what does the coffeemaker look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A grey metal automatic coffeemaker."
  },
  "4965": {
    "question": "Question:where is the coffeemaker?",
    "answer": "Answer:The coffeemaker is at the edge of a white table,close to a sink."
  },
  "4966": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the coffeemaker in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is set in the kitchen beside a corridor."
  },
  "4967": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the coffeemaker?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a dining room."
  },
  "4968": {
    "question": "Question:what does the wall look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, woody,  "
  },
  "4969": {
    "question": "Question:where is the wall?",
    "answer": "Answer:across the sofa, the TV is mounted on the wall"
  },
  "4970": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the wall in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the living room."
  },
  "4971": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the wall?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the dining room and the kitchen."
  },
  "4972": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle, cotton and fluffy"
  },
  "4973": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on the black carpet and next to the stairs."
  },
  "4974": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in living roon on the first floor."
  },
  "4975": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is the room facing the door."
  },
  "4976": {
    "question": "Question:what does the telephone look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:metal,black and white,rectangle"
  },
  "4977": {
    "question": "Question:where is the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of three screens,on the right side of some documents and under a yellow note"
  },
  "4978": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the telephone in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The telephone is in a vast office."
  },
  "4979": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is in front of a corridor door,along the road connecting the tea room and the restaurant."
  },
  "4980": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, cylinder, metal"
  },
  "4981": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of a mirror, on the left of a fire place"
  },
  "4982": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is placed in the corner of a white living room."
  },
  "4983": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living is on the first floor and is next to a long corridor."
  },
  "4984": {
    "question": "Question:what does the dispenser look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white;plastic;small;"
  },
  "4985": {
    "question": "Question:where is the dispenser?",
    "answer": "Answer:below a wall lamp; beside a wastebasket;"
  },
  "4986": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the dispenser in?",
    "answer": "Answer:by side of a narrow hallway;"
  },
  "4987": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the dispenser?",
    "answer": "Answer:a long mirror above an electronic scale near it."
  },
  "4988": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white,soft,cotton"
  },
  "4989": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:they are next to a black long table and near a pool table,"
  },
  "4990": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:they are in a living room on the first floor."
  },
  "4991": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:the living room is next to a corridor and a stair."
  },
  "4992": {
    "question": "Question:what does the paintings look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soild, rectangular and black and white."
  },
  "4993": {
    "question": "Question:where is the paintings?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is set on a black wooden bookshelf, near a black sculpture and below six paintings."
  },
  "4994": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the paintings in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is in a study."
  },
  "4995": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the paintings?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is near a living room and a bathroom."
  },
  "4996": {
    "question": "Question:what does the decotations look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, colorful, fragile"
  },
  "4997": {
    "question": "Question:where is the decotations?",
    "answer": "Answer:near a chandelier, on a wall"
  },
  "4998": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the decotations in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The decotations are hanging on the wall in a gymnasium."
  },
  "4999": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the decotations?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are a spinning bike and a treadmill in this gymnasium."
  },
  "5000": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A brown wooden chair with a backrest."
  },
  "5001": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is beside a grey fridge and a dark green carpet in the dining room."
  },
  "5002": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is front of a glass door."
  },
  "5003": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is near a kicthen."
  },
  "5004": {
    "question": "Question:what does the book look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Leather, rectangular, brown."
  },
  "5005": {
    "question": "Question:where is the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a book with the same material, shape, colour on its right and a round fan next to it."
  },
  "5006": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the book in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The book is set on a red bench in front of a stone pillar."
  },
  "5007": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area has a long corridor  close to the wall."
  },
  "5008": {
    "question": "Question:what does the door look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:woody , brown , tall"
  },
  "5009": {
    "question": "Question:where is the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the sink , next to the shower room"
  },
  "5010": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the door in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The door is located at the center of the bathroom."
  },
  "5011": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathroom is inside of the bedroom."
  },
  "5012": {
    "question": "Question:what does the doorhand look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Small, metal and silver."
  },
  "5013": {
    "question": "Question:where is the doorhand?",
    "answer": "Answer:The doorhand is on the door, next to the bathtub."
  },
  "5014": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the doorhand in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The doorhand is in the bathroom."
  },
  "5015": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the doorhand?",
    "answer": "Answer:The doorhand is close to the toilet and bedroom."
  },
  "5016": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool  look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Wooden, brown and long."
  },
  "5017": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool ?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is against the wall and near a desk."
  },
  "5018": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool  in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is in a dining room."
  },
  "5019": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool ?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to a kitchen and across from a fireplace."
  },
  "5020": {
    "question": "Question:what does the light look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White, metallic and electronic."
  },
  "5021": {
    "question": "Question:where is the light?",
    "answer": "Answer:The light is near a wooden door and there is the same light on the right of it."
  },
  "5022": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the light in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The light is on the ceiling of a big living room."
  },
  "5023": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the light?",
    "answer": "Answer:The light is above the living room and near a attic."
  },
  "5024": {
    "question": "Question:what does the switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:plastic, rectangle."
  },
  "5025": {
    "question": "Question:where is the switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:It has an outlet right under it and It has a very similar switch on its right."
  },
  "5026": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in the first floor where face the dinning table."
  },
  "5027": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:the garden is on its left and the swimming pool is on it's right."
  },
  "5028": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A small deep grey sofa with a light grey pillow."
  },
  "5029": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is beside a small table and in front of a lamp."
  },
  "5030": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a bedroom on the second floor near the balcony."
  },
  "5031": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a stair."
  },
  "5032": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A grey white sofa with a pillow and a scarf."
  },
  "5033": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on the left side of a bed and beside a window."
  },
  "5034": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a bedroom with a double door."
  },
  "5035": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a bathroom and a living room."
  },
  "5036": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is black, small and rectangular."
  },
  "5037": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp hung on the wall and to the left of the door."
  },
  "5038": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is beside the outdoor swimming pool."
  },
  "5039": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp hung on the wall and to the left of the door."
  },
  "5040": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:made of leather,soft"
  },
  "5041": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a fireplace and a small round table with a lamp ,and there is a same one in front of it"
  },
  "5042": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's near a corridor on the first floor"
  },
  "5043": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:the corridor is near 2 bedroom ,a living room and a stair"
  },
  "5044": {
    "question": "Question:what does the box look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Wooden, brown and cuboid."
  },
  "5045": {
    "question": "Question:where is the box?",
    "answer": "Answer:The box is next to a flowerbed and a telescope."
  },
  "5046": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the box in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The box is in a narrow room."
  },
  "5047": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the box?",
    "answer": "Answer:The narrow room is connected with an attic and stairs."
  },
  "5048": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Black,wooden,cuboid"
  },
  "5049": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is placed in front of a mirror and near a brown box."
  },
  "5050": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is placed in the corridor."
  },
  "5051": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is placed near a stairs and a big conference."
  },
  "5052": {
    "question": "Question:what does the power switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is small, white and rectangular."
  },
  "5053": {
    "question": "Question:where is the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is opposite the washing machine and next to the window."
  },
  "5054": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the power switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is in the laundry room."
  },
  "5055": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is opposite the washing machine and next to the window."
  },
  "5056": {
    "question": "Question:what does the light look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:plastic, round and white"
  },
  "5057": {
    "question": "Question:where is the light?",
    "answer": "Answer:The light is on the left of the mirror and above the sink."
  },
  "5058": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the light in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a restroom on the second floor."
  },
  "5059": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the light?",
    "answer": "Answer:The restroom is on the life side of the stairs."
  },
  "5060": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Black,plastic,rotatable"
  },
  "5061": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is placed under a yellow table and near a shelf."
  },
  "5062": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is placed in the front desk."
  },
  "5063": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set near the stairs and next to the hall."
  },
  "5064": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A long yellow wooden table."
  },
  "5065": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a black chair and the stair."
  },
  "5066": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near the corridor and on the second floor."
  },
  "5067": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a kitchen and a bedroom."
  },
  "5068": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A long, thin and black lamp made of wood."
  },
  "5069": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is set on a white wall and there is a white candle on it."
  },
  "5070": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is set in the dining room."
  },
  "5071": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a corridor next to the living room"
  },
  "5072": {
    "question": "Question:what does the towel look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:hairy, blue and brown, rectangular"
  },
  "5073": {
    "question": "Question:where is the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:face the washbasin, next to the closestool"
  },
  "5074": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the towel in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towels are in the bathroom."
  },
  "5075": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathroom is next to the stairs and six bedrooms on the third floor."
  },
  "5076": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Transparent glass vase with a little water in it."
  },
  "5077": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:White flowers are in it, and the vase is on the sink."
  },
  "5078": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is inside the toilet."
  },
  "5079": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is beside the window, opposite the bathroom."
  },
  "5080": {
    "question": "Question:what does the plate look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:silver, big, round"
  },
  "5081": {
    "question": "Question:where is the plate?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the table, next to the vase, next to the bottle"
  },
  "5082": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the plate in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The plate is set in the livingroom."
  },
  "5083": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the plate?",
    "answer": "Answer:The livingroom is next to the dining room and next to the kitchen."
  },
  "5084": {
    "question": "Question:what does the wardrobe look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:woody, large, rectangular"
  },
  "5085": {
    "question": "Question:where is the wardrobe?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a laundry basket, against a wall"
  },
  "5086": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the wardrobe in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The wardrobe is in a man washroom."
  },
  "5087": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the wardrobe?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washroom has a door and a white hair dryer."
  },
  "5088": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Medium size, soild and h-shaped."
  },
  "5089": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set next to a round brown table, near a vase and near a black television."
  },
  "5090": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in a dining room."
  },
  "5091": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is near a kitchen and a living room."
  },
  "5092": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:tall and erect,plastic and metal,black,with two handrails"
  },
  "5093": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is next to a short dark brown locker, in front of a desk full of paper and next to a glass wall."
  },
  "5094": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in a big office containing many drink and snacks."
  },
  "5095": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is at the corner is at the corner of the three fork road and next to an empty office and opposite to the room 356."
  },
  "5096": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white , bright, a little tall"
  },
  "5097": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the table and next to the bed"
  },
  "5098": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the bedroom"
  },
  "5099": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the corridor and on the second floor."
  },
  "5100": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bush look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:green, short, alive"
  },
  "5101": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bush?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the stairs, in front of the French window"
  },
  "5102": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bush in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bush is in the living room."
  },
  "5103": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bush?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is next to the dining room and the balcony."
  },
  "5104": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:filmy, white, concise "
  },
  "5105": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to two beds, another lamp with the same color and shape and the armoire"
  },
  "5106": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is in the bedroom."
  },
  "5107": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is next to the stairs and faces the bathroom."
  },
  "5108": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:standing, black and light"
  },
  "5109": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is between the window and a white cabinet."
  },
  "5110": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a bedroom on the second floor."
  },
  "5111": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is at the left rear corner of the stairs."
  },
  "5112": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A small black lamp which has a stalk and a base."
  },
  "5113": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on a wooden desk beside the bed and is near switches."
  },
  "5114": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It lies in a bedroom which has two lamps in it."
  },
  "5115": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a toilet and near the door."
  },
  "5116": {
    "question": "Question:what does the windows look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Woody, white and deciduous"
  },
  "5117": {
    "question": "Question:where is the windows?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a sliding window divided into 12 pieces of glass."
  },
  "5118": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the windows in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located between two lights beside the bed in a bedroom."
  },
  "5119": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the windows?",
    "answer": "Answer:This bedroom is located at the end of the right turn on the second floor, next to another bedroom and a storage room."
  },
  "5120": {
    "question": "Question:what does the massage bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, soft, rectangular"
  },
  "5121": {
    "question": "Question:where is the massage bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:near a massage bed, in front of a sauna room"
  },
  "5122": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the massage bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The massage bed is put in a sauna."
  },
  "5123": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the massage bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area has two massage beds and a laundry basket.                                                                                                                    "
  },
  "5124": {
    "question": "Question:what does the portrait look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, black, square"
  },
  "5125": {
    "question": "Question:where is the portrait?",
    "answer": "Answer:biside the cabinet, facing the TV"
  },
  "5126": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the portrait in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The portrait is settled in the corner of a bedroom. "
  },
  "5127": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the portrait?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is next to the corridor on the second floor with a fireplace and a bathroom. "
  },
  "5128": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Square, wooden and brown."
  },
  "5129": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is surrounded by four beige and brown chairs, near a big television."
  },
  "5130": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is in a living room on the first floor."
  },
  "5131": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is near a corridor."
  },
  "5132": {
    "question": "Question:what does the painting look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Rectangular, small and papery."
  },
  "5133": {
    "question": "Question:where is the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is near two black screens and near a black television."
  },
  "5134": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the painting in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is in a bedroom."
  },
  "5135": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is near a corridor and a laundry."
  },
  "5136": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:squared; shallow;with black rims;"
  },
  "5137": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pool?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of the stairs covered by thin carpets; near two shower cubicles;"
  },
  "5138": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:at the end of the hallway,tightly surrounded by walls on three sides;"
  },
  "5139": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The walls are decorated with ceramic tiles."
  },
  "5140": {
    "question": "Question:what does the dustbin look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Black,plastic,cylindrical"
  },
  "5141": {
    "question": "Question:where is the dustbin?",
    "answer": "Answer:The dustbin is set on the ground next to a white chair in a corner."
  },
  "5142": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the dustbin in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The dustbin is placed in a small conference room."
  },
  "5143": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the dustbin?",
    "answer": "Answer:The dustbin is set near a bigger conference room and next to the hall."
  },
  "5144": {
    "question": "Question:what does the door look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Woody, white and rectangle"
  },
  "5145": {
    "question": "Question:where is the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed beside a restroom and next to three pictures."
  },
  "5146": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the door in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed in a bedroom opposite the stairs."
  },
  "5147": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is located on the left of the stairs and next to the restroom."
  },
  "5148": {
    "question": "Question:what does the flowers look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Blooming, colorful and beautiful."
  },
  "5149": {
    "question": "Question:where is the flowers?",
    "answer": "Answer:Flowers are on the table."
  },
  "5150": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the flowers in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Flowers are in the living room."
  },
  "5151": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the flowers?",
    "answer": "Answer:They are very close to the bedroom and toilet."
  },
  "5152": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown, little, Two-door cabinet"
  },
  "5153": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a washing machine on it's right. There is the same cabinet directly above it"
  },
  "5154": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is installed in a small laundry."
  },
  "5155": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer: The laundry is flanked by bedrooms, and there is a chandelier in front"
  },
  "5156": {
    "question": "Question:what does the guitar look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Brown, wooden and big."
  },
  "5157": {
    "question": "Question:where is the guitar?",
    "answer": "Answer:The guitar is on the right side of a beige and brown lamp and a black telephone, and near a blue and white bed."
  },
  "5158": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the guitar in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The guitar is in a bedroom."
  },
  "5159": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the guitar?",
    "answer": "Answer:The guitar is near a corridor and a storage room."
  },
  "5160": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A black woodem cabinet with metal handles."
  },
  "5161": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is over a shelf and some towels."
  },
  "5162": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the laundry room."
  },
  "5163": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near the corridor on the second floor and a bedroom."
  },
  "5164": {
    "question": "Question:what does the kitchen look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Metal, silver, cuboid"
  },
  "5165": {
    "question": "Question:where is the kitchen?",
    "answer": "Answer:kitchen next to a stone cylinder and swimming pool"
  },
  "5166": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the kitchen in?",
    "answer": "Answer:kitchen on the balcony"
  },
  "5167": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the kitchen?",
    "answer": "Answer:kitchen Next to the living room"
  },
  "5168": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soild, leather and beige and brown."
  },
  "5169": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is on the right side of the black wooden screen and in front of the window."
  },
  "5170": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in a living room."
  },
  "5171": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is near a study."
  },
  "5172": {
    "question": "Question:what does the coffee maker look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, small, silver"
  },
  "5173": {
    "question": "Question:where is the coffee maker?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the table, next to the Tablet PC"
  },
  "5174": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the coffee maker in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The coffee maker is set in the bright kitchen."
  },
  "5175": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the coffee maker?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to the dining room and next to the livingroom."
  },
  "5176": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bush look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:green, alive, little"
  },
  "5177": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bush?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bush is set in the white flowerpot above the white table."
  },
  "5178": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bush in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bush is in the kitchen."
  },
  "5179": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bush?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to the living room and the dining room."
  },
  "5180": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, small, gray"
  },
  "5181": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a table, next to a picture"
  },
  "5182": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in the corner of a wide bedroom."
  },
  "5183": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is next to a bashroom and there is a garden outside."
  },
  "5184": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A purple, fabric, deck chair."
  },
  "5185": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:A bed near the chair. The chair faces the window."
  },
  "5186": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in a bedroom."
  },
  "5187": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:Behind the chair is the study."
  },
  "5188": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:crooked,orange and white,metal"
  },
  "5189": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the shell,in front of the glowing advertising board and behind a piece of white cloth "
  },
  "5190": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is set in the lobby."
  },
  "5191": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is in front of the reception and opposite to the food bar."
  },
  "5192": {
    "question": "Question:what does the glass cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:glass; tall; black top."
  },
  "5193": {
    "question": "Question:where is the glass cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of a billboard; beside the glass door;"
  },
  "5194": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the glass cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the left of the door."
  },
  "5195": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the glass cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:a recieption of the bath center;"
  },
  "5196": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black and white,metal,cuboid\t"
  },
  "5197": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:in the third position of the left side of the room,under the table,near the foot of a chair"
  },
  "5198": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in a big shared office owning the number of 363."
  },
  "5199": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is along the road to the stairs of the exit and around the corner of a junction of three corridors."
  },
  "5200": {
    "question": "Question:what does the potted plant look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:tall, green, woody"
  },
  "5201": {
    "question": "Question:where is the potted plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a counter, near a water dispenser"
  },
  "5202": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the potted plant in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is put in the corner of a gymnasium."
  },
  "5203": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the potted plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area has a large swimming pool and a treadmill."
  },
  "5204": {
    "question": "Question:what does the windows look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, woody and latticed by iron"
  },
  "5205": {
    "question": "Question:where is the windows?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the wall facing the door and next to the bed."
  },
  "5206": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the windows in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a bedroom on the second floor."
  },
  "5207": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the windows?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is facing the stairs."
  },
  "5208": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cylindrical, plastic and white"
  },
  "5209": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to the window and on a cabinet."
  },
  "5210": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:\nIt is in a chatting room on the first floor."
  },
  "5211": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chatting room is next to the hall."
  },
  "5212": {
    "question": "Question:what does the box look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White, papery and ternary."
  },
  "5213": {
    "question": "Question:where is the box?",
    "answer": "Answer:These boxes is between a ladder and a clutter."
  },
  "5214": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the box in?",
    "answer": "Answer:These boxes is in a utility room."
  },
  "5215": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the box?",
    "answer": "Answer:The room connects with a big living room and leads to a small bedroom via a ladder."
  },
  "5216": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is tiled, large and white."
  },
  "5217": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:A bottle of flowers and some fruits were placed on the table."
  },
  "5218": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is in the kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "5219": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is under the flowers and the pool."
  },
  "5220": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is white, ceramic and large."
  },
  "5221": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is beside the chair and under the lamp."
  },
  "5222": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is on the ground floor kitchen."
  },
  "5223": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:A bottle of flowers and some fruits were placed on the table."
  },
  "5224": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is white, large and rectangular."
  },
  "5225": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is under the flowers and the pool."
  },
  "5226": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is in the kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "5227": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is beside the chair and under the lamp."
  },
  "5228": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is tiled, large and white."
  },
  "5229": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:A bottle of flowers and some fruits were placed on the table."
  },
  "5230": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is in the kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "5231": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is under the flowers and the pool."
  },
  "5232": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is white, ceramic and large."
  },
  "5233": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is beside the chair and under the lamp."
  },
  "5234": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is on the ground floor kitchen."
  },
  "5235": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:A bottle of flowers and some fruits were placed on the table."
  },
  "5236": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is white, large and rectangular."
  },
  "5237": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is under the flowers and the pool."
  },
  "5238": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is in the kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "5239": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is beside the chair and under the lamp."
  },
  "5240": {
    "question": "Question:what does the tap look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, iron "
  },
  "5241": {
    "question": "Question:where is the tap?",
    "answer": "Answer: Below the tap is a cabinet, and it face another big cabinet. There is a mirror right above it."
  },
  "5242": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the tap in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is installed on a small washing room."
  },
  "5243": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the tap?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washing room is built in a small bright bedroom which has the main bedroom on one side and the laundry on the other."
  },
  "5244": {
    "question": "Question:what does the door look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:An old wooden door with metal bolt."
  },
  "5245": {
    "question": "Question:where is the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is just next to the stairway and near a stove."
  },
  "5246": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the door in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is mounted in the wall and faces the narrow side of a red carpet."
  },
  "5247": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a wooden door."
  },
  "5248": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:bright, wall-mounted, rectangular"
  },
  "5249": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:hung on the wall, above the mirror"
  },
  "5250": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the bathroom."
  },
  "5251": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is in a corner which is next to the dining room."
  },
  "5252": {
    "question": "Question:what does the towel look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:made of cloth, yellow,soft"
  },
  "5253": {
    "question": "Question:where is the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's hang on a rack and next to a wardrobe."
  },
  "5254": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the towel in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a  laundry room on the first floor"
  },
  "5255": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:the laundry room is in the washroom,which is near a corridor and a rest room"
  },
  "5256": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Wooden, brown, square"
  },
  "5257": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is on the table with two sofas next to it with green plants"
  },
  "5258": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Vase in the balcony"
  },
  "5259": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:Vase near living room"
  },
  "5260": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Wooden, brown, square"
  },
  "5261": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is on the table with two sofas next to it with green plants"
  },
  "5262": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Vase in the balcony"
  },
  "5263": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:Vase near living room"
  },
  "5264": {
    "question": "Question:what does the flower look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:green and purple,wooden,with long stems"
  },
  "5265": {
    "question": "Question:where is the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the counter,on the right side of the box filled with cards and in front of an exit."
  },
  "5266": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the flower in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is in the reception."
  },
  "5267": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:The reception is opposite to the entrance,in front of the resting area and the food bar."
  },
  "5268": {
    "question": "Question:what does the loudspeaker box look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Black, cuboid, metal."
  },
  "5269": {
    "question": "Question:where is the loudspeaker box?",
    "answer": "Answer:The box is near a table with a green top, on top of a box, against the wall."
  },
  "5270": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the loudspeaker box in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The box is set in the hall."
  },
  "5271": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the loudspeaker box?",
    "answer": "Answer:The box is placed near a conference room and the gate."
  },
  "5272": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A woody, yellow deck chair."
  },
  "5273": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is next to a small table and another chair."
  },
  "5274": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in the outdoor."
  },
  "5275": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair faces a big pool and next to a small pool. "
  },
  "5276": {
    "question": "Question:what does the toilet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White, small and clean."
  },
  "5277": {
    "question": "Question:where is the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The toilet is close to the mirror and the sink."
  },
  "5278": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the toilet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The toilet is in the toilet."
  },
  "5279": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The toilet is close to the bedroom and bathroom."
  },
  "5280": {
    "question": "Question:what does the recliner look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The recliner is long, leather and brown."
  },
  "5281": {
    "question": "Question:where is the recliner?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a television besides and some pillows on the recliner."
  },
  "5282": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the recliner in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The recliner is placed in the corner of the bedroom next to the balcony."
  },
  "5283": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the recliner?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a big bed and painting in the bedroom."
  },
  "5284": {
    "question": "Question:what does the book look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown, papery, thin"
  },
  "5285": {
    "question": "Question:where is the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the stairs, on the second floor of the bookshelf"
  },
  "5286": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the book in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The book is set on the corridor."
  },
  "5287": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:The corridor is facing the stairs and on the second floor."
  },
  "5288": {
    "question": "Question:what does the light bulb look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:transparent,globular,fragile"
  },
  "5289": {
    "question": "Question:where is the light bulb?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's above a long white table and 2 balls."
  },
  "5290": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the light bulb in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a kitchen on the second floor."
  },
  "5291": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the light bulb?",
    "answer": "Answer:the kitchen is near a living room and open-balcony."
  },
  "5292": {
    "question": "Question:what does the drawer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white; wide; glossy;"
  },
  "5293": {
    "question": "Question:where is the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:opposite a brown cabinet; below a sink;"
  },
  "5294": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the drawer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:against the wall on the left side of the door."
  },
  "5295": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:a long room equipped with a shower cubicle."
  },
  "5296": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, wooden and metallic, brown"
  },
  "5297": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:under the big table, in front of the stairs, among four stools and third from left"
  },
  "5298": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is set in the middle of the kitchen."
  },
  "5299": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is on the third floor, next to the balcony and dining, facing the stairs."
  },
  "5300": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cylindrical, blue, graceful"
  },
  "5301": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the blue bed and another lamp with the same color and shape, near the black wall painting"
  },
  "5302": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is in the bedroom."
  },
  "5303": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is next to the stairs and behind the blue wall painting."
  },
  "5304": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, brown, middle"
  },
  "5305": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the door, under the cabinet, there is a coffee machine on it"
  },
  "5306": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is set in the bright kitchen."
  },
  "5307": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is on the first floor and next to the dining room."
  },
  "5308": {
    "question": "Question:what does the shower look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:metal, circle, it has several holes."
  },
  "5309": {
    "question": "Question:where is the shower?",
    "answer": "Answer:A switch under it. Another shower opposite to it."
  },
  "5310": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the shower in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The shower is in a shower room."
  },
  "5311": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the shower?",
    "answer": "Answer:Near the shower is the bathroom."
  },
  "5312": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Wooden, square and clean."
  },
  "5313": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is by the wall with a telephone on it."
  },
  "5314": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is in the living room."
  },
  "5315": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is close to the bedroom and the balcony."
  },
  "5316": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is wooden, large and white."
  },
  "5317": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is under the table and to the right of the towel."
  },
  "5318": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is in the kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "5319": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is under the table and to the right of the towel."
  },
  "5320": {
    "question": "Question:what does the flowerpot look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, ceramic, big"
  },
  "5321": {
    "question": "Question:where is the flowerpot?",
    "answer": "Answer:below a stairs, next to a wall"
  },
  "5322": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the flowerpot in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flowerpot is placed in a staircase."
  },
  "5323": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the flowerpot?",
    "answer": "Answer:The staircase is facing a big and bright living room and there is a corridor between them."
  },
  "5324": {
    "question": "Question:what does the curtain look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:pray, fabric, big"
  },
  "5325": {
    "question": "Question:where is the curtain?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the window, next to the dining table"
  },
  "5326": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the curtain in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the dining room."
  },
  "5327": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the curtain?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the living room and the kitchen."
  },
  "5328": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bookcase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Cuboid, black and thin."
  },
  "5329": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bookcase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bookcase is next to a electronic keyboard and opposite to a lamp and a telephone."
  },
  "5330": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bookcase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bookcase is in a living room."
  },
  "5331": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bookcase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bookcase is near a bedroom."
  },
  "5332": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Glass, transparent, cylindrical"
  },
  "5333": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase was placed on a table with white flowers, an ornament next to it, and a mirror at the back"
  },
  "5334": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Vase In the corridor opposite the stairs"
  },
  "5335": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:vase Connect the living room and yard"
  },
  "5336": {
    "question": "Question:what does the keyboard look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:metal,rectangle,black,"
  },
  "5337": {
    "question": "Question:where is the keyboard?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of the screen,between the mouse and a water bottle, on the white desk"
  },
  "5338": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the keyboard in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The keyboard is in the number 366 office where there is a map on its wall."
  },
  "5339": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the keyboard?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is next to a relax area with sofa in it and connects to a road leading to the tea room and locker room.\n"
  },
  "5340": {
    "question": "Question:what does the dustbin look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black,plastic,cuboid"
  },
  "5341": {
    "question": "Question:where is the dustbin?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the left side of the chair and counter,in front of a door,on the rigth of the billboard"
  },
  "5342": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the dustbin in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The dustbin is in the reception."
  },
  "5343": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the dustbin?",
    "answer": "Answer:The reception is opposite to the entrance and in front of the food bar."
  },
  "5344": {
    "question": "Question:what does the switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, plastic, rectangular"
  },
  "5345": {
    "question": "Question:where is the switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:in fornt of a shelf, next to a table"
  },
  "5346": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The switch is on the wall in a bedroom."
  },
  "5347": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area has a bed and a table next to the bed. "
  },
  "5348": {
    "question": "Question:what does the towel look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Brown, cotton and spotted"
  },
  "5349": {
    "question": "Question:where is the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is hanging on the iron ring above the sink."
  },
  "5350": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the towel in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a restroom on the second floor.\n"
  },
  "5351": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The restroom is on the life side of the stairs."
  },
  "5352": {
    "question": "Question:what does the door look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:woody, tall, opaque"
  },
  "5353": {
    "question": "Question:where is the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of a table, near a chair "
  },
  "5354": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the door in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The door is located in a study."
  },
  "5355": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:The study has some shelves and it has two chairs."
  },
  "5356": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:gray, hairy, retangular"
  },
  "5357": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the carpet, behind the table, next to the stairs"
  },
  "5358": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is located in a bright livingroom."
  },
  "5359": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The livingroom is on the third floor, beside the kitchen and next to the stairs."
  },
  "5360": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bookcase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soild, big and brown."
  },
  "5361": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bookcase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bookcase is near a brown mirror and a black fitness equipment."
  },
  "5362": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bookcase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bookcase is in a bedroom."
  },
  "5363": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bookcase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bookcase is near a toilet and a corridor."
  },
  "5364": {
    "question": "Question:what does the Laundry bucket look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:gray,small,plastic"
  },
  "5365": {
    "question": "Question:where is the Laundry bucket?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to wash machines and a laundry door."
  },
  "5366": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the Laundry bucket in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a laundry room on the second floor."
  },
  "5367": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the Laundry bucket?",
    "answer": "Answer:the laundry room is near a corridor and a bedroom."
  },
  "5368": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a white, square sofa chair filled with cotton.\n"
  },
  "5369": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a stool and reading lamp beside it.\n"
  },
  "5370": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in a living room."
  },
  "5371": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's beside a kitchen."
  },
  "5372": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white,slender and metal."
  },
  "5373": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is on the table, beside the sofa."
  },
  "5374": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is in the living room."
  },
  "5375": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is close to the toilet and bedroom"
  },
  "5376": {
    "question": "Question:what does the printer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black and white,metal,gaint"
  },
  "5377": {
    "question": "Question:where is the printer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The printer is between two dustbins , under a lamp tube and opposite to a door with a sign \"no entry\"."
  },
  "5378": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the printer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The printer is set at the corner a tea room at the end of the corridor."
  },
  "5379": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the printer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The printer is near the stairs of the exit and near an empty office."
  },
  "5380": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pillow look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White, cotton and soft"
  },
  "5381": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:The pillows are on the bed, beneath two paintings."
  },
  "5382": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pillow in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The pillows are against the wall and  facing a wardrobe."
  },
  "5383": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:This bedroom is located at the end of the right turn on the second floor, next to another bedroom and a storage room."
  },
  "5384": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cloth chair ,brow ,single sofa "
  },
  "5385": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:there is another same sofa put nearby ,and the target is back facing a white cabinet."
  },
  "5386": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The single sofa is placed close to the glass door ,which is placed near another same sofa in the living room."
  },
  "5387": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a big TV put in the living room ,but without a balcony ."
  },
  "5388": {
    "question": "Question:what does the green plant look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A tall green plant."
  },
  "5389": {
    "question": "Question:where is the green plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is close to a wooden dining table next to a picture,and near a window."
  },
  "5390": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the green plant in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed in the corner of the dining room."
  },
  "5391": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the green plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a stairway and a kitchen."
  },
  "5392": {
    "question": "Question:what does the whiteboard look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Big,rectangular,white"
  },
  "5393": {
    "question": "Question:where is the whiteboard?",
    "answer": "Answer:The whiteboard is set on the ground and near a television."
  },
  "5394": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the whiteboard in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The whiteboard is placed in a  big conference room."
  },
  "5395": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the whiteboard?",
    "answer": "Answer:The whiteboard is set near a smaller conference and next to the hall."
  },
  "5396": {
    "question": "Question:what does the book look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small,rectangle,a green cover and containing a lot of paper"
  },
  "5397": {
    "question": "Question:where is the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:The book is at the corner of the  white table and on the left of the document holder."
  },
  "5398": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the book in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The book is in a small and crowded working office of the number 365 that only has the room for one person working."
  },
  "5399": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is nearly at the end of the corridor and faces the tea room at a slant."
  },
  "5400": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white,ceramic and smooth"
  },
  "5401": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's surrounded by 3 big mirrors and near a painting on the wall"
  },
  "5402": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's located in the washroom on the first floor"
  },
  "5403": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:the washroom is next to a bedroom which is near the corridor"
  },
  "5404": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:crooked,white and metal"
  },
  "5405": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the right of a green pencil-box,at the right edge of the desk with a orange magazine on it"
  },
  "5406": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is in a small office."
  },
  "5407": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is at the corner of a junction of three roads and next to the corridor door."
  },
  "5408": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Red, small, woody."
  },
  "5409": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a white desk next to  the  chairs and a picture next to  them."
  },
  "5410": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chairs  is set on the  corner of a small room with  a red carpet."
  },
  "5411": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area has two  white desks and lots of red chairs."
  },
  "5412": {
    "question": "Question:what does the dustbin look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:plastic,black,cylindrical"
  },
  "5413": {
    "question": "Question:where is the dustbin?",
    "answer": "Answer:under the window, on the left side of the mirror and behind the sofa"
  },
  "5414": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the dustbin in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the vast rest area."
  },
  "5415": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the dustbin?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is on the left side of the number 05 meeting room and behind the restaurant."
  },
  "5416": {
    "question": "Question:what does the switches look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:square, plastic, white"
  },
  "5417": {
    "question": "Question:where is the switches?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the wall, facing the stairs"
  },
  "5418": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the switches in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The switches are set in the staircase."
  },
  "5419": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the switches?",
    "answer": "Answer:The staircase is on the first floor and next to the livingroom."
  },
  "5420": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, gray, cotton"
  },
  "5421": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:You can see a cabinet on it's left and a paint above it."
  },
  "5422": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is put on the first floor where face the garden."
  },
  "5423": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:You can see a reception area next here, where the stairs beside."
  },
  "5424": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle, long and red"
  },
  "5425": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed on the carpet and in front of the window."
  },
  "5426": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is at the left side of the living room on the first floor."
  },
  "5427": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is at the left side of the gate."
  },
  "5428": {
    "question": "Question:what does the washbasin look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, small, porcelain"
  },
  "5429": {
    "question": "Question:where is the washbasin?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a porcelain, next to boxes"
  },
  "5430": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the washbasin in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washbasin is settled in the corner of a bedroom. "
  },
  "5431": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the washbasin?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is next to the corridor on the second floor with a fireplace and a bathroom. "
  },
  "5432": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:square, silver"
  },
  "5433": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's right above to a mirror and a sink."
  },
  "5434": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It was installed in the toilet in the workshop."
  },
  "5435": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:Work room face the dinning room."
  },
  "5436": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown,wooden,soft"
  },
  "5437": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a small round table with a lamp and it's under a painting"
  },
  "5438": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it is located on the corridor on the first floor and it's in front of a stair"
  },
  "5439": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:the corridor is near the dining room \u3001kitchen and bedroom"
  },
  "5440": {
    "question": "Question:what does the clock look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A white clock with yellow metal frame and yellow hands."
  },
  "5441": {
    "question": "Question:where is the clock?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is hung under a black metal case and is over a wooden desk."
  },
  "5442": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the clock in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the dinging room, far near an upstair and on the left of a wooden door."
  },
  "5443": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the clock?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a table."
  },
  "5444": {
    "question": "Question:what does the post-it note look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small,thin, square,yellow"
  },
  "5445": {
    "question": "Question:where is the post-it note?",
    "answer": "Answer:The post-it note is on the wall that is on the left side of the gate,above the document folder and the pen container."
  },
  "5446": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the post-it note in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in a small two person office full of paper and its number is 349."
  },
  "5447": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the post-it note?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is along the corridor and opposite to a big empty office and is close to the junction of three corridor."
  },
  "5448": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:stands back facing the front door, cloth sofa, its color is white "
  },
  "5449": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:there are three small pillows put at the corner of the sofa,  and the target is put front facing the big glass door to the balcony "
  },
  "5450": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is put in the big living room, which is back facing the front door and front facing the big glass door to the balcony."
  },
  "5451": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is another big sofa close to the target ,and two same tea tables are put in front of the white sofa,"
  },
  "5452": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Big, soild and black."
  },
  "5453": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is set opposite to a black shutter and a white and brown bed."
  },
  "5454": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is in a bedroom."
  },
  "5455": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is near a bathroom."
  },
  "5456": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Blue, leather and soild."
  },
  "5457": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is on the left side of a red sofa, next to a green bed and near a white telephone."
  },
  "5458": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in a bedroom."
  },
  "5459": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is near a corridor."
  },
  "5460": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white and yellow, big, square"
  },
  "5461": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the carpet, in the middle of two nightstands, next to the window"
  },
  "5462": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is located in a bright bedroom."
  },
  "5463": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is on the second floor, on the left of the stairs and in the central of the corridor."
  },
  "5464": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bottle look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:transparent, glass and fragile."
  },
  "5465": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bottle?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bottle is on the left of a slaver and near a glass bottle."
  },
  "5466": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bottle in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bottle is in a big living room."
  },
  "5467": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bottle?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is next to a dining room and leads to outdoors via a door."
  },
  "5468": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown ,stand by a small table,it's a cloth chair "
  },
  "5469": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:the chair is back facing the TV cabinet ,a red carpet is put on the front ground"
  },
  "5470": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The single sofa is put bakc facing the wooden TV cabinet which is close to the glass door in the living room."
  },
  "5471": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are many different size sofas put in the living room which attached a big TV ,but without a balcony."
  },
  "5472": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is h-shaped, soild and wooden and leather."
  },
  "5473": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is the fourth one in a row of chairs from right to left while facing to the chairs, behind a red leather sofa and opposite to a brown wooden desk."
  },
  "5474": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in a reception room on the first floor."
  },
  "5475": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is near a porch."
  },
  "5476": {
    "question": "Question:what does the desk look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Woody, brown, short."
  },
  "5477": {
    "question": "Question:where is the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are some red cabinets near the desk."
  },
  "5478": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the desk in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The desk is set on the corridor of the hall."
  },
  "5479": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area  is  located on the corner of the hall."
  },
  "5480": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, cloth, white"
  },
  "5481": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:around the table, on the carprt, facing the washroom and first from left"
  },
  "5482": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set in the bright dining room."
  },
  "5483": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The dining room is on the third floor, next to the balcony and kitchen."
  },
  "5484": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A medium-sized bed with white sheets and no nightstands."
  },
  "5485": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a glass wall and a white lamp."
  },
  "5486": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a relatively small bedroom."
  },
  "5487": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near another small bedroom."
  },
  "5488": {
    "question": "Question:what does the book look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black and yellow,thick"
  },
  "5489": {
    "question": "Question:where is the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the shell,on the left of a pink tray and under the display"
  },
  "5490": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the book in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a small meeting room."
  },
  "5491": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:The meeting room is opposite to the gate of a big meeting room and next to a room that is forbidden to entry."
  },
  "5492": {
    "question": "Question:what does the toilet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The toilet is oval, white and ceramic."
  },
  "5493": {
    "question": "Question:where is the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The toilet is next to the smoking paper and in the corner."
  },
  "5494": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the toilet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The toilet is in the bathroom."
  },
  "5495": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The toilet is next to the smoking paper and in the corner."
  },
  "5496": {
    "question": "Question:what does the closestool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A small white closetool."
  },
  "5497": {
    "question": "Question:where is the closestool?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near the shower place and the washstand."
  },
  "5498": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the closestool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a restroom on the second floor,which is also in a bedroom."
  },
  "5499": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the closestool?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a bedroom."
  },
  "5500": {
    "question": "Question:what does the fireplace look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:steel\uff0cflowered and inbeded into the wall"
  },
  "5501": {
    "question": "Question:where is the fireplace?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's near a switch and under the television"
  },
  "5502": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the fireplace in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's is inbeded into the middle of the wall"
  },
  "5503": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the fireplace?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a corridor outside the room"
  },
  "5504": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black and brown, rectangle, small"
  },
  "5505": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's put on a table.  it's on the right side of the bed."
  },
  "5506": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's put in a big and  bright main bedroom."
  },
  "5507": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The master bedroom faces the balcony. Right below the room is the swimming pool."
  },
  "5508": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cloth, rectangular, white"
  },
  "5509": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of a picture, next to a sofa"
  },
  "5510": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is settled in a small living facing a big living room on the first floor."
  },
  "5511": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living is next to a corridor and is connected with a small dining room."
  },
  "5512": {
    "question": "Question:what does the washbasin look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, rectangular, white"
  },
  "5513": {
    "question": "Question:where is the washbasin?",
    "answer": "Answer:face a glass door, in front of a mirror"
  },
  "5514": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the washbasin in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washbasin is in the bathroom."
  },
  "5515": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the washbasin?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathrooom is next to the cloakroom in the master bedroom."
  },
  "5516": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black,hard and elegant"
  },
  "5517": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a stony and round table and a same kind of chari"
  },
  "5518": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it is located in the balcony on the second floor"
  },
  "5519": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The balcony is next to a study room and a garden "
  },
  "5520": {
    "question": "Question:what does the TV look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Black, large, appliance"
  },
  "5521": {
    "question": "Question:where is the TV?",
    "answer": "Answer:TV has a potted plant and a Spider-Man model to the left and right"
  },
  "5522": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the TV in?",
    "answer": "Answer:TV hangs on the wall of the living room"
  },
  "5523": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the TV?",
    "answer": "Answer:TV is close to the balcony"
  },
  "5524": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A white clean porcelain sink. "
  },
  "5525": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is under a mirror and on a white desk."
  },
  "5526": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a dark toilet."
  },
  "5527": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a bedroom."
  },
  "5528": {
    "question": "Question:what does the screen look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big and thin,black,metal,with a white note on it"
  },
  "5529": {
    "question": "Question:where is the screen?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the desk between the document holder and a white machine,in front of a white board and behind a keyboard"
  },
  "5530": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the screen in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The screen is in a small-sized office."
  },
  "5531": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the screen?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is next to a relax area and connects to a road leading to the tea room and locker room."
  },
  "5532": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Leopard print, square, leather."
  },
  "5533": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa has grey plush pillows and black curtains at the back."
  },
  "5534": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in the living room."
  },
  "5535": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is next to the door, near the open-air balcony."
  },
  "5536": {
    "question": "Question:what does the oven look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big,metal,black and white"
  },
  "5537": {
    "question": "Question:where is the oven?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a sink and in a table."
  },
  "5538": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the oven in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a kitchen on the second floor."
  },
  "5539": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the oven?",
    "answer": "Answer:the kitchen is near a living room and a open-balcony"
  },
  "5540": {
    "question": "Question:what does the massage bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, soft, rectangular"
  },
  "5541": {
    "question": "Question:where is the massage bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:between two massage beds, near a swimming pool"
  },
  "5542": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the massage bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The massage bed is located in a gymnasium."
  },
  "5543": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the massage bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a treadmill and a spinning bike in this gymnasium."
  },
  "5544": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:deep brown,soft,wide"
  },
  "5545": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:between two small chairs, in front of a book shelf and near a short desk"
  },
  "5546": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in a big restaurant."
  },
  "5547": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The restaurant is opposite to the reception counter and next to the reading area."
  },
  "5548": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:glass, wall-mounted, circular"
  },
  "5549": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:above the paintings, hung on the wall"
  },
  "5550": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the children's bedroom."
  },
  "5551": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the study and the bathroom."
  },
  "5552": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Umbelliform, soild and white and brassy."
  },
  "5553": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is set on the right side of a green bed and a white telephone."
  },
  "5554": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is in a bedroom."
  },
  "5555": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is near a corridor and a toilet."
  },
  "5556": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Woody, rectangular ,red."
  },
  "5557": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are  four chairs with the same shape, material on its right .There are four chairs with the same shape, material opposite to it."
  },
  "5558": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set on one side of the corridor via the altar."
  },
  "5559": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area has a fan and lots of benches on each side of the corridor ."
  },
  "5560": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cylinder, cloth, big"
  },
  "5561": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a bed, on a table"
  },
  "5562": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is placed in the corner of a bedroom."
  },
  "5563": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is next to a bashroom on the first floor."
  },
  "5564": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Medium size, beige and wooden."
  },
  "5565": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set between two long beige sofas, between two windows."
  },
  "5566": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is at the corner of a lounge."
  },
  "5567": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is near a living room and a white corridor."
  },
  "5568": {
    "question": "Question:what does the remote control look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A small black square remote control."
  },
  "5569": {
    "question": "Question:where is the remote control?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on the desk which is beside the bed and is near a lamp."
  },
  "5570": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the remote control in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed in a bedroom."
  },
  "5571": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the remote control?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a toilet and near the entrance of the bedroom."
  },
  "5572": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Big, circle, embedded pool"
  },
  "5573": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pool?",
    "answer": "Answer:A small pool is next to it. A table with several chairs next to it."
  },
  "5574": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The pool is outside."
  },
  "5575": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The pool is next to the corridor."
  },
  "5576": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Big, circle, embedded pool"
  },
  "5577": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pool?",
    "answer": "Answer:A small pool is next to it. A table with several chairs next to it."
  },
  "5578": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The pool is outside."
  },
  "5579": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The pool is next to the corridor."
  },
  "5580": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a white, large, square cabinet."
  },
  "5581": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is above a cabinet, beside a stove."
  },
  "5582": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in the dining room."
  },
  "5583": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to a study and kitchen."
  },
  "5584": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bath look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Yellow, porcelainous and soild."
  },
  "5585": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bath?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bath is under the metal water pipe and it has two pipe switches."
  },
  "5586": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bath in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bath is in a bathroom."
  },
  "5587": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bath?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bath is near a corridor, on the opposite side of a narrow empty room which has two wooden doors."
  },
  "5588": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:gray, porcelain"
  },
  "5589": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:It has a display on the left, a tap and a sink on the right."
  },
  "5590": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's put in a  open kitchen."
  },
  "5591": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:Here you can see the swimming pool, reception area and a wicket."
  },
  "5592": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big,colorless,framed"
  },
  "5593": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to the switch and in opposite of the door"
  },
  "5594": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's hanged on the wall of corridor"
  },
  "5595": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:there is a bedroom in opposite"
  },
  "5596": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden,short,brown"
  },
  "5597": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:in the middle among the sofas,in front of the window"
  },
  "5598": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is at the end of a corridor and in the rest area."
  },
  "5599": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is opposite to the locker room and the tea room,sharing a corridor to an exit gate and at a corner."
  },
  "5600": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cotton, white, small"
  },
  "5601": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is an identical sofa on its right, two pillows are put on it."
  },
  "5602": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's put in the reception area where next to the stairs."
  },
  "5603": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's next to the garden. "
  },
  "5604": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pillow look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle, blue and made by linen"
  },
  "5605": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on the bed close to the two cabinets."
  },
  "5606": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pillow in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a bedroom on the second floor."
  },
  "5607": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is facing the stairs."
  },
  "5608": {
    "question": "Question:what does the telephone look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soild, metal and plastic and black."
  },
  "5609": {
    "question": "Question:where is the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:The telephone is set below a black television and near a red sofa and a blue sofa."
  },
  "5610": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the telephone in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The telephone is in a bedroom."
  },
  "5611": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:The telephone is near a corridor."
  },
  "5612": {
    "question": "Question:what does the oven look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle, steel and grey"
  },
  "5613": {
    "question": "Question:where is the oven?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is embedded in the wall next to the door and the cabinet."
  },
  "5614": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the oven in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "5615": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the oven?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to the chatting room and the door."
  },
  "5616": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White, porcelain and rounded."
  },
  "5617": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is near a towel and in front of a big mirror."
  },
  "5618": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is in a bathroom."
  },
  "5619": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area connects with a bedroom and near a toilet."
  },
  "5620": {
    "question": "Question:what does the counter look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:metal,argent,long and large"
  },
  "5621": {
    "question": "Question:where is the counter?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the left of a long wooden desk and towards the corridor door"
  },
  "5622": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the counter in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The counter is in a food bar."
  },
  "5623": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the counter?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bar is in front of the vast resting area and towards the service desk."
  },
  "5624": {
    "question": "Question:what does the poster look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The poster is big, square and black."
  },
  "5625": {
    "question": "Question:where is the poster?",
    "answer": "Answer:The poster is placed below the television next to the wardrobe."
  },
  "5626": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the poster in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The poster is placed below the television next to the wardrobe."
  },
  "5627": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the poster?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are two tables, sofa and recliner in the room."
  },
  "5628": {
    "question": "Question:what does the printer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Big,white,metal.\n"
  },
  "5629": {
    "question": "Question:where is the printer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The printer is set behind a yellow table surrounded by four chairs ,between two walls."
  },
  "5630": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the printer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The printer is placed in the hall."
  },
  "5631": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the printer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The printer is set near a small conference room and a big conference room ."
  },
  "5632": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:hard,white,wide,oblong"
  },
  "5633": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to two glass walls,in front of a huge pillar"
  },
  "5634": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is in a small room that has a number of 307."
  },
  "5635": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The room is along the road connecting the public sofas and the locker room and the tea room,and is opposite to a big office full of documents."
  },
  "5636": {
    "question": "Question:what does the shower look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:grey, round and steel"
  },
  "5637": {
    "question": "Question:where is the shower?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is hanging on the wall next to the bathtub and window."
  },
  "5638": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the shower in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a restroom on the first floor."
  },
  "5639": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the shower?",
    "answer": "Answer:The restroom is in the bedroom which is at the right turn of the gate."
  },
  "5640": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Rectangular, woody, red."
  },
  "5641": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is  short desk near  the chair and a  picture near it."
  },
  "5642": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The  chair is set at the  corner of the room and  close to the  wall."
  },
  "5643": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:This  area  has  a  white  desk and lots of  red  chair."
  },
  "5644": {
    "question": "Question:what does the towel look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:square, cloth, white"
  },
  "5645": {
    "question": "Question:where is the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the handle , above the toilet"
  },
  "5646": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the towel in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is set in the washroom."
  },
  "5647": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washroom is inside the bedroom, which is on the second floor and on the left of the corridor when go upstairs."
  },
  "5648": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:gray, cloth, short"
  },
  "5649": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the door, facing the bed, next to the picture"
  },
  "5650": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chaire is set in the bright bedroom."
  },
  "5651": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is on the second floor, in the end of the corridor and on the left of the corridor when up to second floor."
  },
  "5652": {
    "question": "Question:what does the closestool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white; porcelain; closed;"
  },
  "5653": {
    "question": "Question:where is the closestool?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the right side of the sink;towards the doors of the restroom and the changing room."
  },
  "5654": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the closestool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:deep inside the washroom;"
  },
  "5655": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the closestool?",
    "answer": "Answer:belongs to a changing room with two identical closets;"
  },
  "5656": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:middle size,like a umbrella,metal"
  },
  "5657": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's on a bedside table and next to a double bed.it's in the corner of a bedroom"
  },
  "5658": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a bedroom on the first floor"
  },
  "5659": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:the bedroom has a washroom and is in the end of a corridor which is near another bedroom   and rest room"
  },
  "5660": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, tall, woody"
  },
  "5661": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the woody doors and the mirror"
  },
  "5662": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the bedroom"
  },
  "5663": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the corridor and another bedroom."
  },
  "5664": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Red chair with a hairy cushion."
  },
  "5665": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a round table with a few bottles of wine near the chair and glass doors behind of it. "
  },
  "5666": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set in a big and bright living room."
  },
  "5667": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set next to a balcony and in front of two small rooms."
  },
  "5668": {
    "question": "Question:what does the door look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Woody, white and rectangle"
  },
  "5669": {
    "question": "Question:where is the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed beside a restroom at the end of the hall."
  },
  "5670": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the door in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed in a bedroom and at the end of the left turn behind the stairs."
  },
  "5671": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is at the end of the left turn behind the stairs."
  },
  "5672": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:grey, wooden and oblong."
  },
  "5673": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is under the many books and near a black sofa."
  },
  "5674": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is in a big living room."
  },
  "5675": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is next to a dining room and leads to outdoors via a door."
  },
  "5676": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cupboard look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:yellow, hanged and woody"
  },
  "5677": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cupboard?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is above the cabinet and facing the table."
  },
  "5678": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cupboard in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "5679": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cupboard?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to the chatting room and the door."
  },
  "5680": {
    "question": "Question:what does the drawer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:woody, white and black"
  },
  "5681": {
    "question": "Question:where is the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:A bed is next to the drawer. A chair is near the drawer. At the right of the drawer are three pillows."
  },
  "5682": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the drawer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a bedroom."
  },
  "5683": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is set faces the window."
  },
  "5684": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Rectangular, big and transparent."
  },
  "5685": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is surrounded by six orange chairs and near a big table."
  },
  "5686": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is in a rest room."
  },
  "5687": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is near a kitchen and a dining room."
  },
  "5688": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stairs look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, woody, burly wood"
  },
  "5689": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stairs?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the stair armrest, next to the white and rough wall"
  },
  "5690": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stairs in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the staircase."
  },
  "5691": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stairs?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the kitchen and the garden."
  },
  "5692": {
    "question": "Question:what does the hand sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:silvery, big, metal"
  },
  "5693": {
    "question": "Question:where is the hand sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:above a drawer, next to a bowl"
  },
  "5694": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the hand sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The hank sink is settled in the center of a kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "5695": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the hand sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is facing a big dining room and there is a cloakroom upstairs."
  },
  "5696": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A large black wooden cabinet with metal handles."
  },
  "5697": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is over two washing machines and near another smaller cabinet."
  },
  "5698": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a laundry room."
  },
  "5699": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a shelf and a bedroom."
  },
  "5700": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Gray, cuboid and big."
  },
  "5701": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is settled on the right side of a induction cooker and near a big table with a metal sink."
  },
  "5702": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is set in a kitchen."
  },
  "5703": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is near a rest room and a corridor."
  },
  "5704": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bottle look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:transparent, glass"
  },
  "5705": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bottle?",
    "answer": "Answer:It has two plants on the left and a display on the right."
  },
  "5706": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bottle in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's put in a  open kitchen."
  },
  "5707": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bottle?",
    "answer": "Answer:Here you can see the swimming pool, reception area and a wicket."
  },
  "5708": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mural look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:colorful, rectangular, large"
  },
  "5709": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mural?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the wall, near two massage beds"
  },
  "5710": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mural in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mural is put on the wall in a bedroom."
  },
  "5711": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mural?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area connects with a gymnasium and has some decorations."
  },
  "5712": {
    "question": "Question:what does the towel look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black, hairy, rectangular"
  },
  "5713": {
    "question": "Question:where is the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the white washbasin and the carbinet, face a door"
  },
  "5714": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the towel in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is in the bathroom."
  },
  "5715": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathroom is next to the stairs and six bedrooms on the third floor."
  },
  "5716": {
    "question": "Question:what does the towel look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is rectangular, soft and white."
  },
  "5717": {
    "question": "Question:where is the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is in the middle of the two pools."
  },
  "5718": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the towel in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is inside the bedroom bathroom."
  },
  "5719": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is in the middle of the two pools."
  },
  "5720": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:golden,reflective,smooth"
  },
  "5721": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's above a washbasin and near a window"
  },
  "5722": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a washroom on the first floor"
  },
  "5723": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:the washroom is next to a bedroom which is near a corridor"
  },
  "5724": {
    "question": "Question:what does the deck chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:long; white cushions; with armrests;"
  },
  "5725": {
    "question": "Question:where is the deck chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a wall with two paintings; on the left of a black end table;"
  },
  "5726": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the deck chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:at the corner of this hall;"
  },
  "5727": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the deck chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:a small hall with three similar deck chais."
  },
  "5728": {
    "question": "Question:what does the plant look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:green, "
  },
  "5729": {
    "question": "Question:where is the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's put on a black table, It's facing the TV and a big sofa behind,"
  },
  "5730": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the plant in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is put on the reception area."
  },
  "5731": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area faces the open kitchen, next to the pool, and dinning table on the other side."
  },
  "5732": {
    "question": "Question:what does the piano look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:huge, woody and brown"
  },
  "5733": {
    "question": "Question:where is the piano?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to a sofa and the stairs."
  },
  "5734": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the piano in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in living roon on the first floor."
  },
  "5735": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the piano?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is the room facing the door."
  },
  "5736": {
    "question": "Question:what does the fruits look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Yellow, pyriform and small."
  },
  "5737": {
    "question": "Question:where is the fruits?",
    "answer": "Answer:The fruits are set on a metal bowl, opposite to a box of paper towel and next to a big gray cabinet."
  },
  "5738": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the fruits in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The fruits are in a kitchen."
  },
  "5739": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the fruits?",
    "answer": "Answer:The fruits are near a dining room."
  },
  "5740": {
    "question": "Question:what does the kattle look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:round, grey and steel"
  },
  "5741": {
    "question": "Question:where is the kattle?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed on a cabinet and above the stove."
  },
  "5742": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the kattle in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "5743": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the kattle?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to the chatting room and the door."
  },
  "5744": {
    "question": "Question:what does the earphone look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Big,white,semicircular"
  },
  "5745": {
    "question": "Question:where is the earphone?",
    "answer": "Answer:The earphone is placed on a yellow table and next to a computer."
  },
  "5746": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the earphone in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The earphone is placed in the hall."
  },
  "5747": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the earphone?",
    "answer": "Answer:The earphone is placed near a big conference room and a tearoom."
  },
  "5748": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:hanged, rectangle and grey"
  },
  "5749": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is hanging on the wall above some towels and next to the door."
  },
  "5750": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a restroom on the second floor."
  },
  "5751": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The restroom is at the left rear corner of the stairs."
  },
  "5752": {
    "question": "Question:what does the desk look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Brown, rectangular and wooden."
  },
  "5753": {
    "question": "Question:where is the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:The desk is in front of a tall mirror with yellow and white border and near a red round leather chair, and it has a glass box containing a sword, two crowns and a staff."
  },
  "5754": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the desk in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The desk is in a reception room."
  },
  "5755": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:The desk is near a porch."
  },
  "5756": {
    "question": "Question:what does the microwave look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black,metal,cuboid"
  },
  "5757": {
    "question": "Question:where is the microwave?",
    "answer": "Answer:above the dustbin,on the desk,on the right of the posters"
  },
  "5758": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the microwave in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The microwave is in the tea room."
  },
  "5759": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the microwave?",
    "answer": "Answer:The room is opposite to the locker,next to the exit and opposite to the resting area."
  },
  "5760": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:round, yellow and woody"
  },
  "5761": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to a table and closest to the door."
  },
  "5762": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a chatting room on the first floor."
  },
  "5763": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chatting room is next to the hall."
  },
  "5764": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Wooden and leather, h-shaped and beige and brown."
  },
  "5765": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is settled next to a square wooden table and near a black television."
  },
  "5766": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in a living room."
  },
  "5767": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is near a corridor."
  },
  "5768": {
    "question": "Question:what does the kettle look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:woody, round and brown"
  },
  "5769": {
    "question": "Question:where is the kettle?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed on a shelf at the left part of the cupboard."
  },
  "5770": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the kettle in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "5771": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the kettle?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to the chatting room and the door."
  },
  "5772": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Red, rectangular,  woody."
  },
  "5773": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are two chairs with the same colour, shape on their right and a white desk near it."
  },
  "5774": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chairs are set close to the wall of the small room."
  },
  "5775": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area is located on a small room with a red  carpet and two white desks."
  },
  "5776": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bowl look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, circle, white"
  },
  "5777": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bowl?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a hand sink, above a drawer"
  },
  "5778": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bowl in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bowl is in a kitchen with wood floor on the first floor."
  },
  "5779": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bowl?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is facing a big dining room and there is a cloakroom upstairs."
  },
  "5780": {
    "question": "Question:what does the keyboard look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle,black,containing lots of bottons"
  },
  "5781": {
    "question": "Question:where is the keyboard?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of a pillow,in front of four screens and on the left of the wooden shelf"
  },
  "5782": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the keyboard in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The keyboard is in a big office."
  },
  "5783": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the keyboard?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is in front of a corridor door,along the road connecting the tea room and the restaurant."
  },
  "5784": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bench look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:long,middle size and stony"
  },
  "5785": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bench?",
    "answer": "Answer:it is next to 2 white stone lions and in front of a flower bed"
  },
  "5786": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bench in?",
    "answer": "Answer:the bench is located in a garden on the second floor"
  },
  "5787": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bench?",
    "answer": "Answer:the garden is near the balcony and the balcony is next to a study room"
  },
  "5788": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Beige and brown, medium size and h-shaped."
  },
  "5789": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set next to a square brown table and near a beige sofa."
  },
  "5790": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in a living room on the first floor."
  },
  "5791": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is near a corridor."
  },
  "5792": {
    "question": "Question:what does the painting look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:ractangle,hanged on the wall,framed"
  },
  "5793": {
    "question": "Question:where is the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's next to the curtain and the door"
  },
  "5794": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the painting in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in front of the bed and the mirror"
  },
  "5795": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:right behind the corridor"
  },
  "5796": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:metallic, brown, big"
  },
  "5797": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the table, next to the window"
  },
  "5798": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is set in the bright kitchen."
  },
  "5799": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is on the first floor and next to the dining room."
  },
  "5800": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cottony, colorful and soft."
  },
  "5801": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a window on the sofa and a black wooden cabinet near the sofa."
  },
  "5802": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is on a small attic, which is on the second floor."
  },
  "5803": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The attic is above the living room, and connects with a staircase."
  },
  "5804": {
    "question": "Question:what does the TV look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Not running, black and large."
  },
  "5805": {
    "question": "Question:where is the TV?",
    "answer": "Answer:The TV is in the cabinet, facing the sofa."
  },
  "5806": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the TV in?",
    "answer": "Answer:TV is set in living room."
  },
  "5807": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the TV?",
    "answer": "Answer:The TV is close to the toilet and bedroom."
  },
  "5808": {
    "question": "Question:what does the flower look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, woody, green, purple and brown"
  },
  "5809": {
    "question": "Question:where is the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front a mirror, on a washbasin"
  },
  "5810": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the flower in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is placed on a washbasin in one side of a washroom."
  },
  "5811": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washroom is behind living room and in front of a dining room."
  },
  "5812": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:tall, filmy, rectangular"
  },
  "5813": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a window, face a bed with two lamps"
  },
  "5814": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is in the bedroom."
  },
  "5815": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is next to the stairs and behind a blue wall painting."
  },
  "5816": {
    "question": "Question:what does the power switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a new row of small square switches."
  },
  "5817": {
    "question": "Question:where is the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is above an exhaust vent and under a light."
  },
  "5818": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the power switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is in a living room.\n"
  },
  "5819": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a clean, tidy and spacious living room.\n"
  },
  "5820": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is wooden, large and white."
  },
  "5821": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is above the table and to the right of the oven."
  },
  "5822": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is in the kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "5823": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is above the table and to the right of the oven."
  },
  "5824": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black and white,metal,cuboid"
  },
  "5825": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:in the first position of the left side of the room,next to two glass walls"
  },
  "5826": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is in a big shared office with the number 363."
  },
  "5827": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is along the road to the stairs of the exit and close to the corner of a junction of three roads."
  },
  "5828": {
    "question": "Question:what does the glass look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, transparent, glass"
  },
  "5829": {
    "question": "Question:where is the glass?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the cabinet, in front of the picture, on the right of the lamp"
  },
  "5830": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the glass in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The glass is set in the spacious livingroom."
  },
  "5831": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the glass?",
    "answer": "Answer:The livingroom is on the first floor and next to the dining room."
  },
  "5832": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Plastic, round, transparent"
  },
  "5833": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is placed on the table with a vase and towel next to it"
  },
  "5834": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Mirror in the toilet"
  },
  "5835": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is a bedroom on one side and a corridor on the other"
  },
  "5836": {
    "question": "Question:what does the box look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Brown,big,cuboid"
  },
  "5837": {
    "question": "Question:where is the box?",
    "answer": "Answer:The box is set under a black board and stand against a wall."
  },
  "5838": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the box in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The box is placed in a tearoom."
  },
  "5839": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the box?",
    "answer": "Answer:The box is set near a reading room and the hall."
  },
  "5840": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Medium size, soild and white."
  },
  "5841": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is near a brown drawer and a white toilet."
  },
  "5842": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is in a toilet."
  },
  "5843": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is near a bedroom and a living room."
  },
  "5844": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, cloth, big"
  },
  "5845": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:on a table, facing a desk"
  },
  "5846": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is settled in a big bathroom on the second floor."
  },
  "5847": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathroom is next to a storeroom and a cloakroom and has a balcony."
  },
  "5848": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pillow look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:pink, quadrate and has four."
  },
  "5849": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:These pillows are on a big bed and near a lamp."
  },
  "5850": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pillow in?",
    "answer": "Answer:These pillows are in a bedroom."
  },
  "5851": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom leads outdoors via a door and connects with a washroom."
  },
  "5852": {
    "question": "Question:what does the potted plant look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:round, small and potted"
  },
  "5853": {
    "question": "Question:where is the potted plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is close to the fence and closest to a door."
  },
  "5854": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the potted plant in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in front of the house."
  },
  "5855": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the potted plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is outside the house and in front of the gate."
  },
  "5856": {
    "question": "Question:what does the painting look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, wall-mounted, blue and yellow"
  },
  "5857": {
    "question": "Question:where is the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:hung on the wall, above the sofa"
  },
  "5858": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the painting in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the living room."
  },
  "5859": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the dining room and the kitchen."
  },
  "5860": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:light brown, ceramic, cylindrical"
  },
  "5861": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the wall, on the wooden floor"
  },
  "5862": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is set on the corner of the stairs."
  },
  "5863": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stairs is facing the kitchen, used to second floor up to third floor."
  },
  "5864": {
    "question": "Question:what does the windows look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:transparent, square, big"
  },
  "5865": {
    "question": "Question:where is the windows?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the bed, facing the door"
  },
  "5866": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the windows in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The windows are located in the bright bedroom."
  },
  "5867": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the windows?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is on the left of the stairs, on the second floor and in the central of the corridor."
  },
  "5868": {
    "question": "Question:what does the fireplace look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:glass, black, big"
  },
  "5869": {
    "question": "Question:where is the fireplace?",
    "answer": "Answer:beside the bed, next to the window"
  },
  "5870": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the fireplace in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The fireplace is on the corner of a warm child-bedroom. "
  },
  "5871": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the fireplace?",
    "answer": "Answer:The child-bedroom is next to the corridor on the second floor with a fireplace and a bathroom."
  },
  "5872": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bush look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:alive, green, long and thin"
  },
  "5873": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bush?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of a wall paining, next to the stairs"
  },
  "5874": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bush in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bush is face the entrance door."
  },
  "5875": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bush?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bush is next to the living room and the dining room."
  },
  "5876": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White, porcelain and rounded."
  },
  "5877": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is in front of a big mirror and under four lights."
  },
  "5878": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is in a bathroom."
  },
  "5879": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area connects with a bedroom and near a toilet."
  },
  "5880": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown,big,made by leather and with three division plates"
  },
  "5881": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the left of a plant,on the right of a table and opposite to a dustbin"
  },
  "5882": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in the vast rest area."
  },
  "5883": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is behind the resaurant and next to a meeting room."
  },
  "5884": {
    "question": "Question:what does the poster look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The poster is big, white and square."
  },
  "5885": {
    "question": "Question:where is the poster?",
    "answer": "Answer:The poster is placed on the opposite of the power switch next to the door."
  },
  "5886": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the poster in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The poster is placed on the opposite of the wall next to the door."
  },
  "5887": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the poster?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are many posters in the corridor."
  },
  "5888": {
    "question": "Question:what does the poster look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The poster is big, white and square."
  },
  "5889": {
    "question": "Question:where is the poster?",
    "answer": "Answer:The poster is placed on the opposite of the power switch next to the door."
  },
  "5890": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the poster in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The poster is placed on the opposite of the wall next to the door."
  },
  "5891": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the poster?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are many posters in the corridor."
  },
  "5892": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stove look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stove is iron, black and rectangular."
  },
  "5893": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stove?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stove is beside the table and drawers."
  },
  "5894": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stove in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stove is in the kitchen on the ground floor."
  },
  "5895": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stove?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stove is beside the table and drawers."
  },
  "5896": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:tall,black,plastic and metal,owning two handrails"
  },
  "5897": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of the third desk on the left side and near the innermost chair"
  },
  "5898": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in a small office for four poeple working in. "
  },
  "5899": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is at the corner of the crossroads and near the tea room and the locker room."
  },
  "5900": {
    "question": "Question:what does the switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, plastic, rectangle"
  },
  "5901": {
    "question": "Question:where is the switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's facing the reception area, and a chair is on its right."
  },
  "5902": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's next to the door to the balcony."
  },
  "5903": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:You can see a reception area next here, where the stairs beside."
  },
  "5904": {
    "question": "Question:what does the painting look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Rectangular, soild and papery."
  },
  "5905": {
    "question": "Question:where is the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is set on the right side of five paintings, near a stair and a brassy switch."
  },
  "5906": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the painting in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is in a corridor."
  },
  "5907": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is near a toilet and a bedroom."
  },
  "5908": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black, rectangular, wood"
  },
  "5909": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a chair, under a lamp"
  },
  "5910": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is in the center of wide and bright study."
  },
  "5911": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The study is next to a bashroom and facing a corridor."
  },
  "5912": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle ,black ,small desk "
  },
  "5913": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a brown chair put under the desk ,and a small porcelain put on the desk "
  },
  "5914": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The desk is put at the corner of the bedroom ,which is close to the glass door."
  },
  "5915": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a small wooden cabinet put at the opposite corner, and the white bed is facing the glass door to balcony."
  },
  "5916": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A brown plastic cabinet on a lattice wall."
  },
  "5917": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is over a sink , faces a shelf and near a picture."
  },
  "5918": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a storage room which is on the ground floor."
  },
  "5919": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near the dining hall."
  },
  "5920": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a round, blue, old desk lamp."
  },
  "5921": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on a table next to a flower."
  },
  "5922": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is in a living room.\n"
  },
  "5923": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a clean, tidy and spacious living room.\n"
  },
  "5924": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:metallic, cylindrical, cream color"
  },
  "5925": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the left side of the bed, on the nightstand"
  },
  "5926": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is set in the bedroom."
  },
  "5927": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is on the second floor, on the left of the corridor when up to second floor and in the end of the corridor."
  },
  "5928": {
    "question": "Question:what does the drawer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:woody, white, medium size."
  },
  "5929": {
    "question": "Question:where is the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is set under a table. Left to the drawer is a chair. There is a computer near the drawer."
  },
  "5930": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the drawer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is in a study."
  },
  "5931": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:Opposite to the drawer is a hallway."
  },
  "5932": {
    "question": "Question:what does the drawer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soild, wooden and brown."
  },
  "5933": {
    "question": "Question:where is the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is on the opposite side of a white toilet and near a white sink."
  },
  "5934": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the drawer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is in a toilet."
  },
  "5935": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is near a bedroom and a living room."
  },
  "5936": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:large, blue, light"
  },
  "5937": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the bed and two lamps, face a curtain with black curtains"
  },
  "5938": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The carbinet is in the bedroom."
  },
  "5939": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is next to the stairs and has a woody table in it."
  },
  "5940": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle, hanged and brown"
  },
  "5941": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to the mirror and above the toilet."
  },
  "5942": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a restroom on the second floor."
  },
  "5943": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The restroom is at the left rear corner of the stairs."
  },
  "5944": {
    "question": "Question:what does the decorations look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:colorful, rectangular, papery"
  },
  "5945": {
    "question": "Question:where is the decorations?",
    "answer": "Answer:near a swimming pool, on the wall"
  },
  "5946": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the decorations in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The decorations are hanging in a gymnasium."
  },
  "5947": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the decorations?",
    "answer": "Answer:The gymnasium has a swimming pool and a treadmill."
  },
  "5948": {
    "question": "Question:what does the door look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:glassy, tall, transparent"
  },
  "5949": {
    "question": "Question:where is the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:near the curtains, facing the outside"
  },
  "5950": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the door in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The door is located in a study."
  },
  "5951": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:The study connects with the outside and has a shelf with a clock."
  },
  "5952": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cupboard look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle, wooden, brown."
  },
  "5953": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cupboard?",
    "answer": "Answer:In front of it is another, smaller cupboard, There is an induction cooker directly under it"
  },
  "5954": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cupboard in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's installed in a  open kitchen."
  },
  "5955": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cupboard?",
    "answer": "Answer:Here you can see the swimming pool, reception area and a wicket."
  },
  "5956": {
    "question": "Question:what does the desk look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Brown, big and wooden desk."
  },
  "5957": {
    "question": "Question:where is the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:The desk is underneath a ceiling lamp which has six yellow lights, surrounded by three wooden chairs with brown mat."
  },
  "5958": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the desk in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The desk is in a study."
  },
  "5959": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:The desk is near a living room with many pictures and has two windows nearby."
  },
  "5960": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pillow look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black, square, cloth"
  },
  "5961": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the right side of the sofa, next to the lamp"
  },
  "5962": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pillow in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The pillow is set in the spacious livingroom."
  },
  "5963": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lvingroom is next to the dining room, on the third floor and there is a balcony outside."
  },
  "5964": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cactus look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small,green,with some pricks"
  },
  "5965": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cactus?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the right side of the sofa,on the book shelf and between two big plants"
  },
  "5966": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cactus in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cactus is in the lobby."
  },
  "5967": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cactus?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cactus is opposite to the reception counter and in front of the food bar."
  },
  "5968": {
    "question": "Question:what does the glass cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:transparent; used for displaying; four-layer;"
  },
  "5969": {
    "question": "Question:where is the glass cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:beside two sofas and an end table; on the right of the door;"
  },
  "5970": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the glass cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:at the entrance of this bath center;"
  },
  "5971": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the glass cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:the elevators are out of it"
  },
  "5972": {
    "question": "Question:what does the curtain look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:long, cloth, yellow and black"
  },
  "5973": {
    "question": "Question:where is the curtain?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a furnace, near a door"
  },
  "5974": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the curtain in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The curtain is hanging in a study."
  },
  "5975": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the curtain?",
    "answer": "Answer:This study has two laptops and two penholders on the table."
  },
  "5976": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pillow look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:soft"
  },
  "5977": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the bed, across from the mirror"
  },
  "5978": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pillow in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the children's bedroom."
  },
  "5979": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the study and the bathroom."
  },
  "5980": {
    "question": "Question:what does the door look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A yellow wooden door with a metal handle."
  },
  "5981": {
    "question": "Question:where is the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is a bedroom\u2019s door and near two swiches."
  },
  "5982": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the door in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is at the entrance of the bedroom which has a screen in the middle of a platform rather than at one end."
  },
  "5983": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near another bedroom."
  },
  "5984": {
    "question": "Question:what does the keyboard look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Black, small and cuboid."
  },
  "5985": {
    "question": "Question:where is the keyboard?",
    "answer": "Answer:The keyboard is set near two screens and a black telephone."
  },
  "5986": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the keyboard in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The keyboard is in a bedroom."
  },
  "5987": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the keyboard?",
    "answer": "Answer:The keyboard is near a corridor."
  },
  "5988": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stairs look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Brown wooden narrow stairs."
  },
  "5989": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stairs?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stairs connect the parlour and the kitchen."
  },
  "5990": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stairs in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stairs is near the kitchen and near a white chair."
  },
  "5991": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stairs?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near the parlour."
  },
  "5992": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a mirror made of glass with a wooden frame, as smooth as new."
  },
  "5993": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is directly above a desk, opposite a painting.\n"
  },
  "5994": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a living room."
  },
  "5995": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a clean, tidy and spacious living room.\n"
  },
  "5996": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:without backrest, its color is red, it's big "
  },
  "5997": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are some pillows put on the sofa ,and another single sofa is put next to it "
  },
  "5998": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is placed in the living room ,which is front facing the glass door and close to a red carpet."
  },
  "5999": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a big TV installed in the living room,and two big pictures are  put on the wall."
  },
  "6000": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black,tall,plastic and metal,with five wheels \n"
  },
  "6001": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of the table,next to the cabinet and a huge pillar"
  },
  "6002": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in a small office that only contains a set of office equipment."
  },
  "6003": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The small office is opposite to a big office full of paper and face the locker room at a slant."
  },
  "6004": {
    "question": "Question:what does the book look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:blue and green,thick,paper"
  },
  "6005": {
    "question": "Question:where is the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the third row of a shelf placed a display,on the right side of the display and under a black ornament"
  },
  "6006": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the book in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The book is in the lobby."
  },
  "6007": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:The book is on the left of the counter and faces the entrance and the food bar at a slant."
  },
  "6008": {
    "question": "Question:what does the door look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle, white and open"
  },
  "6009": {
    "question": "Question:where is the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is between the bathtub and the toilet."
  },
  "6010": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the door in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a restroom on the first floor."
  },
  "6011": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:The restroom is in the bedroom which is at the right turn of the gate."
  },
  "6012": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White bed and white quilt, the quilt is slightly opened."
  },
  "6013": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed rested against a white wall. There were three pillows on the bed, one pure white, one with silver-gray stripes, and one with black spots."
  },
  "6014": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is in the bedroom."
  },
  "6015": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is in the bedroom, which is the first room on the left hand side of the corridor after going up the stairs on the second floor."
  },
  "6016": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:median size ,circle , its color is brown "
  },
  "6017": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are some small plants put in the vases which are on the table , and there are two single chair put next to the table "
  },
  "6018": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The circle chair is put close to the glass door to balcony ,which are placed next to two same single chairs."
  },
  "6019": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a brown cloth single sofa put nearby, and a big bookcase put front facing the balcony."
  },
  "6020": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, beautiful, light"
  },
  "6021": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the wall, above a furnace"
  },
  "6022": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is under another picture in a study."
  },
  "6023": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The study has a furnace in the corner and two chairs."
  },
  "6024": {
    "question": "Question:what does the microwave look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Medium size, soild and cuboid."
  },
  "6025": {
    "question": "Question:where is the microwave?",
    "answer": "Answer:The microwave is set under a red toaster and a orange juicer and near a big table."
  },
  "6026": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the microwave in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The microwave is in a kitchen."
  },
  "6027": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the microwave?",
    "answer": "Answer:The microwave is near a dining room."
  },
  "6028": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, rectangular"
  },
  "6029": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the refrigerator, next to a white door"
  },
  "6030": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the kitchen."
  },
  "6031": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is on the first floor, and is next to the dining room."
  },
  "6032": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:high, wooden and cuboid."
  },
  "6033": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a sofa in front of the closet, and a white wall on the left of it."
  },
  "6034": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is on a small attic, which is on the second floor."
  },
  "6035": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The attic is above the living room, and connects with a staircase."
  },
  "6036": {
    "question": "Question:what does the switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:plastic, small, rectangle, white"
  },
  "6037": {
    "question": "Question:where is the switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:face a sofa, right under the thermostat."
  },
  "6038": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's installed at the first floor where face the stair."
  },
  "6039": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:On it's right side is the dinning table, and on it's left side is a garden."
  },
  "6040": {
    "question": "Question:what does the curtain look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soild, big and gray."
  },
  "6041": {
    "question": "Question:where is the curtain?",
    "answer": "Answer:The curtain is set near a big brown table under a white sculpture, near a big painting and a transparent table surrounded by twelve transparent chairs."
  },
  "6042": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the curtain in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The curtain is in a dining room."
  },
  "6043": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the curtain?",
    "answer": "Answer:The curtain is near a kitchen."
  },
  "6044": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cloth, brown, cylinder"
  },
  "6045": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a bed, on a table"
  },
  "6046": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is in a big bedroom on the second floor."
  },
  "6047": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is next to a bashroom and facing a long corridor."
  },
  "6048": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is stepped, tall and white."
  },
  "6049": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is under the table and to the left of the two chairs."
  },
  "6050": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in the living room on the first floor."
  },
  "6051": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is under the table and to the left of the two chairs."
  },
  "6052": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is stepped, tall and white."
  },
  "6053": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is under the table and to the left of the two chairs."
  },
  "6054": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in the living room on the first floor."
  },
  "6055": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is under the table and to the left of the two chairs."
  },
  "6056": {
    "question": "Question:what does the curtain look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:grey,cloth,long"
  },
  "6057": {
    "question": "Question:where is the curtain?",
    "answer": "Answer:behind the door, in front of the glass wall and on the left of the pillar"
  },
  "6058": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the curtain in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The curtain is in the number 5 meeting room. "
  },
  "6059": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the curtain?",
    "answer": "Answer:The meeting room is by the side of the vast reading area and near the boothes."
  },
  "6060": {
    "question": "Question:what does the door look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Cuboid, soild and brown."
  },
  "6061": {
    "question": "Question:where is the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:The door is settled near a green painting, on the right side of a brassy switch and on the opposite side to a cabinet."
  },
  "6062": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the door in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The door is in a bedroom."
  },
  "6063": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:The door is near a toilet and a corridor."
  },
  "6064": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is h-shaped, big and red and golden."
  },
  "6065": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is settled on the opposite side of a red leather sofa, on the righr side of the same chair and on the second step."
  },
  "6066": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in a reception room."
  },
  "6067": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is near a porch."
  },
  "6068": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wide,wooden,rectangle"
  },
  "6069": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:in the innermost position of the corridor,near the window and in front of the cabinet"
  },
  "6070": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is in a rest area."
  },
  "6071": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is on the left side of the number 05 meeting room and behind the restaurant."
  },
  "6072": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wide; wooden;with two shelves on it;"
  },
  "6073": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:beside two billboards;beside a tall cabinet;"
  },
  "6074": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:faces the door of this room;"
  },
  "6075": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:many cabinets set around the room "
  },
  "6076": {
    "question": "Question:what does the dustbin look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Cylindrical, white, plastic"
  },
  "6077": {
    "question": "Question:where is the dustbin?",
    "answer": "Answer:The dustbin is set on the ground near a yellow table surrounded by fours yellow chairs and next to a brown box."
  },
  "6078": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the dustbin in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The dustbin is placed in the hall."
  },
  "6079": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the dustbin?",
    "answer": "Answer:The dustbin is placed next to a small conference room and a big conference room."
  },
  "6080": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:leather, middle, brown"
  },
  "6081": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the small table, next the lamp, next to the window"
  },
  "6082": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is located in the spacious bedroom."
  },
  "6083": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is on the first floor and next to the kitchen."
  },
  "6084": {
    "question": "Question:what does the trashcan look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:gray, small, hollow"
  },
  "6085": {
    "question": "Question:where is the trashcan?",
    "answer": "Answer:between two elevators, in front of a bar counter"
  },
  "6086": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the trashcan in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The trashcan is located in a bar."
  },
  "6087": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the trashcan?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bar has stairs in the corner and connects with a gymnasium."
  },
  "6088": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:middle, square, black"
  },
  "6089": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the glass door, next to the wall"
  },
  "6090": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set in the corner of the livingroom."
  },
  "6091": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The livingroom is beside the stairs, on the third floor and next to a kitchen."
  },
  "6092": {
    "question": "Question:what does the tap look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:silver, iron"
  },
  "6093": {
    "question": "Question:where is the tap?",
    "answer": "Answer:Right above the bathtub, face the door."
  },
  "6094": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the tap in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's installed in a bathroom."
  },
  "6095": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the tap?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathroom is built in the main room which  faces the balcony. Right below the room is the swimming pool."
  },
  "6096": {
    "question": "Question:what does the flower look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is withering, white and tall."
  },
  "6097": {
    "question": "Question:where is the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is placed on the desk facing the drawer."
  },
  "6098": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the flower in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is placed on the table facing a drawer in the living room."
  },
  "6099": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are many paintings and a keyboard in the living room."
  },
  "6100": {
    "question": "Question:what does the flower look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is white, withering and long."
  },
  "6101": {
    "question": "Question:where is the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is placed on the table facing a drawer."
  },
  "6102": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the flower in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is placed on the desk and some chairs in the living room."
  },
  "6103": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are some paintings and a keyboard. "
  },
  "6104": {
    "question": "Question:what does the flower look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is white, long and withering."
  },
  "6105": {
    "question": "Question:where is the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is placed on the desk and some chairs."
  },
  "6106": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the flower in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is placed on the desk facing the drawer in the kitchen."
  },
  "6107": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are some paintings and a keyboard in the living room."
  },
  "6108": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:round, yellow and woody"
  },
  "6109": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is btween two cotton sofas and on a carpet."
  },
  "6110": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a chatting room on the first floor."
  },
  "6111": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chatting room is next to the hall."
  },
  "6112": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A double bed with three pillows and covered with white sheets."
  },
  "6113": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is beside a big window and two nightstands,one of which has a black remote control on it."
  },
  "6114": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is faced with a closet and lies at the center of the bedroom."
  },
  "6115": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is near the door of the bedroom and near a toilet."
  },
  "6116": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black, white top surface,metal,with lots of little things on it"
  },
  "6117": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is at the office's corner and on the right of the chair."
  },
  "6118": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is in the number 361 small office."
  },
  "6119": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is along the corridor leading to the exit and at the corner of a junction of three roads."
  },
  "6120": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cylindrical, silver, middle"
  },
  "6121": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the table, behind the photo"
  },
  "6122": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is set in the bright livingroom."
  },
  "6123": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The livingroom is on the first floor and next to the kitchen."
  },
  "6124": {
    "question": "Question:what does the TV look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A black new LCD TV.\n"
  },
  "6125": {
    "question": "Question:where is the TV?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is close to a window and over a chair."
  },
  "6126": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the TV in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the corner of a bedroom and near the ceiling."
  },
  "6127": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the TV?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a dark toilet."
  },
  "6128": {
    "question": "Question:what does the switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:plastic, rectangle, white"
  },
  "6129": {
    "question": "Question:where is the switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's right next the door, It is mounted on the wall"
  },
  "6130": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It was installed in the toilet in the workshop\u3002"
  },
  "6131": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:Work room face the dinning room."
  },
  "6132": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stairs look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:yellow, retangular, short"
  },
  "6133": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stairs?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a room, in front of six pictures, used to second floor up to third floor"
  },
  "6134": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stairs in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stairs is located in front of the corridor."
  },
  "6135": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stairs?",
    "answer": "Answer:The corridor is on the second floor and there is a room in the end of the corridor."
  },
  "6136": {
    "question": "Question:what does the plant look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, green and white."
  },
  "6137": {
    "question": "Question:where is the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:There's a outlet on its left and a jar behind it."
  },
  "6138": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the plant in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's put in a  open kitchen."
  },
  "6139": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:Here you can see the swimming pool, reception area and a wicket."
  },
  "6140": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a medium sized, new, wooden stool.\n"
  },
  "6141": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is under a table, in the middle of two chairs."
  },
  "6142": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is by the window of the study.\n"
  },
  "6143": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a very classic study."
  },
  "6144": {
    "question": "Question:what does the clock look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:round,black and white,glass and metal"
  },
  "6145": {
    "question": "Question:where is the clock?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the right side of the printer, on the desk and a canlendar"
  },
  "6146": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the clock in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The clock is in a big office."
  },
  "6147": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the clock?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is in front of a corridor door,along the road connecting the tea room and the restaurant."
  },
  "6148": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:with four locks; tall;narrow;"
  },
  "6149": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:beside a big open basket; opposite a mirror above a table;"
  },
  "6150": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:in the men's changing room;"
  },
  "6151": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:near a shower cubicle and a closestool;"
  },
  "6152": {
    "question": "Question:what does the glass jar look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Cylindrical,transparent,fragile"
  },
  "6153": {
    "question": "Question:where is the glass jar?",
    "answer": "Answer:The glass jar is placed on a cabinet,in front of a window."
  },
  "6154": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the glass jar in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The galss jar is placed in the tearoom."
  },
  "6155": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the glass jar?",
    "answer": "Answer:The glass jar is placed next to two stairs and near a reading room."
  },
  "6156": {
    "question": "Question:what does the power switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Rectangle , small and plastic"
  },
  "6157": {
    "question": "Question:where is the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is on the lower right of a lamp and right above a wooden frame."
  },
  "6158": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the power switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is set in a corridor at the door of a house."
  },
  "6159": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is set beside the door of a kitchen."
  },
  "6160": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A big yellow wooden chair which is upholstered."
  },
  "6161": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located near both downstairs and upstairs and close to a table."
  },
  "6162": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is set in the dining room."
  },
  "6163": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is near a kitchen."
  },
  "6164": {
    "question": "Question:what does the television look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:metal,medium-size,hanged on the wall"
  },
  "6165": {
    "question": "Question:where is the television?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in front of the bed and over the drawer"
  },
  "6166": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the television in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's hanged on the wall in front of the bed and over the drawer"
  },
  "6167": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the television?",
    "answer": "Answer: there is a bathroom on the left side of the television."
  },
  "6168": {
    "question": "Question:what does the door look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White, vertical and clean."
  },
  "6169": {
    "question": "Question:where is the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:The door was close to the switch."
  },
  "6170": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the door in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The door is in the living room."
  },
  "6171": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:The door is close to the bathroom and toilet."
  },
  "6172": {
    "question": "Question:what does the display look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Rectangular,big,liquid crystal"
  },
  "6173": {
    "question": "Question:where is the display?",
    "answer": "Answer:The display is hund on the wall with three stools in front of it.\n"
  },
  "6174": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the display in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The display is set in a tearoom."
  },
  "6175": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the display?",
    "answer": "Answer:The display is placed near a reading room and the hall."
  },
  "6176": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:coloful,stand on the floor ,big"
  },
  "6177": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's between window and bed"
  },
  "6178": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's on the side of the room"
  },
  "6179": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:the bathroom is on its right side"
  },
  "6180": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pictures look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, normal size, wall-mounted"
  },
  "6181": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pictures?",
    "answer": "Answer:opposite to a white wall, hung on the wall"
  },
  "6182": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pictures in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is hung on the wall which is located in a corridor."
  },
  "6183": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pictures?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the staircase and the laundry."
  },
  "6184": {
    "question": "Question:what does the painting look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Colorful, papery and rectangular."
  },
  "6185": {
    "question": "Question:where is the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is above a big beige sofa and near a white and brown lamp."
  },
  "6186": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the painting in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is in a living room."
  },
  "6187": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is near a corridor and a toilet."
  },
  "6188": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white , a little tall, bright"
  },
  "6189": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the table and next to the window"
  },
  "6190": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the bedroom"
  },
  "6191": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the corridor and on the second floor."
  },
  "6192": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Leather and wooden, cuboid and white and black."
  },
  "6193": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is set underneath two skateboards and near a long white table."
  },
  "6194": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is in a bedroom."
  },
  "6195": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is near a toilet and a laundry."
  },
  "6196": {
    "question": "Question:what does the suitcase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Small, woody, red."
  },
  "6197": {
    "question": "Question:where is the suitcase?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a cabinet  behind the suitcase and two extinguishers behind  it."
  },
  "6198": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the suitcase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The  suit  case is  set on the corner  of  the  room."
  },
  "6199": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the suitcase?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area  is  located  on the  corner  of the hall and has somecabinets and light bulbs."
  },
  "6200": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:square, hairy, gray"
  },
  "6201": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:in the middle of two sofas, in front of the livingroom, next to the glass wall"
  },
  "6202": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is set in a spacious balcony."
  },
  "6203": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The balcony is on the third floor, outside the livingroom and next to the kitchen."
  },
  "6204": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Leopard print, square, fabric"
  },
  "6205": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a black rug under the sofa with a black curtain"
  },
  "6206": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Sofa in living room"
  },
  "6207": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:Sofa near the balcony"
  },
  "6208": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:plastic, rectangle, white"
  },
  "6209": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:Surrounded by five chairs,. There is a potted plant on the table"
  },
  "6210": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in a second-floor balcony, which facing the main bedroom."
  },
  "6211": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The balcony is on the second floor of the villa, directly below the garden. "
  },
  "6212": {
    "question": "Question:what does the handdoor look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Metal, white and small."
  },
  "6213": {
    "question": "Question:where is the handdoor?",
    "answer": "Answer:The handdoor is close to the curtain, on the door."
  },
  "6214": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the handdoor in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The handdoor is in the living room."
  },
  "6215": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the handdoor?",
    "answer": "Answer:The handdoor is close to the living room and balcony."
  },
  "6216": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:steel, rectangle and grey"
  },
  "6217": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed on a cabinet and at the right side of the bigger sink."
  },
  "6218": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "6219": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to the chatting room and the door."
  },
  "6220": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Red,soft,big."
  },
  "6221": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is close to two yellow chairs, and stand against the wall."
  },
  "6222": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is set in a reading room."
  },
  "6223": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is placed near a tearoom."
  },
  "6224": {
    "question": "Question:what does the washing machine look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:iron, silver gray"
  },
  "6225": {
    "question": "Question:where is the washing machine?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is the same washing machine directly above it. There is a tap on it's left."
  },
  "6226": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the washing machine in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is installed in a small laundry."
  },
  "6227": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the washing machine?",
    "answer": "Answer: The laundry is flanked by bedrooms, and there is a chandelier in front"
  },
  "6228": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle, blue and coverd by linen"
  },
  "6229": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed beneath the light on the ceiling and on a striped carpet."
  },
  "6230": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a bedroom on the second floor."
  },
  "6231": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is facing the stairs."
  },
  "6232": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:middle, cylindrical, white "
  },
  "6233": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the nightstand, on the right of the bed"
  },
  "6234": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is set in the bright bedroom."
  },
  "6235": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is on the second floor, on the left of the stairs and in the cenrtal of the corridor. "
  },
  "6236": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, rectangular, wall-mounted"
  },
  "6237": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:above the washing machines, hung on the wall"
  },
  "6238": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the laundry."
  },
  "6239": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the staircase and the corridor."
  },
  "6240": {
    "question": "Question:what does the closestool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White and porcelain."
  },
  "6241": {
    "question": "Question:where is the closestool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The closestool is near a roll of paper and under a picture."
  },
  "6242": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the closestool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The closestool is in a bathroom."
  },
  "6243": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the closestool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area connects with a bedroom and near a wash basin."
  },
  "6244": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:the shape of ellipse, white , small one "
  },
  "6245": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a tap installed above the sink , and the a blue towel is hanging close to it."
  },
  "6246": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is put on the washing table in a small bathroom ,which is installed under a tap ,close to the small mirror."
  },
  "6247": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathroom is the small one which is placed opposite a small bedroom ,ant it's attached with a small mirrors installed on the wall close to the sink."
  },
  "6248": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bottle look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black, glass, tall"
  },
  "6249": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bottle?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the table, among four bottles and first from right"
  },
  "6250": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bottle in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bottle is set in the small kitchen."
  },
  "6251": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bottle?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is on the first floor and next to the livingroom."
  },
  "6252": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White, fabric, long"
  },
  "6253": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are several pillows on the sofa, a square coffee table in front, a picture on the back wall, and a lamp next to it."
  },
  "6254": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Sofa in living room"
  },
  "6255": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is near the stairs and opposite the kitchen"
  },
  "6256": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, irregular, stable"
  },
  "6257": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of a chair, next to a bar counter"
  },
  "6258": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is put in a small bar."
  },
  "6259": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bar has stairs in the corner and a gray trashcan."
  },
  "6260": {
    "question": "Question:what does the jar look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black and white, porcelain"
  },
  "6261": {
    "question": "Question:where is the jar?",
    "answer": "Answer:There's a outlet on its left, and two small plant surround it,"
  },
  "6262": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the jar in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's put in a  open kitchen."
  },
  "6263": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the jar?",
    "answer": "Answer:Here you can see the swimming pool, reception area and a wicket."
  },
  "6264": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stove look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Cuboid, black and soild."
  },
  "6265": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stove?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stove is next to a beige long sofa, near a transparent oval table and a long black sofa."
  },
  "6266": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stove in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stove is in a living room."
  },
  "6267": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stove?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stove is near a balcony and a dining room."
  },
  "6268": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Beige, soild and long."
  },
  "6269": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in front of a window, behind a blue patterned carpet and on the left side of a beige chair."
  },
  "6270": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in a lounge."
  },
  "6271": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is opposite to a white corridor."
  },
  "6272": {
    "question": "Question:what does the switcher look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A small yellow metal switch."
  },
  "6273": {
    "question": "Question:where is the switcher?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to the frame of toilet's door and near bedroom's door."
  },
  "6274": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the switcher in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the bedroom."
  },
  "6275": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the switcher?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near the toilet and the entrance of the bedroom."
  },
  "6276": {
    "question": "Question:what does the target look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, plastic"
  },
  "6277": {
    "question": "Question:where is the target?",
    "answer": "Answer:Facing a big painting. On it's left is another painting. "
  },
  "6278": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the  in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is installed on the second-floor porch of the villa."
  },
  "6279": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the ?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a swimming pool beside the villa."
  },
  "6280": {
    "question": "Question:what does the curtain look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Cloth,blue and smooth."
  },
  "6281": {
    "question": "Question:where is the curtain?",
    "answer": "Answer:The curtain is near the bed."
  },
  "6282": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the curtain in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Curtain is in the bedroom."
  },
  "6283": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the curtain?",
    "answer": "Answer:The curtain is close to the living room and bathroom."
  },
  "6284": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown, big, cloth"
  },
  "6285": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:facing the table, in front of the curtain"
  },
  "6286": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set in the spacious office."
  },
  "6287": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is on the first floor and next to the stairs."
  },
  "6288": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bedside table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A black bedside table with a lamp and some books."
  },
  "6289": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bedside table?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is beisde a picture and a bed with black sheet."
  },
  "6290": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bedside table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a bedroom."
  },
  "6291": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bedside table?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a toilet and an empty room."
  },
  "6292": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:woody, rectangular, big"
  },
  "6293": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the carpet, below the lamp"
  },
  "6294": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the study."
  },
  "6295": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The study is next to the bathroom and children's bedroom."
  },
  "6296": {
    "question": "Question:what does the washing machine look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Metal, white and cuboid."
  },
  "6297": {
    "question": "Question:where is the washing machine?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washing machine is set on the right side of a white washing machine and on the left side of a white sink."
  },
  "6298": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the washing machine in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washing machine is in a laundry."
  },
  "6299": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the washing machine?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washing machine is near a corridor."
  },
  "6300": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pillow look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cloth, square, thick"
  },
  "6301": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the sofa, among some pillows, under the big picture"
  },
  "6302": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pillow in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The pillow is set in the livingroom."
  },
  "6303": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:The livingroom is next to the kitchen, on the third floor and there is a balcony outside."
  },
  "6304": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bin look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:made by knitted bamboo; brown; with a lid;"
  },
  "6305": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bin?",
    "answer": "Answer:beside a drinking dispenser; below a wall lamp;"
  },
  "6306": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bin in?",
    "answer": "Answer:in the corner of a wall."
  },
  "6307": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bin?",
    "answer": "Answer:a big women's changing room having a long corridor."
  },
  "6308": {
    "question": "Question:what does the desk look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black, rectangular, woody"
  },
  "6309": {
    "question": "Question:where is the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:behind a black chair and in front of a wall painting"
  },
  "6310": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the desk in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is in the study."
  },
  "6311": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:The study is next to the dining roon and the bathroom on the second floor."
  },
  "6312": {
    "question": "Question:what does the windows look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A clean transparent glass window with wooden frame."
  },
  "6313": {
    "question": "Question:where is the windows?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to a wooden desk with many drawers and a TV."
  },
  "6314": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the windows in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is over a chair and is in the corner of the bedroom."
  },
  "6315": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the windows?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a dark toilet."
  },
  "6316": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a white, soft sofa made of cloth."
  },
  "6317": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are several different pillows on the sofa.\n"
  },
  "6318": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is in a living room.\n"
  },
  "6319": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a clean, tidy and spacious living room.\n"
  },
  "6320": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:blue, square and with four chairs."
  },
  "6321": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are four chairs around the table, and a tree near the table."
  },
  "6322": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is outside."
  },
  "6323": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a stone dome near the table and on the flagstone."
  },
  "6324": {
    "question": "Question:what does the painting look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle,black and yellow,paper"
  },
  "6325": {
    "question": "Question:where is the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the right side of a green picture,above the book shelf and some plants"
  },
  "6326": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the painting in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is in the vast rest area."
  },
  "6327": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is opposite to a big meeting room and behind the restaurant."
  },
  "6328": {
    "question": "Question:what does the towel look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, cotton and hanged"
  },
  "6329": {
    "question": "Question:where is the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed between the bathtub and the basin."
  },
  "6330": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the towel in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a restroom on the first floor."
  },
  "6331": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The restroom is in the bedroom which is at the right turn of the gate."
  },
  "6332": {
    "question": "Question:what does the door look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:tall, white and transparent, glass"
  },
  "6333": {
    "question": "Question:where is the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:across to the white wall, next to the closestool"
  },
  "6334": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the door in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the corner that is between the living room and the toilet."
  },
  "6335": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:The corner is between the living room and the toilet."
  },
  "6336": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, tall, brown"
  },
  "6337": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the right of the range hood, facing the big table"
  },
  "6338": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is located in the kitchen."
  },
  "6339": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is on the first floor, next to the livingroom."
  },
  "6340": {
    "question": "Question:what does the box look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:open; knitted; big;"
  },
  "6341": {
    "question": "Question:where is the box?",
    "answer": "Answer:beside a small box; below a rounded clock."
  },
  "6342": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the box in?",
    "answer": "Answer:at the entrance of the big hall."
  },
  "6343": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the box?",
    "answer": "Answer:near a white fence at the corner of the hall."
  },
  "6344": {
    "question": "Question:what does the handbag look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soild, small and white and blue."
  },
  "6345": {
    "question": "Question:where is the handbag?",
    "answer": "Answer:The handbag is set in a brown cabinet, near a gray and black bed and near a black and brown chair."
  },
  "6346": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the handbag in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The handbag is in a bedroom."
  },
  "6347": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the handbag?",
    "answer": "Answer:The handbag is near a corridor and a bathroom."
  },
  "6348": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle,leather made,brown"
  },
  "6349": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:near the window,surrounded by five chairs and in front of two desks"
  },
  "6350": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in the vast rest area."
  },
  "6351": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is on the left side of the number 05 meeting room and behind the restaurant."
  },
  "6352": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Red and brown, soild and wooden."
  },
  "6353": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chairs are behind a desk under the ceiling lamp and on the left side of the white table under the small wooden carbinet."
  },
  "6354": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chairs are in a study."
  },
  "6355": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chairs are near the living room and on the opposite side of a bedroom."
  },
  "6356": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:metal,black and white,cuboid"
  },
  "6357": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is under a paper and an envelope,behind the big working desk and on the left side of the telephone."
  },
  "6358": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is in a small office that has a number 359 for one people working."
  },
  "6359": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is near two junctions of three roads and opposite to an empty office."
  },
  "6360": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Leather, soild and white."
  },
  "6361": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is near a black telephone and a metal lamp and next to a black table."
  },
  "6362": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in a living room."
  },
  "6363": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is near a bedroom."
  },
  "6364": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Black, plastic, tall"
  },
  "6365": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is on a stool and there is a phone next to it"
  },
  "6366": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp in living room"
  },
  "6367": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is near the stairs and opposite the kitchen"
  },
  "6368": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sculpture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, cylindrical, stone"
  },
  "6369": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sculpture?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the glass door, under the switch"
  },
  "6370": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sculpture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sculpture is located in the corner of the stairs."
  },
  "6371": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sculpture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stairs is between the first and second floor."
  },
  "6372": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Metal, white and brown and soild."
  },
  "6373": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is set between two paintings and opposite to a gray and black bed."
  },
  "6374": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is in a bedroom."
  },
  "6375": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is near a corridor and a living room."
  },
  "6376": {
    "question": "Question:what does the glass table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:transparent,actangular,glass"
  },
  "6377": {
    "question": "Question:where is the glass table?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to 3 chairs and on a carpet."
  },
  "6378": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the glass table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a rest room on the second floor."
  },
  "6379": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the glass table?",
    "answer": "Answer:the rest room is in a big bedroom which is in the end of a corridor and near a open-balcony"
  },
  "6380": {
    "question": "Question:what does the clock look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle,medium-size,decorated"
  },
  "6381": {
    "question": "Question:where is the clock?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a switch and curtain"
  },
  "6382": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the clock in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in dining room"
  },
  "6383": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the clock?",
    "answer": "Answer:there is a kitchen in front of the kitchen"
  },
  "6384": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, glass, fragile"
  },
  "6385": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a white vase, next to the sink"
  },
  "6386": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the washroom."
  },
  "6387": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is located in a bedroom which has a rectangular balcony, a washroom and a toilet, and the cloakroom is next to the washroom and toilet."
  },
  "6388": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:glass, cylindrical, white"
  },
  "6389": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the bed, mext to the telephone"
  },
  "6390": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is on the table settled in a warm child-bedroom. "
  },
  "6391": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The child-bedroom is next to the corridor on the second floor with a fireplace and a bathroom."
  },
  "6392": {
    "question": "Question:what does the paintings look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:two small paintings ,put on the wall, they are all with black frame "
  },
  "6393": {
    "question": "Question:where is the paintings?",
    "answer": "Answer:they are opposite the hovel, and they are place outside the bathroom in the corridor "
  },
  "6394": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the paintings in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Two small pictures are installed on the wall ouside the small bathroom, which are opposite the hovel in the corridor."
  },
  "6395": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the paintings?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a small bedroom next to the pictures, and a small bathroom next to the paintings ,too."
  },
  "6396": {
    "question": "Question:what does the desk look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Wooden, white, short."
  },
  "6397": {
    "question": "Question:where is the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:The desk is surrounded by a lot of red chairs and next to a picture on the wall."
  },
  "6398": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the desk in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The desk is in a small room on the corner of hall. "
  },
  "6399": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area has a red carpet."
  },
  "6400": {
    "question": "Question:what does the power switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is black, plastic and small."
  },
  "6401": {
    "question": "Question:where is the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is placed on the wall facing the stairs."
  },
  "6402": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the power switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is placed on the wall facing the stairs."
  },
  "6403": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are many cabinets and sinks in the kitchen."
  },
  "6404": {
    "question": "Question:what does the dining-table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, white, circular"
  },
  "6405": {
    "question": "Question:where is the dining-table?",
    "answer": "Answer:above the chair,next to the TV"
  },
  "6406": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the dining-table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the dining room"
  },
  "6407": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the dining-table?",
    "answer": "Answer:Th area is next to the garden and on the first floor."
  },
  "6408": {
    "question": "Question:what does the door handle look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:silver, metal, door-mounted"
  },
  "6409": {
    "question": "Question:where is the door handle?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the door, next to the wall"
  },
  "6410": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the door handle in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the children's bedroom."
  },
  "6411": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the door handle?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the study and the bathroom."
  },
  "6412": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, woody"
  },
  "6413": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the staircase and the TV"
  },
  "6414": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the living room"
  },
  "6415": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is on the second floor and next to the staircase and corridor."
  },
  "6416": {
    "question": "Question:what does the door look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown,wooden,oblong,tall"
  },
  "6417": {
    "question": "Question:where is the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:The door is on the left of a pillar ,on the left side of the desk and opposite to a office heaped with papers."
  },
  "6418": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the door in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set in a small office signed number 307 that only contains a set of office equipment."
  },
  "6419": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:The small office faces the locker room at a slant and connects to a road leading to the tea room and the sofas."
  },
  "6420": {
    "question": "Question:what does the washbasin look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white ,  normal size"
  },
  "6421": {
    "question": "Question:where is the washbasin?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the woody doors and below the mirror"
  },
  "6422": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the washbasin in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the bedroom"
  },
  "6423": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the washbasin?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the corridor and on the second floor."
  },
  "6424": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:woody, yellow, deck chair."
  },
  "6425": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is next to another chair.  The chair is near a table."
  },
  "6426": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in the outside."
  },
  "6427": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair faces a pool."
  },
  "6428": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:woody, green and hard"
  },
  "6429": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to the table and other charis."
  },
  "6430": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the dining hall on the first floor."
  },
  "6431": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The dining hall is next to the kitchen and the stairs."
  },
  "6432": {
    "question": "Question:what does the book look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, opened, thick"
  },
  "6433": {
    "question": "Question:where is the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:between window and bed, on a cabinet with a lamp"
  },
  "6434": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the book in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The book is set at a corner of the bedroom."
  },
  "6435": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is surrounded by a balcony , a living room and a bathroom."
  },
  "6436": {
    "question": "Question:what does the towel look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is white, rectangular and soft."
  },
  "6437": {
    "question": "Question:where is the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel hangs beside the table and at the bottom right of the sink."
  },
  "6438": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the towel in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is in the kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "6439": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel hangs beside the table and at the bottom right of the sink."
  },
  "6440": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, gray and white"
  },
  "6441": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:Behind the chair is the window. There is another chair in front of the chair"
  },
  "6442": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in a second-floor balcony, which facing the main bedroom."
  },
  "6443": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The balcony is on the second floor of the villa, directly below the garden. "
  },
  "6444": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a long, marble table that is as smooth as new."
  },
  "6445": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are four wooden chairs directly below it.\n"
  },
  "6446": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in the dining room."
  },
  "6447": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to a study and kitchen."
  },
  "6448": {
    "question": "Question:what does the painting look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Medium size, soild and rectangular."
  },
  "6449": {
    "question": "Question:where is the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is set near a small purple painting and below a brown and round table."
  },
  "6450": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the painting in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is in a stair."
  },
  "6451": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is set near a living room and a corridor."
  },
  "6452": {
    "question": "Question:what does the painting look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Papery, rectabgular and black and white."
  },
  "6453": {
    "question": "Question:where is the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is set on a wall, on the left side of a orange picture and on the right side of two picture and a newspaper."
  },
  "6454": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the painting in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is in a corridor."
  },
  "6455": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is near a bedroom."
  },
  "6456": {
    "question": "Question:what does the glass door look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:made of glass and the frame is made of iron, the frame is black, not very big "
  },
  "6457": {
    "question": "Question:where is the glass door?",
    "answer": "Answer:there is a circle table and several chairs put close to it, the glass door is to the balcony"
  },
  "6458": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the glass door in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Please help me find a glass door to the balcony in the relaxing area, which is close to a circle table and a single brown sofa."
  },
  "6459": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the glass door?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a big white bookcase put in the relaxing room, and the glass door it opposite the main door."
  },
  "6460": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:square, glass, white"
  },
  "6461": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the wall,next to the bed,above two chairs, there is a horse in the picture"
  },
  "6462": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:This picture is located in a spacious and bright bedroom"
  },
  "6463": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:This bedroom is on the second floor, on the right of the stairs and in the end of the corridor. There is a washroom inside the bedroom."
  },
  "6464": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:metal,white,huge,cuboid"
  },
  "6465": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the left side of the dustbin,on the right side of the white board,near the innermost glass wall"
  },
  "6466": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is set a large office owning the number 377."
  },
  "6467": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is around the corner of a junction of three roads and on the left of the stairway door."
  },
  "6468": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, armless"
  },
  "6469": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It faces the wall and faces an identical chair."
  },
  "6470": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It was placed in the hallway between the open kitchen and the pool."
  },
  "6471": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:There's a pool on one side and an open kitchen on the other"
  },
  "6472": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soild, red and white and small."
  },
  "6473": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is under the pink flowers, near a white toilet and a white sink."
  },
  "6474": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is in a toilet."
  },
  "6475": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is near a bedroom and a corridor."
  },
  "6476": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black; short; squared;"
  },
  "6477": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:in the middle of two identical deck chairs;under two magazines and two ornaments;"
  },
  "6478": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the right side of this hall;"
  },
  "6479": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:a hall as a transition from recieption to massage rooms."
  },
  "6480": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chandelier look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:circular, transparent, slight"
  },
  "6481": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chandelier?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the ceiling, near a washroom"
  },
  "6482": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chandelier in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chandelier is located in a gymnasium."
  },
  "6483": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chandelier?",
    "answer": "Answer:The gymnasium has three chandeliers and connects with a washroom."
  },
  "6484": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:colourless,big and stand on the table"
  },
  "6485": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's stand on the table and in front of the table"
  },
  "6486": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's on the side of the room"
  },
  "6487": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in front of the corridor"
  },
  "6488": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Wooden and leather, red and brown and soild."
  },
  "6489": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is on the right side of a tall wooden carbinet and behind a round wooden table."
  },
  "6490": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in a corridor with a stair."
  },
  "6491": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is near a bathroom."
  },
  "6492": {
    "question": "Question:what does the carpet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:soft, thin, circular"
  },
  "6493": {
    "question": "Question:where is the carpet?",
    "answer": "Answer:under the table, between two chairs"
  },
  "6494": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the carpet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a samll bar."
  },
  "6495": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the carpet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area connects with a gymnasium and has stairs in the corner."
  },
  "6496": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black, wood, rectangular"
  },
  "6497": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a chair, under a flowerpot"
  },
  "6498": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is settled in the center of a dining room on the first floor."
  },
  "6499": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The dining is next to a kitchen and there is a bathroom upstairs."
  },
  "6500": {
    "question": "Question:what does the TV look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small;black;rectangle"
  },
  "6501": {
    "question": "Question:where is the TV?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the closet,on the stove"
  },
  "6502": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the TV in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The TV is located in a bright bedroom."
  },
  "6503": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the TV?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is next to the corridor on the second floor with balcony and stove."
  },
  "6504": {
    "question": "Question:what does the towel look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, long, deep blue."
  },
  "6505": {
    "question": "Question:where is the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel hangs above another towel."
  },
  "6506": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the towel in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It hangs on the stainless steel towel rail on the wall of a shower room."
  },
  "6507": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is in a bathroom, opposite to the towel is the glass washbasin with two sinks in it."
  },
  "6508": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table  look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:woody, brown and rectangle."
  },
  "6509": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table ?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is beneath the light and surrounded by four chairs."
  },
  "6510": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table  in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the dining hall on the first floor."
  },
  "6511": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table ?",
    "answer": "Answer:The dining hall is next to the kitchen and the stairs."
  },
  "6512": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:metal and glass,with yellow light and the thin support"
  },
  "6513": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:on a small table on the left side of a chair,next to a brown and grey wall"
  },
  "6514": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is in a small single room."
  },
  "6515": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The room is behind the food bar and close to the wide corridor set some book shelves."
  },
  "6516": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:ceramic, square, cream color"
  },
  "6517": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:facing the washroom's door, under the mirror"
  },
  "6518": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is set in the washroom.\n"
  },
  "6519": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washroom is inside the bright bedroom, which is on the left of the stairs, in the central of the corridor and on the second floor."
  },
  "6520": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is white, ceramic and rectangular."
  },
  "6521": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is below a painting and a vase."
  },
  "6522": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is in the living room."
  },
  "6523": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is below a painting and a vase."
  },
  "6524": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big,yellow,soft"
  },
  "6525": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's on a colorful carpet and near a guitar."
  },
  "6526": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's located in a living room on the first floor."
  },
  "6527": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:the living room is near a dining room,a kitchen and a stair."
  },
  "6528": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pot look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:stone, yellow and round"
  },
  "6529": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pot?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on a yellow cabinet and next to a door."
  },
  "6530": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pot in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a hall on the first floor."
  },
  "6531": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pot?",
    "answer": "Answer:The hall is next to the chatting room."
  },
  "6532": {
    "question": "Question:what does the television look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Metal, big and black."
  },
  "6533": {
    "question": "Question:where is the television?",
    "answer": "Answer:The television is set opposite to a green bed and above a brown and black drawer."
  },
  "6534": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the television in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The television is in a bedroom."
  },
  "6535": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the television?",
    "answer": "Answer:The television is near a corridor."
  },
  "6536": {
    "question": "Question:what does the kettle look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:grey, cylindrical and steel."
  },
  "6537": {
    "question": "Question:where is the kettle?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed on a cabinet and close to a stove."
  },
  "6538": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the kettle in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "6539": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the kettle?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to the chatting room and the door."
  },
  "6540": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Big, wooden and blue and brown."
  },
  "6541": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is next to a brown chair and a black and cubiod luggage. "
  },
  "6542": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is in a bedroom."
  },
  "6543": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is near a living room and a toilet."
  },
  "6544": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Wooden, round and brown."
  },
  "6545": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is near the same wooden table, near a cabinet with utensils which has two wooden chairs with brown leather cushion nearby and near three windows."
  },
  "6546": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is in the corridor."
  },
  "6547": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is near the bathroom."
  },
  "6548": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is rectangular, white and glass."
  },
  "6549": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is above the vase and the table."
  },
  "6550": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is in the living room."
  },
  "6551": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is above the vase and the table."
  },
  "6552": {
    "question": "Question:what does the oven look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:grey, rectangle and closed"
  },
  "6553": {
    "question": "Question:where is the oven?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is embedded in a cabinet and beneath the vase.\n"
  },
  "6554": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the oven in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a kitchen on the first floo"
  },
  "6555": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the oven?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to the chatting room and the door."
  },
  "6556": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Red, leather and medium size."
  },
  "6557": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is underneath a cloth with white hollowed-out pattern and two pillows, near a red and brown chair and a brown wooden table."
  },
  "6558": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in a bedroom."
  },
  "6559": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is near a room with a tall wooden carbinet and near a corridor."
  },
  "6560": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:tall, filmy, rectangular"
  },
  "6561": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:face the window, next to the door, on the armoire"
  },
  "6562": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is in the bedroom"
  },
  "6563": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is next to the stairs and faces the bathroom."
  },
  "6564": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Umbelliform, medium size and white and brown."
  },
  "6565": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is near a brown and black drawer and next to a gray and black bed."
  },
  "6566": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is in a bedroom."
  },
  "6567": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is near a corridor and a living room."
  },
  "6568": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is small, rectangular and black."
  },
  "6569": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp hung on the wall and beside the door."
  },
  "6570": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is beside the outdoor swimming pool."
  },
  "6571": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp hung on the wall and beside the door."
  },
  "6572": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cactus look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:green,full of spines and small"
  },
  "6573": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cactus?",
    "answer": "Answer:on a black tray on the shell,on the left side of a box containing cards"
  },
  "6574": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cactus in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cactus is in the lobby."
  },
  "6575": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cactus?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cactus is in front of the reception and opposite to the food bar."
  },
  "6576": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Black, single, leather."
  },
  "6577": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The club chair is under a painting, next to a black flower bed."
  },
  "6578": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The club chair is in the study."
  },
  "6579": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The club is next to the balcony and near the gym."
  },
  "6580": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, rectangle"
  },
  "6581": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:right above the sink, face the bathtub"
  },
  "6582": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's installed in a bathroom."
  },
  "6583": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathroom is built in the main room which  faces the balcony. Right below the room is the swimming pool."
  },
  "6584": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:large, brown, woody"
  },
  "6585": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:between two cabinet with a lamp , in front of a cabinet with a television"
  },
  "6586": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is set at a corner of the bedroom."
  },
  "6587": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is surrounded by a balcony , a living room and a bathroom."
  },
  "6588": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle , brown, soft"
  },
  "6589": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:between two cabinet with a lamp, in front of a cabinet with a television"
  },
  "6590": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is located at a corner of the bedroom."
  },
  "6591": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is surrounded by a balcony , a living room and a bathroom."
  },
  "6592": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:large, lying, blue"
  },
  "6593": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:between two cabinet with a lamp , in front of a cabinet with a television"
  },
  "6594": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is located at a corner of the bedroom."
  },
  "6595": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:A bathroom is inside of the bedroom"
  },
  "6596": {
    "question": "Question:what does the piano look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black, wood, big"
  },
  "6597": {
    "question": "Question:where is the piano?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a picture, on the left of a fireplace"
  },
  "6598": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the piano in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The piano is placed in the corner of a small and bright living room."
  },
  "6599": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the piano?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living is on the first floor and there is a balcony outside."
  },
  "6600": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Red and brown, meidum size and wooden."
  },
  "6601": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is on the left side of a black wooden bookshelf under a sculpture, and it is on the opposite side of three same chairs."
  },
  "6602": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is at the corner of a study."
  },
  "6603": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is near a corridor."
  },
  "6604": {
    "question": "Question:what does the laptop look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:medium,white and black"
  },
  "6605": {
    "question": "Question:where is the laptop?",
    "answer": "Answer:on a black table,next to a black chair,in front of a wall painting,face the carbinet"
  },
  "6606": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the laptop in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The laptop is set in the study on the second floor."
  },
  "6607": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the laptop?",
    "answer": "Answer:The study has the window which opens outwards and near the dining room."
  },
  "6608": {
    "question": "Question:what does the book look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:flat, black, thick"
  },
  "6609": {
    "question": "Question:where is the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:on a small table, in the middle of two white chairs"
  },
  "6610": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the book in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's located in a bright bedroom and near the wall."
  },
  "6611": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is on the second floor, in the end of the corridor and there is a washroom inside. There is a balcony and a stairs outside. "
  },
  "6612": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:long, cotton, white."
  },
  "6613": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are some pillows put on the sofa, and it's facing a table."
  },
  "6614": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's put in the reception area where next to the stairs."
  },
  "6615": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's next to the garden. "
  },
  "6616": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black, metallic, rotatable"
  },
  "6617": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a black table with a laptop on it, in front of a carbinet"
  },
  "6618": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in the study."
  },
  "6619": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The study is next to the dining room and bathroom on the second floor."
  },
  "6620": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small;white;ceramic;"
  },
  "6621": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the left of the same sink; beside a hair drier"
  },
  "6622": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:at the end of a hallway;"
  },
  "6623": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:in a small room within two closestools and two shower cubicles;"
  },
  "6624": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Yellow,tall,wooden."
  },
  "6625": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is placed under a table with green top ,on the right of a yellow stool and near a racket. "
  },
  "6626": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is set in the hall."
  },
  "6627": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is placed near a small conference room and the front desk."
  },
  "6628": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a square white sofa filled with cotton."
  },
  "6629": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is under a mirror and a picture."
  },
  "6630": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is in a living room.\n"
  },
  "6631": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a clean, tidy and spacious living room.\n"
  },
  "6632": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a rectangular, larger mirror with a wooden frame."
  },
  "6633": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is directly above a bunch of flowers and a wooden table."
  },
  "6634": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the entrance of this house."
  },
  "6635": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:Opposite it is an upward staircase."
  },
  "6636": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is big, black and white."
  },
  "6637": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is next to the door against the wall."
  },
  "6638": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is next to the door against the wall in the bedroom."
  },
  "6639": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a big bed and bathroom in the bedroom."
  },
  "6640": {
    "question": "Question:what does the drawer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is closed, small and wooden."
  },
  "6641": {
    "question": "Question:where is the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a sink and a pot of flower above the drawer."
  },
  "6642": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the drawer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is placed below the sink and the flower in the toilet."
  },
  "6643": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a picture outside the toilet."
  },
  "6644": {
    "question": "Question:what does the telephone look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black and white,plastic,mental"
  },
  "6645": {
    "question": "Question:where is the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's below a television and on a brown table."
  },
  "6646": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the telephone in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a small berdoom on the second floor."
  },
  "6647": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:the bedroom is near the corridor and a stair."
  },
  "6648": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soild, wooden and leather and red and beige."
  },
  "6649": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is the fifth one in a row of chairs from left to right while facing to the chairs, behind a brown wooden desk and in front of a window."
  },
  "6650": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in a reception room on the first floor."
  },
  "6651": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is near a porch."
  },
  "6652": {
    "question": "Question:what does the television look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The television is square, black and power-off."
  },
  "6653": {
    "question": "Question:where is the television?",
    "answer": "Answer:The television is placed next to the cabinet above the coffee machine."
  },
  "6654": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the television in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The television is hung above the sink next to the cabinet in the kitchen."
  },
  "6655": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the television?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are two big tables and a wine cabinet on the opposite."
  },
  "6656": {
    "question": "Question:what does the television look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The television is square, black and power-off."
  },
  "6657": {
    "question": "Question:where is the television?",
    "answer": "Answer:The television is placed next to the cabinet above the coffee machine."
  },
  "6658": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the television in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The television is hung above the sink next to the cabinet in the kitchen."
  },
  "6659": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the television?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are two big tables and a wine cabinet on the opposite."
  },
  "6660": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, soft, plaid"
  },
  "6661": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the lamp and across the mirror"
  },
  "6662": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the bedroom"
  },
  "6663": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the corridor and another bedroom."
  },
  "6664": {
    "question": "Question:what does the power switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a square, small, white switch."
  },
  "6665": {
    "question": "Question:where is the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is beside a fireplace and a door."
  },
  "6666": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the power switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in a living room."
  },
  "6667": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's beside a kitchen."
  },
  "6668": {
    "question": "Question:what does the power switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is small, square and white."
  },
  "6669": {
    "question": "Question:where is the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:The poster and the door is besides."
  },
  "6670": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the power switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is placed between the poster and the door."
  },
  "6671": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are many posters in the corridor."
  },
  "6672": {
    "question": "Question:what does the paintings look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Paper, white and good looking."
  },
  "6673": {
    "question": "Question:where is the paintings?",
    "answer": "Answer:Paintings are on the sofa, next to the table."
  },
  "6674": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the paintings in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Paintings are in the living room."
  },
  "6675": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the paintings?",
    "answer": "Answer:The paintings are very close to the bedroom and the balcony."
  },
  "6676": {
    "question": "Question:what does the carbinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Rectangular, glasses, white ."
  },
  "6677": {
    "question": "Question:where is the carbinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are some books on the cabinet and a short desk next to it."
  },
  "6678": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the carbinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is set along the wall ."
  },
  "6679": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the carbinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area is located at the corner of the hall."
  },
  "6680": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown, wooden"
  },
  "6681": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:face a bedroom, there is the main room on it's right side."
  },
  "6682": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's on the corridor."
  },
  "6683": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:there is the main room on it's right side."
  },
  "6684": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big,rectangle,wooden"
  },
  "6685": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of the shell,in the middle of the room and in front of a dustbin"
  },
  "6686": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in a small meeting room with the number of 03"
  },
  "6687": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The meeting room is opposite to the gate of a big meeting room and next to a room forbidden to entry and is along a corridor to the lobby."
  },
  "6688": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sculpture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sculpture is made of stone, gray and soild."
  },
  "6689": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sculpture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sculpture is near a black bookshelf and a white painting."
  },
  "6690": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sculpture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sculpture is in a balcony."
  },
  "6691": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sculpture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sculpture is near a living room."
  },
  "6692": {
    "question": "Question:what does the kettle look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:grey, cylindrical and steel"
  },
  "6693": {
    "question": "Question:where is the kettle?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed on a shelf at the right side of the cupboard."
  },
  "6694": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the kettle in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "6695": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the kettle?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to the chatting room and the door."
  },
  "6696": {
    "question": "Question:what does the windows look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White, rectangle and sliding"
  },
  "6697": {
    "question": "Question:where is the windows?",
    "answer": "Answer:The window is on the far left of the entire window, above the fluffy stool."
  },
  "6698": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the windows in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed in a bedroom and beside a wardrobe."
  },
  "6699": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the windows?",
    "answer": "Answer:This bedroom is located at the end of the right turn on the second floor, opposite a storage room.\n"
  },
  "6700": {
    "question": "Question:what does the finess equipment look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Big, soild and black."
  },
  "6701": {
    "question": "Question:where is the finess equipment?",
    "answer": "Answer:The fitness equipment is settled near a white and red bed and opposite to a rectangular painting."
  },
  "6702": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the finess equipment in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The fitness equipment is in a bedroom."
  },
  "6703": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the finess equipment?",
    "answer": "Answer:The fitness equipment is near a corridor."
  },
  "6704": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is ceramic, white and small."
  },
  "6705": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are some flowers in the vase. The vase is placed on the table."
  },
  "6706": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is placed on the table in the living room."
  },
  "6707": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a big sofa and a table in the living room."
  },
  "6708": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:sponge,grey and single."
  },
  "6709": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is close to the white sofa and the tea table."
  },
  "6710": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in the living room."
  },
  "6711": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:Behind the chair is balcony and the bedroom is near the sofa."
  },
  "6712": {
    "question": "Question:what does the TV look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big one\uff0cblend material\uff0cwhite frame"
  },
  "6713": {
    "question": "Question:where is the TV?",
    "answer": "Answer:the TV is embed in the wall\uff0ccurtains are close to it"
  },
  "6714": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the TV in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The TV is embed in the wall of big bedroom\uff0cwhich is close to curtains\uff0copposite the shower room."
  },
  "6715": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the TV?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a shower room and small work place in the living room which is close to leisure area."
  },
  "6716": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white,tall,metal"
  },
  "6717": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's on a metal bedside table and next to a bed."
  },
  "6718": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a big bedroom on the second floor."
  },
  "6719": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:the bedroom is in the end of a corridor and near a open-balcony"
  },
  "6720": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A white cabinet with several drawers."
  },
  "6721": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is under a cabinet and next to a gas stove."
  },
  "6722": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a kitchen and near an oven."
  },
  "6723": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a living room and a dining room."
  },
  "6724": {
    "question": "Question:what does the towel look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cloth made,white ,soft and water absorbing"
  },
  "6725": {
    "question": "Question:where is the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's on a towel rack and next to a bathtub"
  },
  "6726": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the towel in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in the washroom on the first floor"
  },
  "6727": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:the washroom is next to a bedroom which is near the corridor"
  },
  "6728": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Porcelainous, small and silvery and yellow."
  },
  "6729": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is settled on a brown table and near a brown sink."
  },
  "6730": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is in a toilet."
  },
  "6731": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is near a corridor and a kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "6732": {
    "question": "Question:what does the phone look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black, small , metal"
  },
  "6733": {
    "question": "Question:where is the phone?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the table and next to the bed "
  },
  "6734": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the phone in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the bedroom"
  },
  "6735": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the phone?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the corridor and on the second floor."
  },
  "6736": {
    "question": "Question:what does the ladder look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:folded,steel and leaning against the chest"
  },
  "6737": {
    "question": "Question:where is the ladder?",
    "answer": "Answer:The ladder is leaning against the chest and near a stick"
  },
  "6738": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the ladder in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The ladder is on the edge fo the room"
  },
  "6739": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the ladder?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a corridor outside the room"
  },
  "6740": {
    "question": "Question:what does the loudspeaker box look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Silver,metal,small"
  },
  "6741": {
    "question": "Question:where is the loudspeaker box?",
    "answer": "Answer:The loudspeaker box is set under a television and near three chairs. "
  },
  "6742": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the loudspeaker box in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The loudspeaker box is placed in a tearoom."
  },
  "6743": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the loudspeaker box?",
    "answer": "Answer:The loudspeaker box is placed near a reading room and the hall."
  },
  "6744": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Black, rectangular, rattan"
  },
  "6745": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a vase on it and there are two sofas next to it"
  },
  "6746": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Table in the balcony"
  },
  "6747": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:Table near living room"
  },
  "6748": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Red, rectangular, woody."
  },
  "6749": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are two chairs with the same colour ,shape on its left and one chair with the same colour, shape on its right.There are five chairs with the same colour ,shape opposite to it."
  },
  "6750": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is set on a side of the corridor via the altar."
  },
  "6751": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area has lots of benches on each side of the corridor ."
  },
  "6752": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, square, ceramic"
  },
  "6753": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the washstand, under the mirror"
  },
  "6754": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is set in the washroom."
  },
  "6755": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washroom is on the third floor, next to the stairs and facing the dining room."
  },
  "6756": {
    "question": "Question:what does the trashcan look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, gray, hollow"
  },
  "6757": {
    "question": "Question:where is the trashcan?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the wall, under a hair dryer"
  },
  "6758": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the trashcan in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in a washroom."
  },
  "6759": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the trashcan?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area has one door and one large mirror."
  },
  "6760": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Black, single, leather."
  },
  "6761": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The club chair is under a picture, next to a metal stool."
  },
  "6762": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The club chair is in the study."
  },
  "6763": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The club is next to the balcony and near the gym."
  },
  "6764": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, bright"
  },
  "6765": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the TV and above the stove"
  },
  "6766": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the bedroom"
  },
  "6767": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the  corridor and on the second floor"
  },
  "6768": {
    "question": "Question:what does the plant look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:green, big"
  },
  "6769": {
    "question": "Question:where is the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a big painting on its right. It's facing a LCD TV."
  },
  "6770": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the plant in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It was placed in a corner of the reception area."
  },
  "6771": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area faces the open kitchen, next to the pool, and dinning table on the other side."
  },
  "6772": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small , black and white , light"
  },
  "6773": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:on a small cabinet , next to the bed"
  },
  "6774": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is located on a small cabinet , in the bedroom."
  },
  "6775": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is surrounded by a balcony , a living room and a bathroom."
  },
  "6776": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small , black and white , light"
  },
  "6777": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:on a small cabinet , next to the bed"
  },
  "6778": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is located on a small cabinet , in the bedroom."
  },
  "6779": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is surrounded by a balcony , a living room and a bathroom."
  },
  "6780": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, shallow; oblong;"
  },
  "6781": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:near a wooden tissue box; faced with a wooden holder and a brown bed."
  },
  "6782": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:in the corner of the room"
  },
  "6783": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:a room with marble floors."
  },
  "6784": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soild, red and brown, wooden."
  },
  "6785": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is on the left side of a small wooden table under a wooden box, near a beige chair and below two pictures."
  },
  "6786": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in a living room."
  },
  "6787": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is near a study."
  },
  "6788": {
    "question": "Question:what does the toilet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, short"
  },
  "6789": {
    "question": "Question:where is the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:under the window,  next to a sink"
  },
  "6790": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the toilet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the toilet."
  },
  "6791": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is in a corner which is next to the dining room."
  },
  "6792": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:square, metallic, black"
  },
  "6793": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the carpet, next to the sofa"
  },
  "6794": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is set in the bright livingroom."
  },
  "6795": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The livingroom is on the first floor and next to the dining room."
  },
  "6796": {
    "question": "Question:what does the carbinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Rectangular, small, red."
  },
  "6797": {
    "question": "Question:where is the carbinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:There  are two cabinet with the same state, size, colour on its left and a brown desk  opposite to it."
  },
  "6798": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the carbinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The  cabinet  is set near a glasses door of the hall."
  },
  "6799": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the carbinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area has some brown cabinets and red cabinets."
  },
  "6800": {
    "question": "Question:what does the desk look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Rectangular , woody, brown."
  },
  "6801": {
    "question": "Question:where is the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a leather chair next to the desk and a book on the desk."
  },
  "6802": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the desk in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The desk is set in front of lots of benches."
  },
  "6803": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area has a woody door and a fan."
  },
  "6804": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:transparent, glass, big"
  },
  "6805": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the left of the door, next to the picture"
  },
  "6806": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is set in the washroom."
  },
  "6807": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washroom is inside the bedroom, which is on the left of the stairs, on the second floor and in the central of the corridor.\n"
  },
  "6808": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:leather,dark yellow and soft"
  },
  "6809": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a sofa ,a window and a curtain."
  },
  "6810": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's located in the corner of a living room on the first floor."
  },
  "6811": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:the living room is near a dining room,a kitchen and a stair."
  },
  "6812": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is glass, round and white."
  },
  "6813": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is above the table and below the flowers."
  },
  "6814": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is in the lounge on the first floor."
  },
  "6815": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is above the table and below the flowers."
  },
  "6816": {
    "question": "Question:what does the outlet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, rectangle, white"
  },
  "6817": {
    "question": "Question:where is the outlet?",
    "answer": "Answer:There's an exact same outlet to the left of it, On its left there is a cooker and a dish with pears"
  },
  "6818": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the outlet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's installed in a  open kitchen."
  },
  "6819": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the outlet?",
    "answer": "Answer:Here you can see the swimming pool, reception area and a wicket."
  },
  "6820": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Silvery, small and metal."
  },
  "6821": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is near a brown cabinet and near an oven."
  },
  "6822": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is in a kitchen."
  },
  "6823": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is near a toilet and a corridor on the first floor."
  },
  "6824": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:standing, wood, yellow"
  },
  "6825": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:between two small chairs, near the stairs"
  },
  "6826": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is set at a corner of the living room, on the second floor."
  },
  "6827": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is very spacious."
  },
  "6828": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cloth, light blue, small"
  },
  "6829": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the left of the small table, next to the glass wall"
  },
  "6830": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is located in a bright balcony."
  },
  "6831": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The balcony is outside the bedroom and next to the washroom."
  },
  "6832": {
    "question": "Question:what does the book look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:thick, revtangular, paper books"
  },
  "6833": {
    "question": "Question:where is the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a door, on the third layer of the shelf"
  },
  "6834": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the book in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The books are put on the shelf which is in front of a table in a study. "
  },
  "6835": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:The study has a lamp in the center and shelves on the wall."
  },
  "6836": {
    "question": "Question:what does the hand door look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Metal, silver and small."
  },
  "6837": {
    "question": "Question:where is the hand door?",
    "answer": "Answer:The hand door was on the wooden door, next to the toilet."
  },
  "6838": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the hand door in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The hand door is in the toilet."
  },
  "6839": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the hand door?",
    "answer": "Answer:The hand door is close to the bedroom and bathroom."
  },
  "6840": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is large, white and rectangular."
  },
  "6841": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is between the ceiling and the refrigerator."
  },
  "6842": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is in the kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "6843": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is between the ceiling and the refrigerator."
  },
  "6844": {
    "question": "Question:what does the Glass bottle look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:glass,transparent,fragile"
  },
  "6845": {
    "question": "Question:where is the Glass bottle?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a woolen pillar and on a black long dining table."
  },
  "6846": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the Glass bottle in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a dining room on the first floor."
  },
  "6847": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the Glass bottle?",
    "answer": "Answer:the dining room is near a living room and a stair."
  },
  "6848": {
    "question": "Question:what does the drawer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, black, wood"
  },
  "6849": {
    "question": "Question:where is the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:under a lamp, next to a fire place"
  },
  "6850": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the drawer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is in the corner of a bright and big living room."
  },
  "6851": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is next to a corridor with wood floor and next to a small living room."
  },
  "6852": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:leather,dark yellow and soft"
  },
  "6853": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a stone horse and curtain."
  },
  "6854": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's located in a living room on the first floor."
  },
  "6855": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:the living room is near a dining room,a kitchen and a stair."
  },
  "6856": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a wooden, old, brown chair."
  },
  "6857": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in front of a doorway, beside a cabinet."
  },
  "6858": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in a living room."
  },
  "6859": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's beside a kitchen."
  },
  "6860": {
    "question": "Question:what does the tablet computer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Metal,black,rectangular."
  },
  "6861": {
    "question": "Question:where is the tablet computer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The tablet computer is placed on a cabinet and near three glass jars."
  },
  "6862": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the tablet computer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The tablet computer is placed in a tearoom."
  },
  "6863": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the tablet computer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The tablet computer is placed next to two stairs and near a reading room."
  },
  "6864": {
    "question": "Question:what does the box look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:plastic, square, white"
  },
  "6865": {
    "question": "Question:where is the box?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the table, next to the vase, next to the photo"
  },
  "6866": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the box in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The box is set in the livingroom."
  },
  "6867": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the box?",
    "answer": "Answer:The livingroom is on the first floor and next to the dining room."
  },
  "6868": {
    "question": "Question:what does the keyboard look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wireless,rectangular,silvery and white"
  },
  "6869": {
    "question": "Question:where is the keyboard?",
    "answer": "Answer:The keyboard is on the middle thite desk,in front of the computer and surrounded by four chairs."
  },
  "6870": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the keyboard in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The keyboard is in a median size meeting room with the identifier of 348."
  },
  "6871": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the keyboard?",
    "answer": "Answer:The meeting room is at the corner of the three fork road,opposite to an empty big room and has a road connecting to the rest area. "
  },
  "6872": {
    "question": "Question:what does the switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle, white, small"
  },
  "6873": {
    "question": "Question:where is the switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:Between a door and a painting, facing another painting."
  },
  "6874": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It was installed right next to the door to the second-floor balcony."
  },
  "6875": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's on the second floor in the hallway, next to a bedroom, and there is a toilet directly under it"
  },
  "6876": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rounded, transparent, uncovered"
  },
  "6877": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the table, under the mirror"
  },
  "6878": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the toilet."
  },
  "6879": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is in a corner which is next to the living room."
  },
  "6880": {
    "question": "Question:what does the toilet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Medium size, cuboid and white."
  },
  "6881": {
    "question": "Question:where is the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The closetool is near a white sink and a rectangular mirrror."
  },
  "6882": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the toilet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The closetool is in a toilet."
  },
  "6883": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The closetool is near a study."
  },
  "6884": {
    "question": "Question:what does the Gym equipment look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black and grey,medium-size, made by metal"
  },
  "6885": {
    "question": "Question:where is the Gym equipment?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's on the right of the treadwill and arm apparatus"
  },
  "6886": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the Gym equipment in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a room at the end of the corridor"
  },
  "6887": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the Gym equipment?",
    "answer": "Answer:there is a small bathroom"
  },
  "6888": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, ellipse, ceramic"
  },
  "6889": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of a picture, next to a cupboard"
  },
  "6890": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is placed in the corner of a kitchen with wood floor on the first floor."
  },
  "6891": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to a dining room and is in front of a storeroom."
  },
  "6892": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Wooden, beige and soild."
  },
  "6893": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set on the right side of a long beige sofa and it is set between a window and a transparent door."
  },
  "6894": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in a lounge."
  },
  "6895": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is on the opposite side of a white corridor and near a living room."
  },
  "6896": {
    "question": "Question:what does the Jar look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big,round,ceramic"
  },
  "6897": {
    "question": "Question:where is the Jar?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a glass window and a woolen roiling."
  },
  "6898": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the Jar in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's on a stair between first floor and second floor.\n"
  },
  "6899": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the Jar?",
    "answer": "Answer:the stair is near a living room."
  },
  "6900": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, rectangular, white"
  },
  "6901": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:facing a lamp, next to a table"
  },
  "6902": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is in a white and bright bathroom."
  },
  "6903": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathroom is next to a cloakroom and has a small balcony."
  },
  "6904": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, plastic, white"
  },
  "6905": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the door, next to the glass wall, under the glass window"
  },
  "6906": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set on the bright balcony."
  },
  "6907": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The balcony is ouside the bedroom, which is on the left of the corridor when go upstairs and on the second floor."
  },
  "6908": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a large, new, square mirror."
  },
  "6909": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is above a cabinet, in front of a bed."
  },
  "6910": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in the bedroom."
  },
  "6911": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is beside the corridor."
  },
  "6912": {
    "question": "Question:what does the deck chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black with white cushions; cozy; long;"
  },
  "6913": {
    "question": "Question:where is the deck chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:in the middle of two black end table; in the middle of two identical deck chair."
  },
  "6914": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the deck chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:in a small hall behind a wooden screen."
  },
  "6915": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the deck chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:near two changing rooms;"
  },
  "6916": {
    "question": "Question:what does the desk look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Black, rectangular, wood."
  },
  "6917": {
    "question": "Question:where is the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are candy on it and there is a picture next to it"
  },
  "6918": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the desk in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The desk is in the living room."
  },
  "6919": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:Table near the corridor connecting the gym"
  },
  "6920": {
    "question": "Question:what does the desk look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Black, rectangular, wood."
  },
  "6921": {
    "question": "Question:where is the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are candy on it and there is a picture next to it"
  },
  "6922": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the desk in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The desk is in the living room."
  },
  "6923": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:Table near the corridor connecting the gym"
  },
  "6924": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a brand new white, rectangular wooden chair."
  },
  "6925": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:This wooden chair is directly below a long white table, to the right of a wooden ladder.\n"
  },
  "6926": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:This wooden chair is in a study.\n"
  },
  "6927": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a very neat study with many books.\n"
  },
  "6928": {
    "question": "Question:what does the tap look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:silver, iron "
  },
  "6929": {
    "question": "Question:where is the tap?",
    "answer": "Answer:Right above the sink and right under the mirror."
  },
  "6930": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the tap in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's installed in the toilet."
  },
  "6931": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the tap?",
    "answer": "Answer:The toilet is on the first floor of the villa, on its left is the garden and on its right is the swimming pool."
  },
  "6932": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:circular, woody and yellow"
  },
  "6933": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to the door and next to a table."
  },
  "6934": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "6935": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to the chatting room and the door."
  },
  "6936": {
    "question": "Question:what does the swivel chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black, large, stable"
  },
  "6937": {
    "question": "Question:where is the swivel chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a spinning bike, near a man washroom"
  },
  "6938": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the swivel chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a gymnasium."
  },
  "6939": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the swivel chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are three chandeliers and a treadmill in this gymnasium."
  },
  "6940": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cylindrical, gray, small"
  },
  "6941": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the door, below the picture frames"
  },
  "6942": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The box is settled in the corridor on the second floor."
  },
  "6943": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The corridor is bright and narrow with the wooden rail."
  },
  "6944": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Hollow, medium size and white."
  },
  "6945": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is before a big mirror and a brown bookcase."
  },
  "6946": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is in a toilet."
  },
  "6947": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is near a bedroom and a corridor."
  },
  "6948": {
    "question": "Question:what does the toilet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer: white,  porcelain"
  },
  "6949": {
    "question": "Question:where is the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:Right under the mirror. There is a sink on its right."
  },
  "6950": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the toilet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's installed in the toilet."
  },
  "6951": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The toilet is on the first floor of the villa, on its left is the garden and on its right is the swimming pool."
  },
  "6952": {
    "question": "Question:what does the fan look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Metal, round, tall."
  },
  "6953": {
    "question": "Question:where is the fan?",
    "answer": "Answer:The fan is set in front of a stone pillar and next to some green books."
  },
  "6954": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the fan in?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a woody chair on its left. There are three ranges of benches on its right."
  },
  "6955": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the fan?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area has a broad corridor via the central hall."
  },
  "6956": {
    "question": "Question:what does the laptop look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, gray, convenient"
  },
  "6957": {
    "question": "Question:where is the laptop?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the table, in front of a chair"
  },
  "6958": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the laptop in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The laptop is located in a study."
  },
  "6959": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the laptop?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are some shelves on the wall and a lamp in the center in the study."
  },
  "6960": {
    "question": "Question:what does the switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:plastic, square,"
  },
  "6961": {
    "question": "Question:where is the switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:It has an outlet in the lower right corner, It's facing a tap and a sink."
  },
  "6962": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is installed on the wall at the edge of the open kitchen"
  },
  "6963": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:Here you can see the swimming pool, reception area and a wicket."
  },
  "6964": {
    "question": "Question:what does the hair dryer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, small, electroic "
  },
  "6965": {
    "question": "Question:where is the hair dryer?",
    "answer": "Answer:against a wall, above a trashcan"
  },
  "6966": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the hair dryer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a man washroom."
  },
  "6967": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the hair dryer?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a large wardrobe and a laundry basket in this man washroom."
  },
  "6968": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:soft, gray and oblong."
  },
  "6969": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is near a wooden desk and near a red sofa."
  },
  "6970": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in a big living room."
  },
  "6971": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is next to a dining room and leads to outdoors via a door."
  },
  "6972": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Tall,rectangular, wooden"
  },
  "6973": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is set under a yellow table surrounded by four yellow chairs and near a yellow box and a dustbin."
  },
  "6974": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is placed in the hall."
  },
  "6975": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is placed near a small conference room and a big conference room."
  },
  "6976": {
    "question": "Question:what does the door look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, wooden, white"
  },
  "6977": {
    "question": "Question:where is the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the right of the oven, facing the cabinet"
  },
  "6978": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the door in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The door is set in the kitchen."
  },
  "6979": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is on the first floor and next to the livingroom."
  },
  "6980": {
    "question": "Question:what does the jug look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Small, porcelainous and white."
  },
  "6981": {
    "question": "Question:where is the jug?",
    "answer": "Answer:The jug is set in a big brown cabinet and near a gray and black bed."
  },
  "6982": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the jug in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The jug is in a bedroom."
  },
  "6983": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the jug?",
    "answer": "Answer:The jug is near a corridor and a bathroom."
  },
  "6984": {
    "question": "Question:what does the fireplace look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, grey, hard"
  },
  "6985": {
    "question": "Question:where is the fireplace?",
    "answer": "Answer:surrounded by a long sofa and two small sofas, under a television"
  },
  "6986": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the fireplace in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The fireplace is set at a side of the living room, on the second floor."
  },
  "6987": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the fireplace?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is very spacious."
  },
  "6988": {
    "question": "Question:what does the curtain look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Beige, cloth and thin."
  },
  "6989": {
    "question": "Question:where is the curtain?",
    "answer": "Answer:The curtain is opposite to a white and brown bed and two skateboards."
  },
  "6990": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the curtain in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The curtain is in a bedroom on the second floor."
  },
  "6991": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the curtain?",
    "answer": "Answer:The curtain is near a toilet."
  },
  "6992": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Rectangular\uff0cblack\uff0crotatable"
  },
  "6993": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is set under a yellow table and next to a box and a shelf."
  },
  "6994": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is placed in the hall."
  },
  "6995": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is placed near a small conference room and a big conference room."
  },
  "6996": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:hanged, white and rectangle."
  },
  "6997": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is hanging on the wall next to the door and facing the bed."
  },
  "6998": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a bedroom on the second floor."
  },
  "6999": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is at the left rear corner of the stairs."
  },
  "7000": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cylindrical, white, yellow"
  },
  "7001": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer: next to the white bed and another lamp with the same color and shape, near the mirror"
  },
  "7002": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer: The lamp is in the bedroom. "
  },
  "7003": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer: The lamp faces a woody table with a white chair."
  },
  "7004": {
    "question": "Question:what does the target look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:iron, silver gray"
  },
  "7005": {
    "question": "Question:where is the target?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a tap on it's left, Right under it is the same washing machine."
  },
  "7006": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the target in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is installed in a small laundry."
  },
  "7007": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the target?",
    "answer": "Answer: The laundry is flanked by bedrooms, and there is a chandelier in front"
  },
  "7008": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is big, square and colorful."
  },
  "7009": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is placed facing the stairs next to the cabinet."
  },
  "7010": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is placed facing the stairs next to the cabinet."
  },
  "7011": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are many cabinets and sinks in the kitchen."
  },
  "7012": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:glass,gray,fragile"
  },
  "7013": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's above a washstand and next to 2 lights.\n"
  },
  "7014": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a washroom on the second floor."
  },
  "7015": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:the washroom is near a bedroom and next to a stari."
  },
  "7016": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden, white and cuboid."
  },
  "7017": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a printer on the left of the cabinet, and a wash basin is in front of it."
  },
  "7018": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is in a tiny room."
  },
  "7019": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The tiny room connects with a living room, and there is a toolroom on the left of the tiny room."
  },
  "7020": {
    "question": "Question:what does the telephone look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:grey;plastic;traditional;"
  },
  "7021": {
    "question": "Question:where is the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:hung on the wall behind the open door; above a socket."
  },
  "7022": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the telephone in?",
    "answer": "Answer:at the entrance of a room with a bathtub and two beds."
  },
  "7023": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:This room is oppposite two oblong paintings across a grey carpet."
  },
  "7024": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:ratten, brown, rectangular"
  },
  "7025": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:face the white table and three chairs with the same shape and color"
  },
  "7026": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chairs are in the dining room."
  },
  "7027": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chairs are in front of the kitchen and face the bathroom and the study in the second floor."
  },
  "7028": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sprinkler look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White, tubular and plastic."
  },
  "7029": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sprinkler?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a big bathtub under the sprinkler and a curtain near it."
  },
  "7030": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sprinkler in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sprinkler is in a bathroom."
  },
  "7031": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sprinkler?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area connects with a bedroom and near a toilet."
  },
  "7032": {
    "question": "Question:what does the printer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:hard,cuboid,black,electric"
  },
  "7033": {
    "question": "Question:where is the printer?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the right side of the phone and the desk,above a dustbin and in front of the curtain "
  },
  "7034": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the printer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a large office owning the number 377."
  },
  "7035": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the printer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is at the corner of a junction of three roads and on the left of the stairway door."
  },
  "7036": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pen look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black,thin and long"
  },
  "7037": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pen?",
    "answer": "Answer:on a blue tray of a desk,next to a magazine and  surrounded by six chairs"
  },
  "7038": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pen in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The pen is in the reception."
  },
  "7039": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pen?",
    "answer": "Answer:The pen is on the left of the counter and faces the entrance and the food bar at a slant."
  },
  "7040": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, rectangular, white"
  },
  "7041": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the woody table and the green chairs"
  },
  "7042": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the study."
  },
  "7043": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The study is next to the bathroom and children's bedroom."
  },
  "7044": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Woody, rectangular, red."
  },
  "7045": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are four chairs with the same material, shape behind them and a brown chair in front of them."
  },
  "7046": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chairs are set close to the wall and on a corridor via the altar."
  },
  "7047": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area has a red carpet and a brown chair."
  },
  "7048": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is small, black and round."
  },
  "7049": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is in the vase. The vase is next to the sink."
  },
  "7050": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is placed next to the sink in the bathroom."
  },
  "7051": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a shower room, sink and toilet in the bathroom."
  },
  "7052": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stove look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, black"
  },
  "7053": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stove?",
    "answer": "Answer:below the TV,  across from the bed "
  },
  "7054": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stove in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the bedroom"
  },
  "7055": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stove?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the living room and on the second floor."
  },
  "7056": {
    "question": "Question:what does the oven look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The oven is large, black and rectangular."
  },
  "7057": {
    "question": "Question:where is the oven?",
    "answer": "Answer:The oven is under the cabinet and on the right side of the refrigerator."
  },
  "7058": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the oven in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The oven is in the kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "7059": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the oven?",
    "answer": "Answer:The oven is under the cabinet and on the right side of the refrigerator."
  },
  "7060": {
    "question": "Question:what does the oven look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The oven is large, black and rectangular."
  },
  "7061": {
    "question": "Question:where is the oven?",
    "answer": "Answer:The oven is under the cabinet and on the right side of the refrigerator."
  },
  "7062": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the oven in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The oven is in the kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "7063": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the oven?",
    "answer": "Answer:The oven is under the cabinet and on the right side of the refrigerator."
  },
  "7064": {
    "question": "Question:what does the desk look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Rectangle ,white, wooden."
  },
  "7065": {
    "question": "Question:where is the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:Two white candles are on the desk.The desk is next to a silvery statue."
  },
  "7066": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the desk in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The desk is surrounded by wooden fences."
  },
  "7067": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area has ranges of benches and pillars."
  },
  "7068": {
    "question": "Question:what does the wax look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white,round,Easily melted\n\n"
  },
  "7069": {
    "question": "Question:where is the wax?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's on a white table and next to a same wax."
  },
  "7070": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the wax in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a dining room on the second floor."
  },
  "7071": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the wax?",
    "answer": "Answer:the dining room is near a living  room and a balcony."
  },
  "7072": {
    "question": "Question:what does the carpet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Lying flat , brown, soft"
  },
  "7073": {
    "question": "Question:where is the carpet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The carpet is set on the ground ,near a bookshelf."
  },
  "7074": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the carpet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The carpet is placed in the hall."
  },
  "7075": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the carpet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The carpet is placed near the gate and next to the front desk."
  },
  "7076": {
    "question": "Question:what does the window look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, transparent, marginate"
  },
  "7077": {
    "question": "Question:where is the window?",
    "answer": "Answer:hung on the white wall, behind the sofa"
  },
  "7078": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the window in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the living room."
  },
  "7079": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the window?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the dining room and the kitchen."
  },
  "7080": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is glass, polygonal and white."
  },
  "7081": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is to the right of the mirror and to the left of the towel."
  },
  "7082": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is inside the bathroom of the bedroom."
  },
  "7083": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is to the right of the mirror and to the left of the towel."
  },
  "7084": {
    "question": "Question:what does the tap look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Metal, silver, streamlined"
  },
  "7085": {
    "question": "Question:where is the tap?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a vase and towel next to the tap"
  },
  "7086": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the tap in?",
    "answer": "Answer:tap in the bedroom"
  },
  "7087": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the tap?",
    "answer": "Answer:tap in the bedroom"
  },
  "7088": {
    "question": "Question:what does the piano look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wood,big,close to window"
  },
  "7089": {
    "question": "Question:where is the piano?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's between painting and lamp"
  },
  "7090": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the piano in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in dinning room"
  },
  "7091": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the piano?",
    "answer": "Answer:there is a study next to the dinning room"
  },
  "7092": {
    "question": "Question:what does the book look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle, small and printed"
  },
  "7093": {
    "question": "Question:where is the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on a sofa and next to a plate."
  },
  "7094": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the book in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a chatting room on the first floor."
  },
  "7095": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chatting room is next to the hall."
  },
  "7096": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black, woody, small"
  },
  "7097": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the bed and the curtains"
  },
  "7098": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the bedroom"
  },
  "7099": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the corridor and on the second floor."
  },
  "7100": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden,high legs,brown"
  },
  "7101": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:around the desk,back to the display and far from the window and close to the meeting room"
  },
  "7102": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is in the vast rest area."
  },
  "7103": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is set on the left side of a meeting room and behind the restaurant."
  },
  "7104": {
    "question": "Question:what does the flowers look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Blooming, white and beautiful."
  },
  "7105": {
    "question": "Question:where is the flowers?",
    "answer": "Answer:Flowers are on the table."
  },
  "7106": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the flowers in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Flowers are in the living room."
  },
  "7107": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the flowers?",
    "answer": "Answer:They are very close to the bedroom and toilet."
  },
  "7108": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is brown, big and square."
  },
  "7109": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a door and television next to the picture."
  },
  "7110": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is placed on the wall of the bedroom."
  },
  "7111": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a big bed and some pictures in the bedroom. "
  },
  "7112": {
    "question": "Question:what does the painting look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black,blue and yellow,paper,rectangle"
  },
  "7113": {
    "question": "Question:where is the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the right side of a yellow painting ,under two lights and on the left side of a box of napkins"
  },
  "7114": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the painting in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is in a food bar."
  },
  "7115": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting faces the door of the corridor at a slant and along the corridor leading to counter. "
  },
  "7116": {
    "question": "Question:what does the tap look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:grey, stick and steel"
  },
  "7117": {
    "question": "Question:where is the tap?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed on a cabinet and between the two sinks.\n"
  },
  "7118": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the tap in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "7119": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the tap?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to the chatting room and the door."
  },
  "7120": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pillow look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soft,rectangular,cotton.\n"
  },
  "7121": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:The pillow is placed on a green sofa on the right side of a bed, next to a lamp."
  },
  "7122": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pillow in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The pillow is placed in a small bedroom."
  },
  "7123": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:The pillow is set near a tea room and next to the hall. "
  },
  "7124": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, tall, large "
  },
  "7125": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:face another carbinet with the same shape and color, next to the door of the clakroom"
  },
  "7126": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The carbinet is in the cloakroom."
  },
  "7127": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cloakroom is in the master bedroom and next to the bathroom."
  },
  "7128": {
    "question": "Question:what does the towel look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:hanged, fluffy and blue"
  },
  "7129": {
    "question": "Question:where is the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to the mirror and above the sink."
  },
  "7130": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the towel in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a restroom on the second floor."
  },
  "7131": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The restroom is at the left rear corner of the stairs."
  },
  "7132": {
    "question": "Question:what does the display look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black,rectangle,containing four parts"
  },
  "7133": {
    "question": "Question:where is the display?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of a pillow,on the left of a wooden desk,on the right of a painting"
  },
  "7134": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the display in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The display is in a big office."
  },
  "7135": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the display?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is in front of a corridor door,along the road linking the tea room with the restaurant."
  },
  "7136": {
    "question": "Question:what does the flower look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is colorful and blossoming."
  },
  "7137": {
    "question": "Question:where is the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is in the vase. The vase is on the table."
  },
  "7138": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the flower in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is placed between the sink and the toilet."
  },
  "7139": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a shower room, sink and toilet in the bathroom. "
  },
  "7140": {
    "question": "Question:what does the flower look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is colorful and blossoming."
  },
  "7141": {
    "question": "Question:where is the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is in the vase. The vase is on the table."
  },
  "7142": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the flower in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is placed between the sink and the toilet."
  },
  "7143": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a shower room, sink and toilet in the bathroom. "
  },
  "7144": {
    "question": "Question:what does the flower look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a blooming, white flower made of fiber."
  },
  "7145": {
    "question": "Question:where is the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on a table next to a porcelain."
  },
  "7146": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the flower in?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is in a living room.\n"
  },
  "7147": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a clean, tidy and spacious living room.\n"
  },
  "7148": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:green, normal size, soft"
  },
  "7149": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the woody table, next to the window"
  },
  "7150": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the study."
  },
  "7151": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to the bathroom and children's bedroom."
  },
  "7152": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:bloom, porcelain and white."
  },
  "7153": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is on the table, next to the telephone."
  },
  "7154": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Vase is in the living room."
  },
  "7155": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is close to the toilet and the bedroom."
  },
  "7156": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:bloom, porcelain and white."
  },
  "7157": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is on the table, next to the telephone."
  },
  "7158": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Vase is in the living room."
  },
  "7159": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is close to the toilet and the bedroom."
  },
  "7160": {
    "question": "Question:what does the Washstand look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white,small,clean"
  },
  "7161": {
    "question": "Question:where is the Washstand?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's under the mirror and in front of the bathtub"
  },
  "7162": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the Washstand in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in washroom"
  },
  "7163": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the Washstand?",
    "answer": "Answer:there is a bedroom across the corridor"
  },
  "7164": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a square, old, white table."
  },
  "7165": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a box of medicine and a charger on it."
  },
  "7166": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in the bedroom."
  },
  "7167": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is beside the corridor."
  },
  "7168": {
    "question": "Question:what does the book look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:yellow and blue,thick,cuboid"
  },
  "7169": {
    "question": "Question:where is the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:in the cabinet drawer and on the right side of the white division plate"
  },
  "7170": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the book in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The book is in a big meeting room."
  },
  "7171": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:The meeting room is by the side of the vast reading area and behind the restaurant."
  },
  "7172": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cylinder, big, white"
  },
  "7173": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a mirror, next to a bed"
  },
  "7174": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is placed in the corner of a small and bright bedroom."
  },
  "7175": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is next to a bashroom and connect with a balcony."
  },
  "7176": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A square wooden table surrounded by eight wooden chairs. "
  },
  "7177": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is on a carpet and has some flowers on it."
  },
  "7178": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is at the center of the room,beside a cooktop."
  },
  "7179": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a stair and near a door."
  },
  "7180": {
    "question": "Question:what does the painting look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle,black and yellow,paper"
  },
  "7181": {
    "question": "Question:where is the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the desk of the food bar,under two lights,next to two stacks of books"
  },
  "7182": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the painting in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is set in the food bar."
  },
  "7183": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is opposite to a row of booths and along a corridor connecting with the food bar and resting area."
  },
  "7184": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a large, wooden, square cabinet."
  },
  "7185": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's on a microwave oven and a pot."
  },
  "7186": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in the dining room."
  },
  "7187": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to a study and kitchen."
  },
  "7188": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chandelier look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:circular, transparent, bright"
  },
  "7189": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chandelier?",
    "answer": "Answer:between two same chandeliers, near a spinning bike"
  },
  "7190": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chandelier in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in a gymnasium."
  },
  "7191": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chandelier?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a spinning bike and a treadmill in this gymnasium."
  },
  "7192": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is h-shaped, wooden and blue."
  },
  "7193": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is on the right side of a white bed and near a beige and black lamp."
  },
  "7194": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in a bedroom on the second floor."
  },
  "7195": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is near a toiler and a corridor."
  },
  "7196": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mouse look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small,metal,black"
  },
  "7197": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mouse?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of two glowing screens and a dixie cup,surround by some documents"
  },
  "7198": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mouse in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mouse is in the 302 office."
  },
  "7199": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mouse?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is in front of a corridor door,along the road connecting the tea room and the restaurant."
  },
  "7200": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Black, short and heavy."
  },
  "7201": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is on the right of a yellow box and on a carpet."
  },
  "7202": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in a big and bright living room."
  },
  "7203": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in front of two doors and connects with a balcony via a glass door."
  },
  "7204": {
    "question": "Question:what does the switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, white, plastic"
  },
  "7205": {
    "question": "Question:where is the switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:between a door and a television, near a romote control."
  },
  "7206": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on the wall in the living room and a romote control on its right."
  },
  "7207": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room has a big television and a big sofa."
  },
  "7208": {
    "question": "Question:what does the switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A small subtle yellow swich."
  },
  "7209": {
    "question": "Question:where is the switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on the wall at the entrance of the room and is beside the door frame."
  },
  "7210": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the bedroom and near a desk."
  },
  "7211": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near another bedroom."
  },
  "7212": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Rectangular, rotatable\uff0cblack"
  },
  "7213": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is placed under a yellow table and behind an apple computer."
  },
  "7214": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is set in the hall."
  },
  "7215": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is placed near a big conference room and a tea room."
  },
  "7216": {
    "question": "Question:what does the switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:plastic, small "
  },
  "7217": {
    "question": "Question:where is the switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's a big painting on its left,  On it's right is a door."
  },
  "7218": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in a small bright bedroom."
  },
  "7219": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:It has the main bedroom on one side and the laundry on the other."
  },
  "7220": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cupboard look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle,brown,big"
  },
  "7221": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cupboard?",
    "answer": "Answer:the fridge is on the left side of it and wash basin on the right side fo it."
  },
  "7222": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cupboard in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in kitchen"
  },
  "7223": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cupboard?",
    "answer": "Answer:the entrance of dining room is on the right side of it."
  },
  "7224": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pool table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:blue and black,woolen"
  },
  "7225": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pool table?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's on a carpet and in front of a television."
  },
  "7226": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pool table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a living room on the first floor."
  },
  "7227": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pool table?",
    "answer": "Answer:the living room is near a dining room and a stair."
  },
  "7228": {
    "question": "Question:what does the computer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:thin,white,with a logo of apple"
  },
  "7229": {
    "question": "Question:where is the computer?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the left side of the counter,behind the document holder and in front of a chair"
  },
  "7230": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the computer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The computer is in the reception."
  },
  "7231": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the computer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The reception is opposite to the entrance,in front of the resting area and the food bar."
  },
  "7232": {
    "question": "Question:what does the shoebox look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:made of wood and there is a glass made surface, stands hard by the wall, its color is white"
  },
  "7233": {
    "question": "Question:where is the shoebox?",
    "answer": "Answer:there is a picture of leopard placed on the opposite wall, and a shoe like handicraft put on the shoebox "
  },
  "7234": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the shoebox in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The shoebox is placed in the corridor ,which is opposite a picture of leopard and under a shoe liked handicraft."
  },
  "7235": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the shoebox?",
    "answer": "Answer:The corridor is narrow which is to the hovel two small bedrooms and a detached bathroom and a small chair is close to the shoebox, which is put at the corner."
  },
  "7236": {
    "question": "Question:what does the fan look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Round, silvery, tall."
  },
  "7237": {
    "question": "Question:where is the fan?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is set in front of a stone pillar and next to a desk, two books."
  },
  "7238": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the fan in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The fan is located on a long corridor close to the wall."
  },
  "7239": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the fan?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area has lots of red benches."
  },
  "7240": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A wooden sofa upholstered with white cushion. "
  },
  "7241": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a carpet and a black sofa."
  },
  "7242": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is set close to the wall."
  },
  "7243": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a stair and entrances of bedrooms."
  },
  "7244": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Square, glass and clean."
  },
  "7245": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is near the washstand and sink."
  },
  "7246": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Mirror is in the bathroom."
  },
  "7247": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is near the bathroom and bedroom."
  },
  "7248": {
    "question": "Question:what does the seat look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:squared;brown; wooden;"
  },
  "7249": {
    "question": "Question:where is the seat?",
    "answer": "Answer:three cabinets around it;right faces a big box;"
  },
  "7250": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the seat in?",
    "answer": "Answer:in the center of the room"
  },
  "7251": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the seat?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the corridor of this men's changing room."
  },
  "7252": {
    "question": "Question:what does the glass look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A columnal transparent glass."
  },
  "7253": {
    "question": "Question:where is the glass?",
    "answer": "Answer:Situated at the second layer of the shelf which is on a desk,it is next to a picture and a silver statue."
  },
  "7254": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the glass in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is set in the dining room."
  },
  "7255": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the glass?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a stair and a kitchen."
  },
  "7256": {
    "question": "Question:what does the closet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:yellow, rectangle and woody"
  },
  "7257": {
    "question": "Question:where is the closet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to a door with a pot on it."
  },
  "7258": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the closet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a hall on the first floor."
  },
  "7259": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the closet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The hall is next to the chatting room."
  },
  "7260": {
    "question": "Question:what does the television look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Rectangular, metal and black."
  },
  "7261": {
    "question": "Question:where is the television?",
    "answer": "Answer:The television is opposite to a brown table and a green sofa and above a beige cabinet."
  },
  "7262": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the television in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The television is in a bedroom."
  },
  "7263": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the television?",
    "answer": "Answer:The television is near a corridor and a storage room."
  },
  "7264": {
    "question": "Question:what does the dispenser look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white; oblong; plastic;"
  },
  "7265": {
    "question": "Question:where is the dispenser?",
    "answer": "Answer:in the middle of a black cabinet and a small waste basket; near a cabinet with four lockers;"
  },
  "7266": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the dispenser in?",
    "answer": "Answer:along a long hallway of the men's changing room,against the wall"
  },
  "7267": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the dispenser?",
    "answer": "Answer:big enough for changing clothes;"
  },
  "7268": {
    "question": "Question:what does the decorations look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:colorful, flabellate, papery"
  },
  "7269": {
    "question": "Question:where is the decorations?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the wall, next to a massage bed"
  },
  "7270": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the decorations in?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a potted plant on its left in a small bedroom."
  },
  "7271": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the decorations?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom has a potted plant and connects with a gymnasium."
  },
  "7272": {
    "question": "Question:what does the flower look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Spherical, purple and small"
  },
  "7273": {
    "question": "Question:where is the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to the bed and on a cabinet."
  },
  "7274": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the flower in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a bedroom on the second floor."
  },
  "7275": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is facing the stairs."
  },
  "7276": {
    "question": "Question:what does the dustbin look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:On the ground , cylinder\uff0cwhite"
  },
  "7277": {
    "question": "Question:where is the dustbin?",
    "answer": "Answer:The dustbin is set under a yellow table and next to a black chair."
  },
  "7278": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the dustbin in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The dustbin is placed in the hall."
  },
  "7279": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the dustbin?",
    "answer": "Answer:The dustbin is set near the gate and the front desk."
  },
  "7280": {
    "question": "Question:what does the painting look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:square, black white and blue, Ink painting"
  },
  "7281": {
    "question": "Question:where is the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:Above the table, beside the door"
  },
  "7282": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the painting in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is hung on the wall of the bedroom"
  },
  "7283": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:The balcony is next to the bedroom. It is located in the second floor and there is a swimming pool downstairs. "
  },
  "7284": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:green, big"
  },
  "7285": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the white lamp and below the painting"
  },
  "7286": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the living room "
  },
  "7287": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the dining room and the staircase"
  },
  "7288": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soild, h-shaped and red and brown."
  },
  "7289": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is near a red sofa, in front of a black carbinet and near a wooden table."
  },
  "7290": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in a bedroom."
  },
  "7291": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is near a corridor and opposite to a room with a black carbinet."
  },
  "7292": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pillow look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A patterned blue pillow with flowers on it."
  },
  "7293": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:It lies on the head of the bed,below an air conditioning."
  },
  "7294": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pillow in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a bedroom."
  },
  "7295": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a toilet."
  },
  "7296": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:soft\u3001long and it's a lounge chair"
  },
  "7297": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:there is a same chair near it and it's next to a small table"
  },
  "7298": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in the corner of the balcony on the second floor "
  },
  "7299": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:there is a study room the balcony and there is a stair in the study room"
  },
  "7300": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pillow look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A small yellow pillow on a white leather sofa."
  },
  "7301": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near the projector and another yellow pillow."
  },
  "7302": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pillow in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is the closest yellow pillow to a narrow arching door in the living room. "
  },
  "7303": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a carpet."
  },
  "7304": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden and glass, square, white and black"
  },
  "7305": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the wall, facing the stairs, among six pictures and first from left"
  },
  "7306": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is set on the corridor.\n"
  },
  "7307": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The corridor is on the second floor, has two stairs and some rooms beside it."
  },
  "7308": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:grey, cloth and metal,short"
  },
  "7309": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:facing the table on the left which is away from the screen,close to the passageway in the middle and close to the screen"
  },
  "7310": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is in a vast reading hall."
  },
  "7311": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The reading hall is behind the restaurant and near a meeting room and some boothes."
  },
  "7312": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:lying, small, soft"
  },
  "7313": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:between a big sofa and the bedroom, near the kitchen"
  },
  "7314": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is set at a corner of the living room, on the second floor."
  },
  "7315": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is next to the kitchen and the bedrooms."
  },
  "7316": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:lying, small, soft"
  },
  "7317": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:between a big sofa and the bedroom, near the kitchen"
  },
  "7318": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is set at a corner of the living room, on the second floor."
  },
  "7319": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is next to the kitchen and the bedrooms."
  },
  "7320": {
    "question": "Question:what does the painting look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Medium size, soild and orange."
  },
  "7321": {
    "question": "Question:where is the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is set on the right side of a black and white painting and on the left side of a painting."
  },
  "7322": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the painting in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is in a corridor on the second floor."
  },
  "7323": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is near a bedroom."
  },
  "7324": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is large, white and rectangular."
  },
  "7325": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is under the sink and towel."
  },
  "7326": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is under the sink and towel."
  },
  "7327": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is under the sink and towel."
  },
  "7328": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White, metal and plastic, round"
  },
  "7329": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is on the bedside table, next to the bed\n"
  },
  "7330": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer: lamp in the bedroom"
  },
  "7331": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer: lamp at the end of the corridor on the second floor on the first floor living room"
  },
  "7332": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, brown, wood"
  },
  "7333": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:under a plate, under a lamp"
  },
  "7334": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is placed in a dining room with wood floor."
  },
  "7335": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The dining is next to a kitchen on the first floor and there is a road outside."
  },
  "7336": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, small, colorful"
  },
  "7337": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a door, on a wall"
  },
  "7338": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is hanging in the corridor."
  },
  "7339": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:This corridor connects with a study and is on the first floor."
  },
  "7340": {
    "question": "Question:what does the box look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, black, rectangular"
  },
  "7341": {
    "question": "Question:where is the box?",
    "answer": "Answer:under a printer, in front of some photos"
  },
  "7342": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the box in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in a neat living room."
  },
  "7343": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the box?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a television and a DVD in the front of the living room."
  },
  "7344": {
    "question": "Question:what does the light look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Glowing, plastic and attached to a fan"
  },
  "7345": {
    "question": "Question:where is the light?",
    "answer": "Answer:The light is attached to a fan hanging on the roof."
  },
  "7346": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the light in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a bedroom and above the bed."
  },
  "7347": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the light?",
    "answer": "Answer:This bedroom is located at the end of the right turn on the second floor, opposite a storage room."
  },
  "7348": {
    "question": "Question:what does the floor lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown,metal,tall"
  },
  "7349": {
    "question": "Question:where is the floor lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a bed and a mirror"
  },
  "7350": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the floor lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a bedroom with a washroom on the second floor."
  },
  "7351": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the floor lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:the bedroom is near a corridor and a living room"
  },
  "7352": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stone look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:BIg,gray,hard."
  },
  "7353": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stone?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stone is placed on a tall yellow stool in front of a television."
  },
  "7354": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stone in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stone is set in a tearoom."
  },
  "7355": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stone?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stone is placed near a reading room and the hall."
  },
  "7356": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bell look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:square,metal,fragile"
  },
  "7357": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bell?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's hang on a white pillar and near a mirror."
  },
  "7358": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bell in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a living room on the second floor."
  },
  "7359": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bell?",
    "answer": "Answer:the living room is next to a balcony and a stair."
  },
  "7360": {
    "question": "Question:what does the outlet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:square, white, plastic"
  },
  "7361": {
    "question": "Question:where is the outlet?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a tap on its left, and it face the big cabinet. It's installed with the switch."
  },
  "7362": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the outlet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's installed in a  open kitchen."
  },
  "7363": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the outlet?",
    "answer": "Answer: Here you can see the swimming pool, reception area and a wicket."
  },
  "7364": {
    "question": "Question:what does the monitor look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, black, small"
  },
  "7365": {
    "question": "Question:where is the monitor?",
    "answer": "Answer:on a microwave, next to a cupboard"
  },
  "7366": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the monitor in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The monitor is in the corner of a kitchen with wood floor."
  },
  "7367": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the monitor?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to a small storeroom and a big dining room on the first floor."
  },
  "7368": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:light blue, rectangular, cloth"
  },
  "7369": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the left of the small table, next to the glass door, under the glass window"
  },
  "7370": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set in a sunny balcony."
  },
  "7371": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The balcony is next to the washroom, next to the roof and outside the bedroom."
  },
  "7372": {
    "question": "Question:what does the glass look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Cylindrical, transparent, big"
  },
  "7373": {
    "question": "Question:where is the glass?",
    "answer": "Answer:The glass is placed on a brown table surrounded by six transparent chairs, and next to a television."
  },
  "7374": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the glass in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The glass is placed in a small conference room."
  },
  "7375": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the glass?",
    "answer": "Answer:The glass is set near a bigger conference room and next to the hall."
  },
  "7376": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cylindrical, middle, white"
  },
  "7377": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the left of the bed, on the nightstand, next to the window"
  },
  "7378": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is set in the bright and spacious bedroom."
  },
  "7379": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is on the first floor and next to the kitchen."
  },
  "7380": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:woody, round and brown"
  },
  "7381": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is hanging on the wall above the basin and under the light."
  },
  "7382": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a restroom on the second floor."
  },
  "7383": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The restroom is at the left rear corner of the stairs."
  },
  "7384": {
    "question": "Question:what does the telephone look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Quadrangular, soild and black."
  },
  "7385": {
    "question": "Question:where is the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:The telephone is near a green bed and a tall lamp."
  },
  "7386": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the telephone in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The telephone is in a bedroom."
  },
  "7387": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:The telephone is near a corridor and a toilet."
  },
  "7388": {
    "question": "Question:what does the fridge look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A grey,double-door,tall refrigerator."
  },
  "7389": {
    "question": "Question:where is the fridge?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to a tall white cabinet and faces a white table."
  },
  "7390": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the fridge in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is situated near a door."
  },
  "7391": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the fridge?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near two glass doors and close to the dining room. "
  },
  "7392": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:long; with metal frames; with wooden armrests;"
  },
  "7393": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the door and on the left of a small wooden table;"
  },
  "7394": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:faced with a huge mosaic post in the hall."
  },
  "7395": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:a big hall with a big bathing pool;"
  },
  "7396": {
    "question": "Question:what does the black board look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Rectangular,back,wooden"
  },
  "7397": {
    "question": "Question:where is the black board?",
    "answer": "Answer:The black board is placed on a brown box  and against a wall."
  },
  "7398": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the black board in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The black board is placed in the tearoom."
  },
  "7399": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the black board?",
    "answer": "Answer:The black board is placed next two stairs and near a reading room."
  },
  "7400": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Woody, rectangle and glass-coverd"
  },
  "7401": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed opposite a cabinet and hung on the wall."
  },
  "7402": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the hall on the second floor and placed on the far right side."
  },
  "7403": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The hall is on the second floor."
  },
  "7404": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:soft,cuboid,green and grey "
  },
  "7405": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:leaning against the painting wall,opposite to the white pillar, on the left side of the path"
  },
  "7406": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is at the end of the corridor and in the rest area."
  },
  "7407": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is opposite to the locker room and the tea room,sharing a corridor to the exit and at a corner."
  },
  "7408": {
    "question": "Question:what does the washstand look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white,small size,smooth"
  },
  "7409": {
    "question": "Question:where is the washstand?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a glass bottle and  near a woolen pillar."
  },
  "7410": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the washstand in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's on the dining table in a dining room on the first floor."
  },
  "7411": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the washstand?",
    "answer": "Answer:the dining room is near a living room and a stair."
  },
  "7412": {
    "question": "Question:what does the photo look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Papery, colorful and small."
  },
  "7413": {
    "question": "Question:where is the photo?",
    "answer": "Answer:The photo is set on the right side of a yellow model car and above a colorful photo."
  },
  "7414": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the photo in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The photo is in a bedroom."
  },
  "7415": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the photo?",
    "answer": "Answer:The photo is near a toilet."
  },
  "7416": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:square, wooden and glass, white and black"
  },
  "7417": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the wall, facing the stairs, among six pictures and sixth from left"
  },
  "7418": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is set on the corridor."
  },
  "7419": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The corridor is on the second floor, has some rooms and two stairs beside it."
  },
  "7420": {
    "question": "Question:what does the towel look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, gray, soft"
  },
  "7421": {
    "question": "Question:where is the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:Hang on the wall, over the toilet"
  },
  "7422": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the towel in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is settled in the toilet."
  },
  "7423": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The toilet is settled in the corner of a bedroom."
  },
  "7424": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:narrow;covered by white quilts and a grey cushion; used for massage;"
  },
  "7425": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:near two wall lamps; beside a brown cabinet;"
  },
  "7426": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:faced with the sink in the middle of two walls;"
  },
  "7427": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:a room with single  small bed and wooden floors;"
  },
  "7428": {
    "question": "Question:what does the television look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black,hanged on the wall and on standby"
  },
  "7429": {
    "question": "Question:where is the television?",
    "answer": "Answer:The television is over a fireplace and under a light"
  },
  "7430": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the television in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The television is hanged on the center of the wall of the room"
  },
  "7431": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the television?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a corridor outside the room"
  },
  "7432": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Big, white and red and cuboid."
  },
  "7433": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is set near two black screens, below two paintings and near a black fitness equipment."
  },
  "7434": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is in a bedroom."
  },
  "7435": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is near a corridor."
  },
  "7436": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Leather, soild and green."
  },
  "7437": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is next to a brown table, on the opposite side of a black television and next to a white and blue bed."
  },
  "7438": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in a bedroom."
  },
  "7439": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is near a corridor and a storage room."
  },
  "7440": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Metal, silver grey, tall feet"
  },
  "7441": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:In front the stool  is a dining table with a set of cutlery on it"
  },
  "7442": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:the stool In the corridor connecting the kitchen to the living room"
  },
  "7443": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The back of the stool  is the living room and the front is the kitchen"
  },
  "7444": {
    "question": "Question:what does the swimming pool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:ceramic,big and smooth"
  },
  "7445": {
    "question": "Question:where is the swimming pool?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a lawn and some chairs under the sunshine."
  },
  "7446": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the swimming pool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's on a open-balcony on the second floor."
  },
  "7447": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the swimming pool?",
    "answer": "Answer:the open-balcont is near a living room and a rest room."
  },
  "7448": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:elliptical, big, white"
  },
  "7449": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:on a long table, next to a book"
  },
  "7450": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is in the middle of a bright and white living room."
  },
  "7451": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is next to a corridor on the first floor."
  },
  "7452": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, oval and light"
  },
  "7453": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed on a smal white cabinet and next to a white candle."
  },
  "7454": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:\nIt is in a bedroom on the second floor."
  },
  "7455": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is at the left rear corner of the stairs."
  },
  "7456": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Clean, cotton and white"
  },
  "7457": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:It has a blanket and some pillows on it."
  },
  "7458": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed beside a cabinet and between a door and a lamp."
  },
  "7459": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:This bedroom is located at the end of the right turn on the second floor, opposite a storage room."
  },
  "7460": {
    "question": "Question:what does the drawer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Black, wooden and cuboid."
  },
  "7461": {
    "question": "Question:where is the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is under a vase and near a beautiful bed."
  },
  "7462": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the drawer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is in a small attic, which is on the second floor."
  },
  "7463": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The attic is above the living room, and connects with a staircase."
  },
  "7464": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black,tall,plastic and metal,with five wheels and  two handrails    "
  },
  "7465": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of the chair,on the left side of the room,in the second seat from left to right"
  },
  "7466": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in a big simple shared office with the number 363."
  },
  "7467": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is along the road to the stairs of the exit and around the corner of a junction of three roads."
  },
  "7468": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cloth, small, white"
  },
  "7469": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a table, facing a bed"
  },
  "7470": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is settled in the corner of a bedroom on the second floor."
  },
  "7471": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is next to a long corridor and has a tiny balcony."
  },
  "7472": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Red, conical and and small."
  },
  "7473": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is set on a yellow and white table and next to a black television."
  },
  "7474": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is in a bedroom."
  },
  "7475": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is near a corridor and a living room."
  },
  "7476": {
    "question": "Question:what does the photo look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Brown and colorful, soild and rectangular."
  },
  "7477": {
    "question": "Question:where is the photo?",
    "answer": "Answer:The photo is near a brown table surrounded by four brown chairs, near a small vase and near two paintings."
  },
  "7478": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the photo in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The photo is in a living room."
  },
  "7479": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the photo?",
    "answer": "Answer:The photo is near a bedroom."
  },
  "7480": {
    "question": "Question:what does the plant look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:short,green,with standing leaves"
  },
  "7481": {
    "question": "Question:where is the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a short chair,in front of the pillar and a book shelf"
  },
  "7482": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the plant in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The plant is in a large restaurant."
  },
  "7483": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:The resturant is opposite to the service counter and near the corridor to the meeting room."
  },
  "7484": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bottle look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:transparent, glass and fragile."
  },
  "7485": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bottle?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bottle is near a picture and near a glass bottle and a slaver."
  },
  "7486": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bottle in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bottle is in a big living room."
  },
  "7487": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bottle?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is next to a dining room and leads to outdoors via a door."
  },
  "7488": {
    "question": "Question:what does the paintings look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wall-mounted, rectangular, colorful"
  },
  "7489": {
    "question": "Question:where is the paintings?",
    "answer": "Answer:hung on the wall, above the cabinet"
  },
  "7490": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the paintings in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It located in the corridor."
  },
  "7491": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the paintings?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the bathroom and the study."
  },
  "7492": {
    "question": "Question:what does the Sprinkler look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:gray,mental"
  },
  "7493": {
    "question": "Question:where is the Sprinkler?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's above a water tap and near a washstand."
  },
  "7494": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the Sprinkler in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a washroom on the second floor."
  },
  "7495": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the Sprinkler?",
    "answer": "Answer:the washroom is near a stair ,a living room and a rest room."
  },
  "7496": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Wooden, brown and tall."
  },
  "7497": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is set near a brown and white table under a computer and near several pictures."
  },
  "7498": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is in a study."
  },
  "7499": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is near a toilet and a dining room."
  },
  "7500": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pillow look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cream color, small, cloth"
  },
  "7501": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the sofa, among three pillows and on the left of them"
  },
  "7502": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pillow in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The pillow is set in the bright and spacious livingroom."
  },
  "7503": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:The livingroom is on the first floor and next to the kitchen."
  },
  "7504": {
    "question": "Question:what does the drawer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is large, wooden and white."
  },
  "7505": {
    "question": "Question:where is the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is under the table and next to the door."
  },
  "7506": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the drawer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is in the kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "7507": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is under the table and next to the door."
  },
  "7508": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, brown, stable "
  },
  "7509": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:between two chairs, near the decorations"
  },
  "7510": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is put in a small bar."
  },
  "7511": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area has a large cabinet and a wide bar counter."
  },
  "7512": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cylindrical, green and white"
  },
  "7513": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the bed and another lamp with the same shape and color, next to the window with red curtains"
  },
  "7514": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is in the master bedroom."
  },
  "7515": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The master bedroom is next to the stairs with a bathroom and a cloakroom in it."
  },
  "7516": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is h-shaped, black and beige and small."
  },
  "7517": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is near a beige leather sofa and on the right side of the black bookshelf in the direction facing the wooden doors."
  },
  "7518": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in a living room."
  },
  "7519": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is on the opposite side of a atr stduio."
  },
  "7520": {
    "question": "Question:what does the laundry basket look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown, rectangular, hollow"
  },
  "7521": {
    "question": "Question:where is the laundry basket?",
    "answer": "Answer:against a wall, next to a wardrobe."
  },
  "7522": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the laundry basket in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The laundry basket is in a man washroom."
  },
  "7523": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the laundry basket?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area has a door and connects with a gymnasium."
  },
  "7524": {
    "question": "Question:what does the power switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Rectangle , small and plastic"
  },
  "7525": {
    "question": "Question:where is the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:This switch is next to a door, directly above a wooden barrel."
  },
  "7526": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the power switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is set in a corridor at the door of a house."
  },
  "7527": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is set beside the door of a kitchen."
  },
  "7528": {
    "question": "Question:what does the computer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:a quadrate and metal screen with a argent color "
  },
  "7529": {
    "question": "Question:where is the computer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The computer is in front of a black chair,next to a bottle and a lamp and above the white table."
  },
  "7530": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the computer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The computer is in a office."
  },
  "7531": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the computer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The computer is in a office which is on the side of the corridor and behind a glass wall."
  },
  "7532": {
    "question": "Question:what does the computer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:a quadrate and metal screen with a argent color "
  },
  "7533": {
    "question": "Question:where is the computer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The computer is in front of a black chair,next to a bottle and a lamp and above the white table."
  },
  "7534": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the computer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The computer is in an office whose number is 359."
  },
  "7535": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the computer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The computer is in a office which is on the side of the corridor and behind a glass wall."
  },
  "7536": {
    "question": "Question:what does the computer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:an quadrate and metal screen with a argent color "
  },
  "7537": {
    "question": "Question:where is the computer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The computer is in front of a black chair,next to a bottle and a lamp and above the white table."
  },
  "7538": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the computer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The computer is in an office whose number is 359."
  },
  "7539": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the computer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The computer is in a office which is on the side of the corridor and behind a glass wall."
  },
  "7540": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, irregular, stable"
  },
  "7541": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of another chair, in front of stairs"
  },
  "7542": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is located in a bar."
  },
  "7543": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bar has a wide bar counter and two elevators."
  },
  "7544": {
    "question": "Question:what does the door look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Square, glass and clean."
  },
  "7545": {
    "question": "Question:where is the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:The door is close to the sofa and chair."
  },
  "7546": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the door in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The door is between the living room and the balcony."
  },
  "7547": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:The door is close to the living room and balcony."
  },
  "7548": {
    "question": "Question:what does the tap look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:silver, iron, slender"
  },
  "7549": {
    "question": "Question:where is the tap?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are two washing machines nearby, Below the tap is a cabinet"
  },
  "7550": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the tap in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is installed in a small laundry."
  },
  "7551": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the tap?",
    "answer": "Answer: The laundry is flanked by bedrooms, and there is a chandelier in front"
  },
  "7552": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sculpture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cylindrical, grey and man-like"
  },
  "7553": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sculpture?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed on the windowsill and close to the window."
  },
  "7554": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sculpture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a chatting room on the first floor."
  },
  "7555": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sculpture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chatting room is next to the hall."
  },
  "7556": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:sponge,grey and single."
  },
  "7557": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is close to the bed and the flower."
  },
  "7558": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in the bedroom."
  },
  "7559": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:Behind the chair is balcony and the living room is near the sofa."
  },
  "7560": {
    "question": "Question:what does the towel look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Cloth, blue and white and solid."
  },
  "7561": {
    "question": "Question:where is the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is near a white sink and near some mirrors."
  },
  "7562": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the towel in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is in a toilet."
  },
  "7563": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is near a bedroom and a corridor."
  },
  "7564": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:tall, thin, filmy"
  },
  "7565": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:face a woody bed, set on a armoire"
  },
  "7566": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is in the bedroom."
  },
  "7567": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer: The bedroom is next to the stairs and the master bedroom."
  },
  "7568": {
    "question": "Question:what does the spinning bike look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:gray, black, heavy, metallic"
  },
  "7569": {
    "question": "Question:where is the spinning bike?",
    "answer": "Answer:between a swivel chair and a treadmill, near a big mirror"
  },
  "7570": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the spinning bike in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is put in a gymnasium."
  },
  "7571": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the spinning bike?",
    "answer": "Answer:It connects with a man washroom and a woman washroom."
  },
  "7572": {
    "question": "Question:what does the power switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is plastic, small and white."
  },
  "7573": {
    "question": "Question:where is the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is on the wall and beside the door."
  },
  "7574": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the power switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is in the utility room."
  },
  "7575": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is on the wall and beside the door."
  },
  "7576": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, cloth, white"
  },
  "7577": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:facing the washroom and second from left, on the carpet, around the table"
  },
  "7578": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set in the middle of the bright dining room."
  },
  "7579": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The dining room is next to the livingroom and kitchen ,facing the washroom and next to the balcony."
  },
  "7580": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white and gray,big,smooth,made of a big cabinet and 4 small cabinets"
  },
  "7581": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a room and a bench."
  },
  "7582": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a storage room on the first floor."
  },
  "7583": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:the storage room is in the end of a corridor,which links a living room and the storage room."
  },
  "7584": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:plaid, small , soft"
  },
  "7585": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the staircase and the doors"
  },
  "7586": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the living room"
  },
  "7587": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is on the second floor and next to the staircase and corridor."
  },
  "7588": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Oval, medium size and transparent."
  },
  "7589": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is set between a beige sofa and a black and gray sofa, and in front of a black stove."
  },
  "7590": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is in a living room."
  },
  "7591": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is near a dining room."
  },
  "7592": {
    "question": "Question:what does the telephone look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Quadrangular, metal and plastic and black."
  },
  "7593": {
    "question": "Question:where is the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:The telephone is on the left side of a gray and black bed and near a white and brown lamp and a brown and black drawer."
  },
  "7594": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the telephone in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The telephone is in a bedroom."
  },
  "7595": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:The telephone is near a corridor and a living room."
  },
  "7596": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A yellow wooden chair with a backrest."
  },
  "7597": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is between two other chairs with black color,which are as big as it."
  },
  "7598": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It lies front of fake grass and a glass embeded in the stone wall."
  },
  "7599": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near places which are used to cook and used to eat."
  },
  "7600": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is h-shaped, wooden and red and brown."
  },
  "7601": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set before a wooden brown desk under a ceiling lamp with yellow light and opposite to a beige floriated sofa in the living room."
  },
  "7602": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in a study."
  },
  "7603": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is near a living room."
  },
  "7604": {
    "question": "Question:what does the clock look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:round, steel and yellow"
  },
  "7605": {
    "question": "Question:where is the clock?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed on a shelf next to the refrigerator."
  },
  "7606": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the clock in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "7607": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the clock?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to the chatting room and the door."
  },
  "7608": {
    "question": "Question:what does the tap look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black, metal and with two switches."
  },
  "7609": {
    "question": "Question:where is the tap?",
    "answer": "Answer:The tap is in front of a big mirror and under four lights."
  },
  "7610": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the tap in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The tap is in a bathroom."
  },
  "7611": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the tap?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area connects with a bedroom and near a toilet."
  },
  "7612": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is small, rectangular and white."
  },
  "7613": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is under the table and sink."
  },
  "7614": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is in the kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "7615": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is under the table and sink."
  },
  "7616": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:metal and plastic,black,tall"
  },
  "7617": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of the desk in the innermost position,facing the painting of scissors and in front of the green file holder"
  },
  "7618": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in a small office."
  },
  "7619": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is at the corner of a junction of three roads and next to the corridor door."
  },
  "7620": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soild, beige and brown and umbelliform."
  },
  "7621": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is on the left side of a blue and white bed, on a beige drawer and near a black telephone."
  },
  "7622": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is in a bedroom."
  },
  "7623": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is near a storage room."
  },
  "7624": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a large, square white cabinet."
  },
  "7625": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is beside two chairs."
  },
  "7626": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in the dining room."
  },
  "7627": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to a study and kitchen."
  },
  "7628": {
    "question": "Question:what does the drawer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white; no handles; wide;"
  },
  "7629": {
    "question": "Question:where is the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:faces a brown bed and a holder;below a mirror with golden frames;"
  },
  "7630": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the drawer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the right side of a table with a sink."
  },
  "7631": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:a room with two identical beds and two different sinks;"
  },
  "7632": {
    "question": "Question:what does the window look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:closed,medium-size and transparent"
  },
  "7633": {
    "question": "Question:where is the window?",
    "answer": "Answer:close to the curtain and on the right of the television"
  },
  "7634": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the window in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's on the left side of the painting and on the right side of the television."
  },
  "7635": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the window?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's on opposite of the corridor"
  },
  "7636": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden and meltallic, rectangular, brown"
  },
  "7637": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:under the big table, in front of the stairs, among four stools and forth from left"
  },
  "7638": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is set in the middle of the kitchen."
  },
  "7639": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is facing the stairs, on the third floor and next to the livingroom and balcony.\n"
  },
  "7640": {
    "question": "Question:what does the potted plant look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:potted, round and green"
  },
  "7641": {
    "question": "Question:where is the potted plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is close to the fence and third closest to a door."
  },
  "7642": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the potted plant in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in front of the house."
  },
  "7643": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the potted plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is outside the house and in front of the gate."
  },
  "7644": {
    "question": "Question:what does the drawer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is wooden, brown and small."
  },
  "7645": {
    "question": "Question:where is the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a shelf and some bottles of wine above the drawer."
  },
  "7646": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the drawer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is placed below a shelf and some bottles of wine."
  },
  "7647": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a pot of flower, desk and some chairs on the opposite."
  },
  "7648": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is empty, ceramic and white."
  },
  "7649": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is below the mirror next to the toilet."
  },
  "7650": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is below the mirror next to the toilet."
  },
  "7651": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a mirror, toilet and sink in the toilet."
  },
  "7652": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, gray and white"
  },
  "7653": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are no small pillows on the chair, Facing two beach chairs."
  },
  "7654": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in a second-floor balcony, which facing the main bedroom."
  },
  "7655": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The balcony is on the second floor of the villa, directly below the garden. "
  },
  "7656": {
    "question": "Question:what does the screen look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black,thin,oblong,electric"
  },
  "7657": {
    "question": "Question:where is the screen?",
    "answer": "Answer:The screen is on the right of a gift bag and on the right of the phone and above the dustbin."
  },
  "7658": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the screen in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the number 361 small and single office."
  },
  "7659": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the screen?",
    "answer": "Answer:This room is along the corridor leading to the exit and around the corner of a junction of three roads."
  },
  "7660": {
    "question": "Question:what does the wall look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white"
  },
  "7661": {
    "question": "Question:where is the wall?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the staircase, next to the door which outside is the garden"
  },
  "7662": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the wall in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the stair."
  },
  "7663": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the wall?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the kitchen and the garden."
  },
  "7664": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown and blue, with thin table legs, it's the shape of rectangle"
  },
  "7665": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are eight chairs put surrounding the table, and it is put close to a big mirror "
  },
  "7666": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is put close to the glass door in the dining room ,which is next to big mirror."
  },
  "7667": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a big mirror put  on the wall of dining room, and it attached with two glass door."
  },
  "7668": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soild, rectangular and long."
  },
  "7669": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is on the right side of a same red sofa and in front of a window with red curtains."
  },
  "7670": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in a rest room."
  },
  "7671": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is near a bedroom with a red bed and opposite to a white corridor."
  },
  "7672": {
    "question": "Question:what does the flower look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is small, white and tall."
  },
  "7673": {
    "question": "Question:where is the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is beside the pool and mirror."
  },
  "7674": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the flower in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is in the bathroom."
  },
  "7675": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is beside the pool and mirror."
  },
  "7676": {
    "question": "Question:what does the power switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is rectangular, small and white."
  },
  "7677": {
    "question": "Question:where is the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is on the wall and beside the door."
  },
  "7678": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the power switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is in the bedroom."
  },
  "7679": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is on the wall and beside the door."
  },
  "7680": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, wooden and metallic, brown\n"
  },
  "7681": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:under the stone table, next to the glass door, among three stools and first from right"
  },
  "7682": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is set in the spacious kitchen."
  },
  "7683": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is on the third floor, next to the livingroom, next to the balcony."
  },
  "7684": {
    "question": "Question:what does the closestool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, medium, orbicular"
  },
  "7685": {
    "question": "Question:where is the closestool?",
    "answer": "Answer:face a door, next to a washbasin and towel"
  },
  "7686": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the closestool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The closestool is in the bathroom."
  },
  "7687": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the closestool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathroom is next to the stairs and six bedrooms on the third floor."
  },
  "7688": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A white metal sink."
  },
  "7689": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on a granite board and under a mirror."
  },
  "7690": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a bathroom where the wall is yellow and brown."
  },
  "7691": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near the bedroom ."
  },
  "7692": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Medium size, soild and beige."
  },
  "7693": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in front of the window, on the opposite side of the table under the wooden box and near a beige leather sofa."
  },
  "7694": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is at the corner of a living room."
  },
  "7695": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is on the opposite side of a studio as well as a study."
  },
  "7696": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, ceramic, white and brown"
  },
  "7697": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:facing the stairs, behind the oven"
  },
  "7698": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is set in the middle of the kitchen."
  },
  "7699": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is on the third floor, next to the balcony and facing the stairs."
  },
  "7700": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden, brown and with four legs."
  },
  "7701": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is next to a big bed and near two sockets."
  },
  "7702": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is in a small bedroom."
  },
  "7703": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom where can see a kitchen and a stairs leads to a utility room via a ladder."
  },
  "7704": {
    "question": "Question:what does the globe look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:blue,medium-size,made by metal"
  },
  "7705": {
    "question": "Question:where is the globe?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's on the table and next to the chair"
  },
  "7706": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the globe in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in study."
  },
  "7707": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the globe?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's dinning room outside the study."
  },
  "7708": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, L-figurate"
  },
  "7709": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a picture on the back and a TV in front of it"
  },
  "7710": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is put on the reception area."
  },
  "7711": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area faces the open kitchen, next to the pool, and dinning table on the other side."
  },
  "7712": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Red chair with a hairy cushion."
  },
  "7713": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is near a round table and in front of some frame and paintings."
  },
  "7714": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set in a big and bright living room."
  },
  "7715": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in front of a big white fireplace and its left has two black sofas"
  },
  "7716": {
    "question": "Question:what does the screen look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Small, metal and black."
  },
  "7717": {
    "question": "Question:where is the screen?",
    "answer": "Answer:The screen is settled on a brown table, near a white typewriter and near a black fitness equipment."
  },
  "7718": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the screen in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The screen is set in a bedroom."
  },
  "7719": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the screen?",
    "answer": "Answer:The screen is near a corridor."
  },
  "7720": {
    "question": "Question:what does the clock look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:round,sharp and red"
  },
  "7721": {
    "question": "Question:where is the clock?",
    "answer": "Answer:above some red books on the locker,on the right side of the display and on the left of a pillar"
  },
  "7722": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the clock in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The clock is placed in the reading area."
  },
  "7723": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the clock?",
    "answer": "Answer:The reading room is across to the number 05 meeting office and some boothes and behind the restaurant."
  },
  "7724": {
    "question": "Question:what does the tap look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Curved, metal, smooth lines"
  },
  "7725": {
    "question": "Question:where is the tap?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a flower and a metal bottle next to it"
  },
  "7726": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the tap in?",
    "answer": "Answer:tap in the toilet"
  },
  "7727": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the tap?",
    "answer": "Answer:tap between living room staircase and bedroom"
  },
  "7728": {
    "question": "Question:what does the towel look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:soft, brown and oblong."
  },
  "7729": {
    "question": "Question:where is the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is near a vase and in front of a big mirror."
  },
  "7730": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the towel in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is in a bathroom."
  },
  "7731": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area connects with a bedroom and near a toilet."
  },
  "7732": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden, quaint and delicate."
  },
  "7733": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a desk and a bench near the chair."
  },
  "7734": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on an area under the stairs."
  },
  "7735": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is across from a fireplace and near a kitchen."
  },
  "7736": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Big, rectangular and brown."
  },
  "7737": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is surrounded by eight brown chairs and under a vase."
  },
  "7738": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is in a dining room."
  },
  "7739": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is near a kitchen."
  },
  "7740": {
    "question": "Question:what does the toilet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, white, ceramic"
  },
  "7741": {
    "question": "Question:where is the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the washstand, under the photo"
  },
  "7742": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the toilet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The toilet is located in the washroom. "
  },
  "7743": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washroom is inside the office, which is next to the stairs and livingroom and on the first floor."
  },
  "7744": {
    "question": "Question:what does the penholder look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, hollow, straight                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                  "
  },
  "7745": {
    "question": "Question:where is the penholder?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a box, in front of a door"
  },
  "7746": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the penholder in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The penholder is put on the table in a study."
  },
  "7747": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the penholder?",
    "answer": "Answer:The study is on the first floor and next to a living room and a bedroom."
  },
  "7748": {
    "question": "Question:what does the kettle look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:steel, cylindrical and sliver"
  },
  "7749": {
    "question": "Question:where is the kettle?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed on a cabinet and close to a pot."
  },
  "7750": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the kettle in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "7751": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the kettle?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to the chatting room and the door."
  },
  "7752": {
    "question": "Question:what does the computer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Rectangular, black screen, hard"
  },
  "7753": {
    "question": "Question:where is the computer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The computer is placed on a yellow table and in front of a black chair,next to a white earphone."
  },
  "7754": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the computer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The computer is placed in the hall."
  },
  "7755": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the computer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The computer is placed near a tea room and a big conference room."
  },
  "7756": {
    "question": "Question:what does the box look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Big, lying flat, black."
  },
  "7757": {
    "question": "Question:where is the box?",
    "answer": "Answer:The box is placed on a yellow box next to a corner and a tripod."
  },
  "7758": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the box in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The box is placed in the hall."
  },
  "7759": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the box?",
    "answer": "Answer:The box is set next to a wall and near the gate."
  },
  "7760": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Medium size, concave and gray."
  },
  "7761": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is set in a big table and opposite to a induction cooker."
  },
  "7762": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is in a kitchen."
  },
  "7763": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is near a dining room."
  },
  "7764": {
    "question": "Question:what does the drawer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a white, rectangular, small drawershu."
  },
  "7765": {
    "question": "Question:where is the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is directly below a desk, opposite a cabinet.\n"
  },
  "7766": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the drawer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a study."
  },
  "7767": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to a kitchen and dining room."
  },
  "7768": {
    "question": "Question:what does the shutter look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Medium size, white and soild."
  },
  "7769": {
    "question": "Question:where is the shutter?",
    "answer": "Answer:The shutter is near a towel and a table with two white sinks."
  },
  "7770": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the shutter in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The shutter is in a bathroom."
  },
  "7771": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the shutter?",
    "answer": "Answer:The shutter is near a bedroom."
  },
  "7772": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bush look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:green plants,lush"
  },
  "7773": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bush?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a white bench a roiling.it's also in front of  flower bed but  far away from the balcony"
  },
  "7774": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bush in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's  in the corner of the garden with a flower bed on the second floor"
  },
  "7775": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bush?",
    "answer": "Answer:the garden is near a balcony which is near a study room with a stair in the corner"
  },
  "7776": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bush look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:green plants,lush"
  },
  "7777": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bush?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a white bench a roiling.it's also in front of  flower bed but  far away from the balcony"
  },
  "7778": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bush in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's  in the corner of the garden with a flower bed on the second floor"
  },
  "7779": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bush?",
    "answer": "Answer:the garden is near a balcony which is near a study room with a stair in the corner"
  },
  "7780": {
    "question": "Question:what does the loudspeaker box look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Black,cuboid, metal"
  },
  "7781": {
    "question": "Question:where is the loudspeaker box?",
    "answer": "Answer:The loudspeaker box is set on the ground and next to a tripod ."
  },
  "7782": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the loudspeaker box in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The loudspeaker box is set in the hall."
  },
  "7783": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the loudspeaker box?",
    "answer": "Answer:The loudspeaker box is placed near a wall and the gate."
  },
  "7784": {
    "question": "Question:what does the washbasin look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white , big , rectangular"
  },
  "7785": {
    "question": "Question:where is the washbasin?",
    "answer": "Answer:below the mirror and the white lamps"
  },
  "7786": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the washbasin in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the bathroom "
  },
  "7787": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the washbasin?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the dining room and on the first floor"
  },
  "7788": {
    "question": "Question:what does the drawer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A single small wooden drawer."
  },
  "7789": {
    "question": "Question:where is the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is between a big window and the bed."
  },
  "7790": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the drawer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed at the corner of the bedroom."
  },
  "7791": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:No nearby areas."
  },
  "7792": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soild, rectangular and golden."
  },
  "7793": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is in the second row and the third column of the six pictures and above a cabinet with a silver ship."
  },
  "7794": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is in a living room on the second floor."
  },
  "7795": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is near a corridor and a study. "
  },
  "7796": {
    "question": "Question:what does the painting look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Rectangular, green and blue and soild."
  },
  "7797": {
    "question": "Question:where is the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is set near a green and blue painting and on the opposite side of two white washing machines. "
  },
  "7798": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the painting in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is set in a corridor."
  },
  "7799": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is near a laundry."
  },
  "7800": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A black leather sofa with a pink pillow."
  },
  "7801": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is close to a white fan and another sofa."
  },
  "7802": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is set against a wall and near a carpet."
  },
  "7803": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a stair."
  },
  "7804": {
    "question": "Question:what does the tv look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle, hanged and black"
  },
  "7805": {
    "question": "Question:where is the tv?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is facing the door and above the fireplace."
  },
  "7806": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the tv in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in living roon on the first floor."
  },
  "7807": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the tv?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is the room facing the door."
  },
  "7808": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:square, middle, silver"
  },
  "7809": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the wall, facing the balcony, on the washstand"
  },
  "7810": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is set in the washroom. "
  },
  "7811": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washroom is inside the bedroom, which is on the second floor and on the left of the corridor when go upstairs."
  },
  "7812": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A black wooden table with a glass board. "
  },
  "7813": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is beisde a window and there is a gray chair facing  it. "
  },
  "7814": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a bedroom."
  },
  "7815": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are some pictrues,trophies and a clock on it."
  },
  "7816": {
    "question": "Question:what does the TV look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wall-mounted, regular, black"
  },
  "7817": {
    "question": "Question:where is the TV?",
    "answer": "Answer:hung on the wall, across the sofa"
  },
  "7818": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the TV in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the living room. "
  },
  "7819": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the TV?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is near the window and next to the dining room."
  },
  "7820": {
    "question": "Question:what does the painting look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, square, yellow and blue"
  },
  "7821": {
    "question": "Question:where is the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's right under the cabinet, plant and books."
  },
  "7822": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the painting in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It hangs on the first floor where face the garden."
  },
  "7823": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:You can see a reception area next here, where the stairs beside."
  },
  "7824": {
    "question": "Question:what does the remote control look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:blend material and plastic\uff0cwhite\uff0csmall"
  },
  "7825": {
    "question": "Question:where is the remote control?",
    "answer": "Answer:they are installed on the wall which is close to big bed\uff0cbalcony is on the opposite"
  },
  "7826": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the remote control in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Two remote control switches are installed on the wall which is close to big bed\uff0copposite balcony in big bedroom."
  },
  "7827": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the remote control?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a dark color carpet placed on the ground beside the wall\uff0cand the color of big bed is white and purple."
  },
  "7828": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden,middle size,soft"
  },
  "7829": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a long desk and near a railing"
  },
  "7830": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it is located in a study room on the second floor"
  },
  "7831": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:there is a stair in the corner of the study room and there is a balcony outside the study room"
  },
  "7832": {
    "question": "Question:what does the book look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Rectangular , small, brown."
  },
  "7833": {
    "question": "Question:where is the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a book with the same state, size, colour next to it and a  round fan next to it."
  },
  "7834": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the book in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The book is set on a red benches and in front of a stone pillar."
  },
  "7835": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area has a long corridor close to the wall."
  },
  "7836": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White, square, cloth"
  },
  "7837": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a pillow above the bed and a sink next to it"
  },
  "7838": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Bed in the bedroom"
  },
  "7839": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed at the end of the living room"
  },
  "7840": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White, square, cloth"
  },
  "7841": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a pillow above the bed and a sink next to it"
  },
  "7842": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Bed in the bedroom"
  },
  "7843": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed at the end of the living room"
  },
  "7844": {
    "question": "Question:what does the shutter look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soild, medium size and transparent."
  },
  "7845": {
    "question": "Question:where is the shutter?",
    "answer": "Answer:The shutter is settled in a wall, near a big painting and a white bed."
  },
  "7846": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the shutter in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The shutter is in a bedroom on the second floor."
  },
  "7847": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the shutter?",
    "answer": "Answer:The shutter is near a toilet."
  },
  "7848": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is an old wooden brown cabinet."
  },
  "7849": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:He was directly above the sink and diagonally below a ceiling light."
  },
  "7850": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:This cupboard is in the study."
  },
  "7851": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a white long table and many white chairs in this study."
  },
  "7852": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Big, soild and white and brown."
  },
  "7853": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is next to a brown wall and between two small black tables under a black lamp and a black sculpture."
  },
  "7854": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is in a bedroom."
  },
  "7855": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is near a bathroom."
  },
  "7856": {
    "question": "Question:what does the armchair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown,middle size and soft"
  },
  "7857": {
    "question": "Question:where is the armchair?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in front of a sofa and next to a door."
  },
  "7858": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the armchair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in the corner of a living room on the second floor."
  },
  "7859": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the armchair?",
    "answer": "Answer:the living room is next to a rest room ,a dining room and a balcony."
  },
  "7860": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:actangular,gray ,on the wall"
  },
  "7861": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in front of 2 white chairs and near a lamp."
  },
  "7862": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a big bedroom on the second floor."
  },
  "7863": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:the bedroom has a bathroom and a dressing room and it's near a open-balcony."
  },
  "7864": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is square, white and ceramic."
  },
  "7865": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is on the table. The drawer is below the table."
  },
  "7866": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is placed on the opposite of the balcony."
  },
  "7867": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are many cabinets and sinks around."
  },
  "7868": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is ceramic, white and big."
  },
  "7869": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stove and the vase is on the table."
  },
  "7870": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is placed facing the balcony."
  },
  "7871": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are many cabinets and sinks in the kitchen."
  },
  "7872": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is ceramic, white and big."
  },
  "7873": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is on the table. The chairs are under the table."
  },
  "7874": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is placed facing the balcony in the kitchen."
  },
  "7875": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are many cabinets and sinks in the kitchen."
  },
  "7876": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:gray, rectangular, cloth"
  },
  "7877": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the glass wall, on the left of the table"
  },
  "7878": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is set in the bright balcony."
  },
  "7879": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The balcony is outside the livingroom, next to the dining room and on the third floor."
  },
  "7880": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden; narrow; long;"
  },
  "7881": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:beside the glass door;opposite a big cabinet;"
  },
  "7882": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:at the entrance of this store."
  },
  "7883": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The long table as a displaying shelf"
  },
  "7884": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle, stand hard by the wall, it is the style of graffiti."
  },
  "7885": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a beautiful picture put on back wall , and a small lamp is next to the bed "
  },
  "7886": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is placed hard by the wall inside a small bedroom ,which is close to a small lamp."
  },
  "7887": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is quite small ,and There is a small wooden table put next to the bed which is opposite the cloth cabinet."
  },
  "7888": {
    "question": "Question:what does the grass bottle look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small,fragile,transparent\n"
  },
  "7889": {
    "question": "Question:where is the grass bottle?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a oven and another glass bottle."
  },
  "7890": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the grass bottle in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's on a black table in the kitchen on the second floor.\n"
  },
  "7891": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the grass bottle?",
    "answer": "Answer:the kitchen is next to a open-balcony."
  },
  "7892": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden; squared; simple;"
  },
  "7893": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:in the middle of two deck chairs and near a wooden door."
  },
  "7894": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:faces the huge pillar in the center of the hall."
  },
  "7895": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:a big hall leading to a long hallway."
  },
  "7896": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is square, small and glass."
  },
  "7897": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is placed above the drawer and sink."
  },
  "7898": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is placed above the drawer and sink in the toilet. "
  },
  "7899": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a sink and toilet in the toilet."
  },
  "7900": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Red and brown, soild and wooden."
  },
  "7901": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is on the left side of a short brown table and in front of a window."
  },
  "7902": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set in a study."
  },
  "7903": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is near a bedroom with a blue carpet."
  },
  "7904": {
    "question": "Question:what does the monocycle look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Black,rubber,round"
  },
  "7905": {
    "question": "Question:where is the monocycle?",
    "answer": "Answer:The monocycle is set in a corner and near a bookshelf."
  },
  "7906": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the monocycle in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The monocucle is placed in a reading room."
  },
  "7907": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the monocycle?",
    "answer": "Answer:The monocycle is set next to a tearoom."
  },
  "7908": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden; embeded into the wall; has two doors;"
  },
  "7909": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:opposite a big mirror; next to a box;"
  },
  "7910": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:faces a wooden bench;"
  },
  "7911": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:belongs to a corner of a hallway."
  },
  "7912": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a yellow, glass transparent ceiling light."
  },
  "7913": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is under the roof, above the floor-to-ceiling windows."
  },
  "7914": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is set in a corridor at the door of a house."
  },
  "7915": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is set beside the door of a kitchen."
  },
  "7916": {
    "question": "Question:what does the closestool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white , normal size"
  },
  "7917": {
    "question": "Question:where is the closestool?",
    "answer": "Answer:below the towel and next to the woody door"
  },
  "7918": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the closestool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the bathroom"
  },
  "7919": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the closestool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is in the bedroom and on the second floor "
  },
  "7920": {
    "question": "Question:what does the plate look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:round, transparent and glass"
  },
  "7921": {
    "question": "Question:where is the plate?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed on a cabinet and next to a kettle."
  },
  "7922": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the plate in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "7923": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the plate?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to the chatting room and the door."
  },
  "7924": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:yellow, metal frame and being related to football."
  },
  "7925": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is on the wall and above a toilet."
  },
  "7926": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is in a bathroom."
  },
  "7927": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area connects with a bedroom and near a toilet."
  },
  "7928": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:thin, metallic, circular"
  },
  "7929": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the black table and next to the laptop"
  },
  "7930": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is in the study."
  },
  "7931": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The study is next to the dining roon and the bathroom on the second floor."
  },
  "7932": {
    "question": "Question:what does the window look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:square, glass, big"
  },
  "7933": {
    "question": "Question:where is the window?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the right of the picture, next to the washroom"
  },
  "7934": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the window in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The window is located in the bright bedroom."
  },
  "7935": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the window?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is on the second floor and on the left side of the corridor when go upstairs."
  },
  "7936": {
    "question": "Question:what does the book look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:thin,erect,red and white"
  },
  "7937": {
    "question": "Question:where is the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the left of a wheel,on the third row of the shell that's on the left of the corridor door and under a white model"
  },
  "7938": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the book in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The book is in the lobby."
  },
  "7939": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the book?",
    "answer": "Answer: It's on the right of the counter and faces the food bar at a slant."
  },
  "7940": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small one, irregular shape, its color is black and it's a cloth chair"
  },
  "7941": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:there are two white pillows put int the chair, and it is put back facing the glass door to the balcony "
  },
  "7942": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is put in the big living room, which is back facing the big glass door to the balcony, and there are two white pillows put on it."
  },
  "7943": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are several different size sofas put in the living room, and a median mirror is installed on the wall."
  },
  "7944": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White, square, cloth"
  },
  "7945": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are pillows on the bed and there are tables on the left and right"
  },
  "7946": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Bed in the bedroom"
  },
  "7947": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The yard is opposite the bed and the living room is next to it"
  },
  "7948": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown,big,woody"
  },
  "7949": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's on the left of lights and the mirror"
  },
  "7950": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in the bathroom"
  },
  "7951": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:the bedroom is on the right side of it"
  },
  "7952": {
    "question": "Question:what does the drawer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, white, wood"
  },
  "7953": {
    "question": "Question:where is the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:below a vase, below a bowl"
  },
  "7954": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the drawer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is in the corner of a kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "7955": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to a small storeroom and there is a cloakroom upstairs."
  },
  "7956": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A black hemispherical lamp with a metal stalk and metal base. "
  },
  "7957": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near several books and over black cushions."
  },
  "7958": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on a white desk and beside a big picture."
  },
  "7959": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near the bedroom's door and an empty room."
  },
  "7960": {
    "question": "Question:what does the painting look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Medium size, rectangular and white."
  },
  "7961": {
    "question": "Question:where is the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is near a transparent table surrounded by twelve transparent chairs and a brown table."
  },
  "7962": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the painting in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is in a dining room."
  },
  "7963": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is near a living room."
  },
  "7964": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:square, brown, leather"
  },
  "7965": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the trash can, next to the small table, on the left of the door"
  },
  "7966": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is set in the spacious office."
  },
  "7967": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is on the first floor and next to the livingroom."
  },
  "7968": {
    "question": "Question:what does the closestool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, normal size"
  },
  "7969": {
    "question": "Question:where is the closestool?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the woody doors, below the mirror"
  },
  "7970": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the closestool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the bedroom"
  },
  "7971": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the closestool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is in the bedroom and on the third floor."
  },
  "7972": {
    "question": "Question:what does the curtain look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:gray, fabric"
  },
  "7973": {
    "question": "Question:where is the curtain?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the glass door, next to the stairs"
  },
  "7974": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the curtain in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the kitchen."
  },
  "7975": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the curtain?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the stairs, and a garden is outside."
  },
  "7976": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:large, white, stable"
  },
  "7977": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:near a bar counter, next to a chair "
  },
  "7978": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is in the corner of the bar."
  },
  "7979": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bar has decorations on the wall and stairs in the corner."
  },
  "7980": {
    "question": "Question:what does the carpet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:soft, brown, thin"
  },
  "7981": {
    "question": "Question:where is the carpet?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a laundry basket, in front of a massage bed"
  },
  "7982": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the carpet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:This carpet is put in a sauna."
  },
  "7983": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the carpet?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area connects with a sauna room and has massage beds."
  },
  "7984": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:transparent,middle size,fragile"
  },
  "7985": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's on a black table and next to a sofa."
  },
  "7986": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a living room on the first floor."
  },
  "7987": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:the living room is near a dining room , a kitchen and a corridor."
  },
  "7988": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, middle, rectangular"
  },
  "7989": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:around the table, facing the glass window, second from the left"
  },
  "7990": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set in a spacious dining room."
  },
  "7991": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The dining room is on the third floor, next to the kitchen and facing the washroom."
  },
  "7992": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pot look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:round,woody and brown"
  },
  "7993": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pot?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed on a shelf under the table ."
  },
  "7994": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pot in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "7995": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pot?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to the chatting room and the door."
  },
  "7996": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Glass, transparent, cylindrical"
  },
  "7997": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are red and pink flowers in the vase, there is a table lamp next to it, and they are placed on a small table together"
  },
  "7998": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Vase in the bedroom"
  },
  "7999": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:Opposite the vase is a small balcony with a toilet next to it"
  },
  "8000": {
    "question": "Question:what does the telephone look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White, plastic, square"
  },
  "8001": {
    "question": "Question:where is the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:The telephone is on a stool with a lamp next to it"
  },
  "8002": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the telephone in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The telephone in living room"
  },
  "8003": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:The telephone is near the stairs and opposite the kitchen"
  },
  "8004": {
    "question": "Question:what does the treadmill look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black, heavy, metallic"
  },
  "8005": {
    "question": "Question:where is the treadmill?",
    "answer": "Answer:near a big mirror, next to a spinning bike"
  },
  "8006": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the treadmill in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The treadmill is in a gymnasium."
  },
  "8007": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the treadmill?",
    "answer": "Answer:The gymnasium has three chandeliers and a swivel chair."
  },
  "8008": {
    "question": "Question:what does the desk look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Small, old, and wooden"
  },
  "8009": {
    "question": "Question:where is the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:The desk is next to a big cabinet with a computer and in front of a red chair."
  },
  "8010": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the desk in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The desk is located on one side of the corridor."
  },
  "8011": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area is next to a small room with cabinets."
  },
  "8012": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stairs look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Beige, stair-stepping and soild."
  },
  "8013": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stairs?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stair is near a transparent table surrounded transparent chairs and near two brown chairs."
  },
  "8014": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stairs in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stair is in a dining room."
  },
  "8015": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stairs?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stair is near a kitchen."
  },
  "8016": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:one of them is square and another one is rectangle, they are installed on the wall of bathroom, one without frame and another with wooden frame"
  },
  "8017": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:there is another similar mirror installed close to the target, and there is a sink under it"
  },
  "8018": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirrors are installed on the wall of bathroom which are farther to the door."
  },
  "8019": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathroom is the one placed in big bedroom which attached with balcony and a small dressing room."
  },
  "8020": {
    "question": "Question:what does the drawer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is wooden, small and closed."
  },
  "8021": {
    "question": "Question:where is the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are some pictures below the drawer. There is a chair next to the drawer."
  },
  "8022": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the drawer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is placed below the picture next to the chair in the room."
  },
  "8023": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are two tables, sofa and recliner in the room."
  },
  "8024": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown,leather and metal and owning two argent handrails"
  },
  "8025": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:around the table,back to a pillar and closest to the gate"
  },
  "8026": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is in a big meeting room."
  },
  "8027": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The meeting room is by the side of the reading area and behind the restaurant."
  },
  "8028": {
    "question": "Question:what does the container look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A square yellow linen container."
  },
  "8029": {
    "question": "Question:where is the container?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a wine barrel and another wooden container."
  },
  "8030": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the container in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is under a stair and a black item."
  },
  "8031": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the container?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near the living room."
  },
  "8032": {
    "question": "Question:what does the plant look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:green, "
  },
  "8033": {
    "question": "Question:where is the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:Behind it are curtains, There is a black and yellow painting on its right side."
  },
  "8034": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the plant in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's put in the work room."
  },
  "8035": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:Work room face the dinning room."
  },
  "8036": {
    "question": "Question:what does the switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soild, rectangular and brassy."
  },
  "8037": {
    "question": "Question:where is the switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:The switch is near a green painting and opposite to a white cabinet."
  },
  "8038": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The switch is in a corridor on the second floor."
  },
  "8039": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:The switch is near a toilet and a bedroom."
  },
  "8040": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a new wooden square table."
  },
  "8041": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the middle of two chairs."
  },
  "8042": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is set in a corridor at the door of a house."
  },
  "8043": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is set beside the door of a kitchen."
  },
  "8044": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stove look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stove is square, irony and black."
  },
  "8045": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stove?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stove is placed on the table next to the vase."
  },
  "8046": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stove in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stove is placed on the table next to the vase in the kitchen."
  },
  "8047": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stove?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are many cabinets and sinks in the kitchen."
  },
  "8048": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Leopard print, long, fabric"
  },
  "8049": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:On top of it is a plush pillow and a tray with pots and flowers on the tray"
  },
  "8050": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Sofa in living room"
  },
  "8051": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:Living room connected with balcony and gym"
  },
  "8052": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White and brown, round and wooden."
  },
  "8053": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is set under a brown vase, near a red and brown chair and opposite to a wooden carbinet."
  },
  "8054": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is in a bedroom."
  },
  "8055": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is on the opposite side of a narrow room with a wooden carbinet."
  },
  "8056": {
    "question": "Question:what does the drawer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is wooden, square and small."
  },
  "8057": {
    "question": "Question:where is the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is placed below the shelf and some bottles of wine."
  },
  "8058": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the drawer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is placed below the shelf and some bottles of wine."
  },
  "8059": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a pot of flower, desk and chairs on the opposite."
  },
  "8060": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, cylindrical"
  },
  "8061": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the bed and window."
  },
  "8062": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the children's bedroom."
  },
  "8063": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the study and the bathroom."
  },
  "8064": {
    "question": "Question:what does the telephone look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:plastic,metal,black and white"
  },
  "8065": {
    "question": "Question:where is the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's on a transparent glass table and near a glass bottle."
  },
  "8066": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the telephone in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a bathroom on the second floor."
  },
  "8067": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:the bathroom is in a big bedroom which is in the end of a corridor and near a open-balcony."
  },
  "8068": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:with four long legs,wooden,brown"
  },
  "8069": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the left of a white dustbin,in front of the white desk,in the third position from left to right"
  },
  "8070": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is in the tea room."
  },
  "8071": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The tea room is next to the exit and opposite to the resting area."
  },
  "8072": {
    "question": "Question:what does the towel look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle, gray, soft "
  },
  "8073": {
    "question": "Question:where is the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the door, next to the wall"
  },
  "8074": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the towel in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is settled in the corner of a bedroom. "
  },
  "8075": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is next to the corridor on the second floor with a fireplace and a bathroom. "
  },
  "8076": {
    "question": "Question:what does the computer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:triangle,a white,thin screen declining,possessing a wide base and a apple logo"
  },
  "8077": {
    "question": "Question:where is the computer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The computer is on a yellow table mat,next to a lamb and in front of a chair."
  },
  "8078": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the computer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The computer is in an office numbering 356 that filled with stationery,book and poster."
  },
  "8079": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the computer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The  computer is on the right of a white huge pillar and face the corridor at a slant."
  },
  "8080": {
    "question": "Question:what does the luggage look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Medium size, soild and black."
  },
  "8081": {
    "question": "Question:where is the luggage?",
    "answer": "Answer:The luggage is set near a blue and brown bed, in front of the window and near the white baskets."
  },
  "8082": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the luggage in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The luggage is in a bedroom."
  },
  "8083": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the luggage?",
    "answer": "Answer:The luggage is near a living room and a toilet."
  },
  "8084": {
    "question": "Question:what does the light look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A light with a lampshade,a dulb and orange glows."
  },
  "8085": {
    "question": "Question:where is the light?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is above a mirror and a sink,attached to the wall."
  },
  "8086": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the light in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the toilet."
  },
  "8087": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the light?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near the bedroom."
  },
  "8088": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pillow look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:light blue, small, cloth"
  },
  "8089": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the long sofa, among six sofas and third from left, in front of a pillow"
  },
  "8090": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pillow in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The pillow is set in the livingroom."
  },
  "8091": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:The livingroom is on the first floor and next to the kitchen and dining room."
  },
  "8092": {
    "question": "Question:what does the toilet paper look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, columniform, wall-mounted"
  },
  "8093": {
    "question": "Question:where is the toilet paper?",
    "answer": "Answer:hung on the wall, next to the toilet"
  },
  "8094": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the toilet paper in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the bathroom."
  },
  "8095": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the toilet paper?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is in a corner which is next to the dining room."
  },
  "8096": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is an old, short, square table.\n"
  },
  "8097": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a porcelain and a book on it.\n"
  },
  "8098": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in a living room."
  },
  "8099": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's beside a kitchen."
  },
  "8100": {
    "question": "Question:what does the power switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is small, plastic and white."
  },
  "8101": {
    "question": "Question:where is the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is on the wall and beside the door."
  },
  "8102": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the power switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is in the aisle beside the stairs."
  },
  "8103": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is on the wall and beside the door."
  },
  "8104": {
    "question": "Question:what does the deck chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black; with grey towels; white cushions;"
  },
  "8105": {
    "question": "Question:where is the deck chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the right of an end table with magazines on it; beside the door of men's changing room."
  },
  "8106": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the deck chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:against a wall with two wall lamps;"
  },
  "8107": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the deck chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:behind the recieption of this area."
  },
  "8108": {
    "question": "Question:what does the photo look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:square, wooden and glass, white and black"
  },
  "8109": {
    "question": "Question:where is the photo?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the wall, above the toilet"
  },
  "8110": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the photo in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The photo is set in the washroom."
  },
  "8111": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the photo?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washroom is inside the office, which is next to the livingroom and on the first floor."
  },
  "8112": {
    "question": "Question:what does the seat look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:squared; black leather cushion;wooden frames;"
  },
  "8113": {
    "question": "Question:where is the seat?",
    "answer": "Answer:three cabinets around it;faces a black cabinet below a black mirror;"
  },
  "8114": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the seat in?",
    "answer": "Answer:in the center of a cubicle."
  },
  "8115": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the seat?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a corridor inside the women's changing room."
  },
  "8116": {
    "question": "Question:what does the display look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:large,thin,black"
  },
  "8117": {
    "question": "Question:where is the display?",
    "answer": "Answer:between two black shells,in the middle of the brown book shell and at the end of the corridor"
  },
  "8118": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the display in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's is in a vast reading hall. "
  },
  "8119": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the display?",
    "answer": "Answer:The reading hall is behind the restaurant and near a meeting room and some boothes."
  },
  "8120": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:plastic and glass, cylindrical, white"
  },
  "8121": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the right of the bed, on the nightstand"
  },
  "8122": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is set in the spacious bedroom."
  },
  "8123": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is on the first floor and next to the kitchen."
  },
  "8124": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:circle, glass, transparent."
  },
  "8125": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:A smaller sink is right to it. A screen is left to it. Above the sink is a big mirror on the wall."
  },
  "8126": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is in a glass washbasin in a bathroom."
  },
  "8127": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:Opposite to the sink is a shower room."
  },
  "8128": {
    "question": "Question:what does the washstand look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rounded,small,white"
  },
  "8129": {
    "question": "Question:where is the washstand?",
    "answer": "Answer:under the mirror and the light"
  },
  "8130": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the washstand in?",
    "answer": "Answer:in the bathroom"
  },
  "8131": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the washstand?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is on the right side of it"
  },
  "8132": {
    "question": "Question:what does the armchair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:leather,stand on the floor,black"
  },
  "8133": {
    "question": "Question:where is the armchair?",
    "answer": "Answer: in opposite of bed and next to the table"
  },
  "8134": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the armchair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in the bedroom"
  },
  "8135": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the armchair?",
    "answer": "Answer:there are a bathroom on the right of it"
  },
  "8136": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is colorful, big and square."
  },
  "8137": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is hung on the wall facing the sofa."
  },
  "8138": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is hung on the wall facing the sofa in the living room."
  },
  "8139": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is hung on the wall facing the sofa in the living room."
  },
  "8140": {
    "question": "Question:what does the clothes rack look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, rectangular, wall-mounted "
  },
  "8141": {
    "question": "Question:where is the clothes rack?",
    "answer": "Answer:there is a rectangular white bag in it, on the left of the white door"
  },
  "8142": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the clothes rack in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the cloakroom."
  },
  "8143": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the clothes rack?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is located in a bedroom which has a rectangular balcony, a washroom and a toilet, and the cloakroom is next to the washroom and toilet."
  },
  "8144": {
    "question": "Question:what does the freezer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle,big,made by metal"
  },
  "8145": {
    "question": "Question:where is the freezer?",
    "answer": "Answer:there is a basket on it and a cupboard on the right"
  },
  "8146": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the freezer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in the kitchen"
  },
  "8147": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the freezer?",
    "answer": "Answer:there is a bedroom behind it"
  },
  "8148": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, armless"
  },
  "8149": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It faces the pool and there is an identical chair on the left."
  },
  "8150": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It was placed in the hallway between the open kitchen and the pool."
  },
  "8151": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:There's a pool on one side and an open kitchen on the other"
  },
  "8152": {
    "question": "Question:what does the photo look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White and black, rectangular and small."
  },
  "8153": {
    "question": "Question:where is the photo?",
    "answer": "Answer:The photo is settled near two colorful photos, below a yellow photo and near a black fitness equipment."
  },
  "8154": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the photo in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The photo is in a bedroom."
  },
  "8155": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the photo?",
    "answer": "Answer:The photo is near a toilet."
  },
  "8156": {
    "question": "Question:what does the book look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:blue and yellow,paper"
  },
  "8157": {
    "question": "Question:where is the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:in the drawer of the shelf,on the left of a white baffle"
  },
  "8158": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the book in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stack of books in a small meeting room with the number of 03."
  },
  "8159": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:The meeting room is opposite to the gate of a big meeting room and next to a room forbidden to entry and is along a corridor to the lobby."
  },
  "8160": {
    "question": "Question:what does the paintings look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soild, small and rectangular."
  },
  "8161": {
    "question": "Question:where is the paintings?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is in the first row, the first column of the six paintings and above two red and brown chairs."
  },
  "8162": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the paintings in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is in a study."
  },
  "8163": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the paintings?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is near a living room."
  },
  "8164": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Medium size, wooden and brown."
  },
  "8165": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is on the right side of an oven and near a sink."
  },
  "8166": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is in a kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "8167": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is near a corridor and a toilet."
  },
  "8168": {
    "question": "Question:what does the computer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Rectangle, open, black"
  },
  "8169": {
    "question": "Question:where is the computer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The computer is set on a yellow table and next to a window."
  },
  "8170": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the computer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The computer is placed in the front desk."
  },
  "8171": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the computer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The computer is set near the stairs and the hall."
  },
  "8172": {
    "question": "Question:what does the telephone look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black and white,metal,rectangle"
  },
  "8173": {
    "question": "Question:where is the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the left of a yellow book,in front of two glowing screens and on the right side of glass wall"
  },
  "8174": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the telephone in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The telephone is in the 302 office."
  },
  "8175": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is in front of a corridor door,along the road connecting the tea room and the restaurant."
  },
  "8176": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white,big,metal,oblong"
  },
  "8177": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the left of the cabinet,in front of a chair,above a box and with a computer on it"
  },
  "8178": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in the middle of a small single office signed number 362."
  },
  "8179": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is opposite to a public working office and has a road leading to the exit on the left side."
  },
  "8180": {
    "question": "Question:what does the plant look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Tall, green and vibrant"
  },
  "8181": {
    "question": "Question:where is the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:pot culture next is a glass door and the sofa opposite"
  },
  "8182": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the plant in?",
    "answer": "Answer:pot culture In the living room"
  },
  "8183": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:pot culture Near the balcony"
  },
  "8184": {
    "question": "Question:what does the desk look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, rectangular,woody"
  },
  "8185": {
    "question": "Question:where is the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the stove and the window"
  },
  "8186": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the desk in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the bedroom"
  },
  "8187": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the corridor and another bedroom."
  },
  "8188": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black and white,metal,cuboid\t"
  },
  "8189": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:under the desk,next to the chair"
  },
  "8190": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in a small office that only contains a set of office equipment and is signed number 307."
  },
  "8191": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The small office is opposite to a big office full of paper , faces the locker room at a slant,along the road to tea room as well."
  },
  "8192": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:long; black;with two towels;"
  },
  "8193": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:in the middle of the five chairs; below a yellow security identifier."
  },
  "8194": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:against a wall with two wall lamps;"
  },
  "8195": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:a hall with a rounded bar in the center."
  },
  "8196": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Wooden, golden and soild."
  },
  "8197": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is in the first row and the third column of the six pictures and above a cabinet with a silver ship."
  },
  "8198": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is in a living room."
  },
  "8199": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is near a corridor and a study."
  },
  "8200": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a blue, cotton-filled, square sofa chair.\n"
  },
  "8201": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is behind the two wooden chairs, opposite the door of the room."
  },
  "8202": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in a living room."
  },
  "8203": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's beside a kitchen."
  },
  "8204": {
    "question": "Question:what does the shower look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cylinder, silvery, metal"
  },
  "8205": {
    "question": "Question:where is the shower?",
    "answer": "Answer:below a light, next to a door"
  },
  "8206": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the shower in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The shower is in a small bathroom on the second floor."
  },
  "8207": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the shower?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathroom is between a gym and a bedroom and faces a corridor."
  },
  "8208": {
    "question": "Question:what does the armchair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cloth small brown"
  },
  "8209": {
    "question": "Question:where is the armchair?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the big sofa and behind the swimming pool"
  },
  "8210": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the armchair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:outdoor"
  },
  "8211": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the armchair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's close to the entrance to the house"
  },
  "8212": {
    "question": "Question:what does the tap look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Metal, silver, high"
  },
  "8213": {
    "question": "Question:where is the tap?",
    "answer": "Answer:Below the tap is the pool with some vases and fruit trays to the left and right"
  },
  "8214": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the tap in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Tap in the kitchen"
  },
  "8215": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the tap?",
    "answer": "Answer:Opposite the tap is the living room"
  },
  "8216": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cupboard look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:metal and glass,closed,full of chinaT"
  },
  "8217": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cupboard?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's behind dining table and in front of kitchen"
  },
  "8218": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cupboard in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in dining room"
  },
  "8219": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cupboard?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a kitchen behind it."
  },
  "8220": {
    "question": "Question:what does the fan look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Round, silvery, tall."
  },
  "8221": {
    "question": "Question:where is the fan?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a woody wardrobe near the fan and a fences near it."
  },
  "8222": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the fan in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The fan is set at the corner of the hall."
  },
  "8223": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the fan?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area is close to a glasses door of the hall."
  },
  "8224": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black and brown, rectangle, small"
  },
  "8225": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's put on a table.  it's on the left side of the bed."
  },
  "8226": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's put in a big and  bright main bedroom."
  },
  "8227": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The master bedroom faces the balcony. Right below the room is the swimming pool."
  },
  "8228": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Red and brown, wooden and soild."
  },
  "8229": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is on the right side of a small white table and near the desk under the ceiling lamp."
  },
  "8230": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in a study."
  },
  "8231": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is near a bedroom."
  },
  "8232": {
    "question": "Question:what does the tap look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:iron, silver"
  },
  "8233": {
    "question": "Question:where is the tap?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a display in its left.  A calendar is right above it."
  },
  "8234": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the tap in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's installed in a  open kitchen."
  },
  "8235": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the tap?",
    "answer": "Answer: Here you can see the swimming pool, reception area and a wicket."
  },
  "8236": {
    "question": "Question:what does the carpet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown, hairy, square"
  },
  "8237": {
    "question": "Question:where is the carpet?",
    "answer": "Answer:there is a big sofa on it, there is a table on it, on the wooden floor"
  },
  "8238": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the carpet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The carpet is located in a bright livingroom."
  },
  "8239": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the carpet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The livingroom is on the third floor, next to the stairs and kitchen and there is a balcony outside."
  },
  "8240": {
    "question": "Question:what does the microwave oven look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Black, soild and small."
  },
  "8241": {
    "question": "Question:where is the microwave oven?",
    "answer": "Answer:The microwave oven is set under a brown cabinet and near some plates."
  },
  "8242": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the microwave oven in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The microwave oven is in a kitchen."
  },
  "8243": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the microwave oven?",
    "answer": "Answer:The microwave oven is near a corridor on the first floor."
  },
  "8244": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A small square glass mirror."
  },
  "8245": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on the left of another mirror,behind a sink and near three small windows."
  },
  "8246": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a bathroom connected to a bedroom."
  },
  "8247": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a bedroom and an empty room."
  },
  "8248": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a new, square, black painting."
  },
  "8249": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's on a sofa, next to a switch."
  },
  "8250": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is in a living room.\n"
  },
  "8251": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a clean, tidy and spacious living room.\n"
  },
  "8252": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:ceramic, cylindric and brown."
  },
  "8253": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a picture on the right of the vase and a toilet is under the vase."
  },
  "8254": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is in a toilet."
  },
  "8255": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is on a laundry and connected with a kitchen."
  },
  "8256": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Black and silvery, soild and small."
  },
  "8257": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is set one a white long table, on the left side of a white and brown bed and near two skateboards."
  },
  "8258": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is in a bedroom on the second floor."
  },
  "8259": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is near a toilet."
  },
  "8260": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is rectangular, iron and silver."
  },
  "8261": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is to the right of the towel and brush."
  },
  "8262": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is in the bathroom."
  },
  "8263": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is to the right of the towel and brush."
  },
  "8264": {
    "question": "Question:what does the screen look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle,black,metal"
  },
  "8265": {
    "question": "Question:where is the screen?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of the class wall and curtain,on the desk and on the left of the phone"
  },
  "8266": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the screen in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The screen is in a large office owning the number 377."
  },
  "8267": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the screen?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is at the corner of a junction of three roads and on the left of the stairway door."
  },
  "8268": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black,metallic,like a mushroom "
  },
  "8269": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:the lamp is on a long square table and surrounded by 3 chairs"
  },
  "8270": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it is in a study room on the second floor"
  },
  "8271": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer: there is a stair in the corner of the study room and a balcony outside the study room"
  },
  "8272": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, gray, white, soft"
  },
  "8273": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of a television, near a lamp and a table"
  },
  "8274": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is settled in the living room and on a carpet. "
  },
  "8275": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room has a tall shelf with some photos and another small shelf with a printer and a box. "
  },
  "8276": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big one, rectangle\uff0cthe color of it is white"
  },
  "8277": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:there is a desk in front of the target\uff0cand the cabinet is opposite the glass door which is to balcony"
  },
  "8278": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The white cabinet is placed front facing glass door\uff0cwhich is placed behind desk in the big bedroom."
  },
  "8279": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a shower room and small work place in the living room which is close to leisure area.\n"
  },
  "8280": {
    "question": "Question:what does the painting look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Black and beige, medium size and rectangular."
  },
  "8281": {
    "question": "Question:where is the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is settled near a brown table surrounded by four chairs and near a white sofa."
  },
  "8282": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the painting in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is in a living room."
  },
  "8283": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is near a bedroom."
  },
  "8284": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Wooden, yellow and white and soild."
  },
  "8285": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is under a black television and a red lamp and near a gray and black bed."
  },
  "8286": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is in a bedroom."
  },
  "8287": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is near a corridor and a living room."
  },
  "8288": {
    "question": "Question:what does the plant look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:tall,wooden,green and with a great deal of leaves"
  },
  "8289": {
    "question": "Question:where is the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:surrounded by three sofas,on the left of a glass wall"
  },
  "8290": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the plant in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's is at the end of a corridor and in the rest area."
  },
  "8291": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is opposite to the locker and the tea room,sharing a corridor to the exit and at a corner."
  },
  "8292": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cup look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:ceramic, cylindrical, black"
  },
  "8293": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cup?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the first floor of the cup holder, in the central of the cup holder, in the middle of two cups"
  },
  "8294": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cup in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cup is set in a small kitchen. "
  },
  "8295": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cup?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is on the first floor and next to the livingroom."
  },
  "8296": {
    "question": "Question:what does the painting look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:colorful ink painting"
  },
  "8297": {
    "question": "Question:where is the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:face the French window, right above the switch."
  },
  "8298": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the painting in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's install in a big and  bright main bedroom."
  },
  "8299": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:The master bedroom faces the balcony. Right below the room is the swimming pool."
  },
  "8300": {
    "question": "Question:what does the desk look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden,glass,rectangular"
  },
  "8301": {
    "question": "Question:where is the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's surrounded by 3 chairs and it's near a railing"
  },
  "8302": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the desk in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's located in a study room on the second floor"
  },
  "8303": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:there is a stair in the corner of the study room and a balcony outside the study room"
  },
  "8304": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:irregular, black, smooth"
  },
  "8305": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:between a big sofa and the bedroom, near stairs"
  },
  "8306": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is set at a corner of the living room."
  },
  "8307": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is very spacious."
  },
  "8308": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black, irregular, smooth"
  },
  "8309": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a small table with a lamp, between a big sofa and the bedroom"
  },
  "8310": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is set at a corner of the living room, on the second floor."
  },
  "8311": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is surrounded by a kitchen and two bedrooms."
  },
  "8312": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:irregular, leather, smooth"
  },
  "8313": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:between a big sofa and the bedroom, near stairs"
  },
  "8314": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is set at a corner of the living room."
  },
  "8315": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is next to the kitchen and the bedrooms."
  },
  "8316": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, white, plastic"
  },
  "8317": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the wall, next to faucet, on the right of the door when facing the balcony"
  },
  "8318": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set on the sunny balcony."
  },
  "8319": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The balcony is outside the bedroom, which is in the end of corridor, on the second floor and on the left of the corridor when go upstairs."
  },
  "8320": {
    "question": "Question:what does the hand door look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White, small and metal."
  },
  "8321": {
    "question": "Question:where is the hand door?",
    "answer": "Answer:The hand door is close to the bed and the lamp."
  },
  "8322": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the hand door in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Hand door is in the bedroom."
  },
  "8323": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the hand door?",
    "answer": "Answer:The hand door is close to the balcony and the living room."
  },
  "8324": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, cloth, black"
  },
  "8325": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a green plant, next to a piano "
  },
  "8326": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture in settled in a small and bright living room in the first floor."
  },
  "8327": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living is next to a washroom and connect with a dining through a corridor."
  },
  "8328": {
    "question": "Question:what does the television look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular,glass and reflective"
  },
  "8329": {
    "question": "Question:where is the television?",
    "answer": "Answer:there are 2 same kind of televisions next to it and it's in the center."
  },
  "8330": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the television in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a living room on the first floor."
  },
  "8331": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the television?",
    "answer": "Answer:the living room is near a dining room and a stair."
  },
  "8332": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is big and colorful."
  },
  "8333": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is placed between some boxes and the big closet."
  },
  "8334": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is placed between some boxes and the big closet."
  },
  "8335": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are many clothes and shoes in the closet."
  },
  "8336": {
    "question": "Question:what does the air-conditioner look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, rectangular, long"
  },
  "8337": {
    "question": "Question:where is the air-conditioner?",
    "answer": "Answer:above the TV, next to the French window"
  },
  "8338": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the air-conditioner in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The air-conditioner is in the living room."
  },
  "8339": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the air-conditioner?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is next to the balcony and in front of the dining room."
  },
  "8340": {
    "question": "Question:what does the book look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Green,paper,rectangular"
  },
  "8341": {
    "question": "Question:where is the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:The book is set near a glass on a yellow table in front of a sofa."
  },
  "8342": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the book in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The book is placed in the hall."
  },
  "8343": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:The book is set near a bedroom and a tearoom."
  },
  "8344": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden; narrow but long; double-shelf;"
  },
  "8345": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of two identical stools; faces a big glass door;"
  },
  "8346": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:in the center of this small hall;"
  },
  "8347": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:a recieption for this area;"
  },
  "8348": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, cylindrycal, "
  },
  "8349": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the table, next to the bed"
  },
  "8350": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the children's bedroom."
  },
  "8351": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the study and the bathroom."
  },
  "8352": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown, circular and woody"
  },
  "8353": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to a trash bin with a vase on it."
  },
  "8354": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a hall on the first floor."
  },
  "8355": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The hall is next to the chatting room."
  },
  "8356": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Genuine leather\uff0cSingle sofa."
  },
  "8357": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:There have four sofas in the last row. Facing forward, It's second from left to right.It's under the projector."
  },
  "8358": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in the last row of the screening hall, facing the door direction from left to right, the second sofa."
  },
  "8359": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The nearest area is the living room."
  },
  "8360": {
    "question": "Question:what does the glass door look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, transparent, tall"
  },
  "8361": {
    "question": "Question:where is the glass door?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the staircase, across to the table"
  },
  "8362": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the glass door in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the kitchen."
  },
  "8363": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the glass door?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the living room and the dining room."
  },
  "8364": {
    "question": "Question:what does the whiteboard look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:tall,metal,white,rectangle"
  },
  "8365": {
    "question": "Question:where is the whiteboard?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the left of the cabinet,in front of the glass wall"
  },
  "8366": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the whiteboard in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a large office owning the number 377."
  },
  "8367": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the whiteboard?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is at the corner of a junction of three roads and on the left of the stairway door."
  },
  "8368": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is rectangular, black and large."
  },
  "8369": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is between the column and the table."
  },
  "8370": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is beside the outdoor swimming pool."
  },
  "8371": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is between the column and the table."
  },
  "8372": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bag look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cloth,long belts,white,black mark"
  },
  "8373": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bag?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bag is hung behind the door,on the right side of the air-conditioner on the floor and at the corner of the office."
  },
  "8374": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bag in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bag is in a six person office."
  },
  "8375": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bag?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is at the corner of the three fork road,connecting to two corridors and next to an empty office and opposite to the room 356."
  },
  "8376": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Glass, black frame, square"
  },
  "8377": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:One door on each side"
  },
  "8378": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:picture On the wall of the corridor"
  },
  "8379": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:picture Connecting the living room and bedroom"
  },
  "8380": {
    "question": "Question:what does the typewriter look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Cuboid, black and soild."
  },
  "8381": {
    "question": "Question:where is the typewriter?",
    "answer": "Answer:The typewriter is set near a black and gray computer and a tall brown cabinet."
  },
  "8382": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the typewriter in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The typewriter is in a study."
  },
  "8383": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the typewriter?",
    "answer": "Answer:The typewriter is set near a toilet and a dining room."
  },
  "8384": {
    "question": "Question:what does the curtains look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:long, cloth, yellow and black"
  },
  "8385": {
    "question": "Question:where is the curtains?",
    "answer": "Answer:close to a shelf, in the corner"
  },
  "8386": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the curtains in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The curtain is in a small study."
  },
  "8387": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the curtains?",
    "answer": "Answer:The study has four doors and connects with the outside via a door."
  },
  "8388": {
    "question": "Question:what does the shelf look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:woody, tall, stable "
  },
  "8389": {
    "question": "Question:where is the shelf?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the wall, in front of a curtain "
  },
  "8390": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the shelf in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The shelf is located in a study while it is also near the bedroom."
  },
  "8391": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the shelf?",
    "answer": "Answer:The study has a big table in the center and connects with a bedroom."
  },
  "8392": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:long; deck chair; with metal frames;"
  },
  "8393": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:close to the bathing pool; next to a wall decorated with marble tiles;"
  },
  "8394": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the far right of this row;"
  },
  "8395": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:faced with an empty space;"
  },
  "8396": {
    "question": "Question:what does the fireplace look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a black old curved fireplace."
  },
  "8397": {
    "question": "Question:where is the fireplace?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is beside two chairs."
  },
  "8398": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the fireplace in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in a living room."
  },
  "8399": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the fireplace?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's beside a kitchen."
  },
  "8400": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cylindrical, metallic, tall"
  },
  "8401": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the cabinet which is on the left of the television, in front of a picture"
  },
  "8402": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is located in the livingroom."
  },
  "8403": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The livingroom is on the first floor and next to the kitchen and dining room."
  },
  "8404": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a large, white bed filled with cotton."
  },
  "8405": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a desk lamp and table beside it."
  },
  "8406": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in the bedroom."
  },
  "8407": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is beside the corridor."
  },
  "8408": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, white, rectangular"
  },
  "8409": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:facing a black table, in front of a window"
  },
  "8410": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is placed in a tiny and bright living on the first floor."
  },
  "8411": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is next to a washroom and is connected with a corridor."
  },
  "8412": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, white, rectangular"
  },
  "8413": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:facing a black table, in front of a window"
  },
  "8414": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is placed in a tiny and bright living on the first floor."
  },
  "8415": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is next to a washroom and is connected with a corridor."
  },
  "8416": {
    "question": "Question:what does the painting look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Small, rectangular and brown."
  },
  "8417": {
    "question": "Question:where is the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is set above two black screens and a keyboard."
  },
  "8418": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the painting in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is in a bedroom."
  },
  "8419": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is near a corridor."
  },
  "8420": {
    "question": "Question:what does the Nightstand look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the floor,rectangle and woody"
  },
  "8421": {
    "question": "Question:where is the Nightstand?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a bedside lamp on the nightstand and a bed next to it"
  },
  "8422": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the Nightstand in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's on side of the room"
  },
  "8423": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the Nightstand?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's near the corridor"
  },
  "8424": {
    "question": "Question:what does the washbasin look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, small"
  },
  "8425": {
    "question": "Question:where is the washbasin?",
    "answer": "Answer:below the mirror and the lamp"
  },
  "8426": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the washbasin in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the bedroom"
  },
  "8427": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the washbasin?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the living room and on the second floor."
  },
  "8428": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pillow look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cloth, square, cream color"
  },
  "8429": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the sofa, among three pillows and on the right of them"
  },
  "8430": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pillow in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The pillow is set in the livingroom. "
  },
  "8431": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:The livingroom is on the first and next to the kitchen and dining room."
  },
  "8432": {
    "question": "Question:what does the toilet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:oval, white and smooth"
  },
  "8433": {
    "question": "Question:where is the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to the door and the towels."
  },
  "8434": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the toilet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a restroom on the first floor."
  },
  "8435": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The restroom is in the bedroom which is at the right turn of the gate."
  },
  "8436": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Wooden, soild and brown."
  },
  "8437": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is set next to a gray and black bed and on the left side of a black and brown chair."
  },
  "8438": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is in a bedroom."
  },
  "8439": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is near a corridor and a bathroom."
  },
  "8440": {
    "question": "Question:what does the tissue look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, cylindrical and rolled"
  },
  "8441": {
    "question": "Question:where is the tissue?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed on a cabinet and close to a bread maker."
  },
  "8442": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the tissue in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "8443": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the tissue?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to the chatting room and the door."
  },
  "8444": {
    "question": "Question:what does the outlet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:plastic, white, rectangle"
  },
  "8445": {
    "question": "Question:where is the outlet?",
    "answer": "Answer:under the mirror, On the wall above the sink"
  },
  "8446": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the outlet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's installed in a bathroom."
  },
  "8447": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the outlet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathroom is built in the main room which  faces the balcony. Right below the room is the swimming pool."
  },
  "8448": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Cylindrical,big,transparent"
  },
  "8449": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is set in a corner ,next to a fire extinguisher and a door."
  },
  "8450": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is placed in the corridor."
  },
  "8451": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is placed  near a big conference room and a small conference room."
  },
  "8452": {
    "question": "Question:what does the painting look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:colorful,medium-size,hanged on the wall "
  },
  "8453": {
    "question": "Question:where is the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the left of the cabinet and another painting"
  },
  "8454": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the painting in?",
    "answer": "Answer:hanged on the wall of corridor"
  },
  "8455": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:there are a bedroom ,a bath room and a room around the corridor"
  },
  "8456": {
    "question": "Question:what does the toilet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:middle size,ceramic ,white and smooth"
  },
  "8457": {
    "question": "Question:where is the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's below a window and next to a rack."
  },
  "8458": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the toilet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a small washroom on the second floor"
  },
  "8459": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:the washroom is in front of a bathroom and next to a dressing room."
  },
  "8460": {
    "question": "Question:what does the armchair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:stand on the floor,leather,red"
  },
  "8461": {
    "question": "Question:where is the armchair?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the table and in front of a painting"
  },
  "8462": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the armchair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a family cinema"
  },
  "8463": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the armchair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's close to toilet"
  },
  "8464": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:tall, woody, bright"
  },
  "8465": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the sofa and the staircase"
  },
  "8466": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the living room"
  },
  "8467": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the staircase and on the third floor."
  },
  "8468": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cloth, rectangular, white"
  },
  "8469": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a table, facing a chair"
  },
  "8470": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is placed in the center of a bedroom on the first floor."
  },
  "8471": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is next to a bashroom and connected with a dining room."
  },
  "8472": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cloth, rectangular, white"
  },
  "8473": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a table, facing a chair"
  },
  "8474": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is placed in the center of a bedroom on the first floor."
  },
  "8475": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is next to a bashroom and connected with a dining room."
  },
  "8476": {
    "question": "Question:what does the switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:square, white, plastic"
  },
  "8477": {
    "question": "Question:where is the switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a tap on its left, and it face the big cabinet."
  },
  "8478": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's installed in a  open kitchen."
  },
  "8479": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the switch?",
    "answer": "Answer: Here you can see the swimming pool, reception area and a wicket."
  },
  "8480": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:gray,long,soft"
  },
  "8481": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in front of a fireplace ,next to a short stool and a black table with a bunch of flowers."
  },
  "8482": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's located in the center of a  living room on first floor."
  },
  "8483": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:the living room is near a dining room,kitchen and a corridor."
  },
  "8484": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is big, square and plastic."
  },
  "8485": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a table in front of the sofa. The pillow is on the sofa."
  },
  "8486": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is placed behind the table in the balcony."
  },
  "8487": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are many recliners, stools and desk in the balcony."
  },
  "8488": {
    "question": "Question:what does the light look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Veined, round tabled and luminescent"
  },
  "8489": {
    "question": "Question:where is the light?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed on a woody cabinet and beside a green plant."
  },
  "8490": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the light in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a bedroom on the largest cabinet of this room."
  },
  "8491": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the light?",
    "answer": "Answer:This bedroom is located at the end of the right turn on the second floor, opposite a storage room."
  },
  "8492": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown;wooden;simple;"
  },
  "8493": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:under a pot; next to a glass shower cubicle;"
  },
  "8494": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:innermost of the whole room."
  },
  "8495": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:a long room within only one narrow bed and wooden floors;"
  },
  "8496": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pillow look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A small light yellow pillow."
  },
  "8497": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on a medium-sized bed and between two grey pillows."
  },
  "8498": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pillow in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is also near a white lamp,in a relatively small bedroom."
  },
  "8499": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near another bedroom."
  },
  "8500": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:quite small  one ,stands at the corner ,made of wood"
  },
  "8501": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:close to two picture which are put on the side wall ,the target is at the corner outside the bedroom ,in the porch "
  },
  "8502": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The small wooden chair is put at the corner outside the living room in the porch ,under a black handicraft."
  },
  "8503": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are many beautiful pictures put on the side wall of the porch "
  },
  "8504": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, cylinder, ceramic"
  },
  "8505": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:on a stone table, next to some fruit"
  },
  "8506": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is placed in the center of a kitchen with wood floor."
  },
  "8507": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to a small storeroom and there is a cloakroom upstairs."
  },
  "8508": {
    "question": "Question:what does the toilet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soild, small and white."
  },
  "8509": {
    "question": "Question:where is the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The toilet is opposite to a brown drawer and near a white sink."
  },
  "8510": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the toilet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The toilet is in a toilet."
  },
  "8511": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The toilet is near a living room and a bedroom."
  },
  "8512": {
    "question": "Question:what does the glasses look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Rectangular, big and transparent."
  },
  "8513": {
    "question": "Question:where is the glasses?",
    "answer": "Answer:The glasses are set opposite to a white and brown bed, two skateboards and two brassy lamps."
  },
  "8514": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the glasses in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The glasses are in a bedroom."
  },
  "8515": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the glasses?",
    "answer": "Answer:The glasses are near a balcony and a toilet."
  },
  "8516": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Rectangular, brown and tall."
  },
  "8517": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is aet behind the tiger skin rug, near a blue leather sofa and between two windows."
  },
  "8518": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is set in a bedroom with a blue carpet."
  },
  "8519": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is on the opppsite side of a stair of a corridor."
  },
  "8520": {
    "question": "Question:what does the outlet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:square, plastic"
  },
  "8521": {
    "question": "Question:where is the outlet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's facing the display and two plants."
  },
  "8522": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the outlet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is installed on the wall at the edge of the open kitchen"
  },
  "8523": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the outlet?",
    "answer": "Answer:Here you can see the swimming pool, reception area and a wicket."
  },
  "8524": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:woody, large, yellow"
  },
  "8525": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:surrounded by eight woody,yellow chairs,in front of a brown and white wall painting,next to potted plants"
  },
  "8526": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is set in the living room."
  },
  "8527": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is next to the kitchen and near the French door leaded to the courtyard."
  },
  "8528": {
    "question": "Question:what does the dispenser look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white; oblong; plastic;"
  },
  "8529": {
    "question": "Question:where is the dispenser?",
    "answer": "Answer:under a blue bucket. below a squared picture."
  },
  "8530": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the dispenser in?",
    "answer": "Answer:behind a bar facing two white stools."
  },
  "8531": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the dispenser?",
    "answer": "Answer:a small recieption in front of the massage areas."
  },
  "8532": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:steel and wood, rectangular, white"
  },
  "8533": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:surrounded by six rattan chairs, next to a wall painting and a mirror."
  },
  "8534": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is in the dining room and on the second floor."
  },
  "8535": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is near the kitchen, the bathroom, the study."
  },
  "8536": {
    "question": "Question:what does the door look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, woody and open"
  },
  "8537": {
    "question": "Question:where is the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to the carpet and the basin."
  },
  "8538": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the door in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a restroom on the second floor."
  },
  "8539": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:The restroom is on the life side of the stairs."
  },
  "8540": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white; oblong; shallow;"
  },
  "8541": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:beside five white bottles;below a long mirror with double golden frames;"
  },
  "8542": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:faced with an advanced big machine;"
  },
  "8543": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:a room within three advanced instruments;"
  },
  "8544": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a square, medium-sized white stool."
  },
  "8545": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is beside a table and a sofa."
  },
  "8546": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the living room.\n"
  },
  "8547": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:This living room is very neat and white.\n"
  },
  "8548": {
    "question": "Question:what does the desk look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Brown, soild and wooden."
  },
  "8549": {
    "question": "Question:where is the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:The desk is set on a red quadrate carpet with white flowers and yellow flowers, near a red bed and a red sofa with a white blanket on it."
  },
  "8550": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the desk in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The desk is set in a bedroom."
  },
  "8551": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is near a corridor and a wooden stair."
  },
  "8552": {
    "question": "Question:what does the door handle look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Small, metal and silver."
  },
  "8553": {
    "question": "Question:where is the door handle?",
    "answer": "Answer:The door handle is on the door, next to the bathtub."
  },
  "8554": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the door handle in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The door handle is in the bathroom."
  },
  "8555": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the door handle?",
    "answer": "Answer:The door handle is close to the toilet and bedroom."
  },
  "8556": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:slender,tall and metal."
  },
  "8557": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is on the nightstand and near the bed."
  },
  "8558": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is in the bedroom."
  },
  "8559": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is near the balcony and living room.\n"
  },
  "8560": {
    "question": "Question:what does the fruit look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:round, green and piled"
  },
  "8561": {
    "question": "Question:where is the fruit?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is above the table in a bowl."
  },
  "8562": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the fruit in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the dining hall on the first floor."
  },
  "8563": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the fruit?",
    "answer": "Answer:The dining hall is next to the kitchen and the stairs."
  },
  "8564": {
    "question": "Question:what does the photo frame look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Rectangular, vertical, wooden"
  },
  "8565": {
    "question": "Question:where is the photo frame?",
    "answer": "Answer:The photo frame is placed on a table in front of a mirror and next to a blue photo frame."
  },
  "8566": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the photo frame in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The photo frame is placed in the corridor."
  },
  "8567": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the photo frame?",
    "answer": "Answer:The photo frame is placed near a big conference room and a small conference room."
  },
  "8568": {
    "question": "Question:what does the beach chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:gray, rectangle,  armless "
  },
  "8569": {
    "question": "Question:where is the beach chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:Standing outside the door and looking in, on its right is another same beach chair, there is a little round stool between two chair"
  },
  "8570": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the beach chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in a second-floor balcony, which facing the main bedroom"
  },
  "8571": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the beach chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The balcony is on the second floor of the villa, directly below the garden"
  },
  "8572": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle, cotton"
  },
  "8573": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:two pillows are put on it, It's face a black table."
  },
  "8574": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's put in the work room."
  },
  "8575": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:Work room face the dinning room."
  },
  "8576": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A  medium-sized bed with grey sheets and pillows."
  },
  "8577": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is between two narrow windows and near a grey sofa."
  },
  "8578": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a bedroom which connects with a bathroom."
  },
  "8579": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a bathroom and an empty room."
  },
  "8580": {
    "question": "Question:what does the power switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is plastic, small and white."
  },
  "8581": {
    "question": "Question:where is the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is on the wall and beside the staircase."
  },
  "8582": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the power switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is in the aisle beside the stairs."
  },
  "8583": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is on the wall and beside the staircase."
  },
  "8584": {
    "question": "Question:what does the laundry basket look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, brown, rectangular"
  },
  "8585": {
    "question": "Question:where is the laundry basket?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a storage cabinet, next to a carpet"
  },
  "8586": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the laundry basket in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The laundry basket is located in a sauna."
  },
  "8587": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the laundry basket?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are two massage beds and a class cabinet in this sauna."
  },
  "8588": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black, circle, wood"
  },
  "8589": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:under a vase and is next to a sofa"
  },
  "8590": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is placed in a bright and clean bedroom."
  },
  "8591": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is next to a bashroom and connected with a kitchen."
  },
  "8592": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden,square and comfortable."
  },
  "8593": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is close to the desk and the glass door."
  },
  "8594": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is on the balcony."
  },
  "8595": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set near the bedroom and living room."
  },
  "8596": {
    "question": "Question:what does the plants look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:green,lush and brown"
  },
  "8597": {
    "question": "Question:where is the plants?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's near a sofa under the sunshine and next to a window."
  },
  "8598": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the plants in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in the corner of the open-balcony on the second floor."
  },
  "8599": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the plants?",
    "answer": "Answer:the open-balcony is near a living room and a kitchen."
  },
  "8600": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A long white outdoor chair."
  },
  "8601": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to a white stone table and near some big windows."
  },
  "8602": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed outside the house in the yard."
  },
  "8603": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is close to the entrance of the house."
  },
  "8604": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, brown, leather"
  },
  "8605": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the left of the table, on the carpet, next to the window"
  },
  "8606": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is located in the spacious livingroom."
  },
  "8607": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The livingroom is on the first floor and next to the dining room."
  },
  "8608": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, white, soft"
  },
  "8609": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:across from the cabinet, next to the white lamp"
  },
  "8610": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the bedroom"
  },
  "8611": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the living room and the corridor and on the third floor."
  },
  "8612": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Brown, small and wooden."
  },
  "8613": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is set in a brown cabinet and near a gray and black bed."
  },
  "8614": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is in a bedroom."
  },
  "8615": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is near a corridor and a bathroom."
  },
  "8616": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White,wooden,hard"
  },
  "8617": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is set behind of a  black computer and near a red stairs."
  },
  "8618": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is placed in the front desk."
  },
  "8619": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is placed next to the hall and a stairs."
  },
  "8620": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black with  a grey surface;short;"
  },
  "8621": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:beside a tall and transparent cabinet; faces the round table as the front desk of this whole bath center;"
  },
  "8622": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:almost at the corner of this hall;"
  },
  "8623": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:the entrance of the whole bath center;"
  },
  "8624": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black, rectangle, wooden"
  },
  "8625": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table was laid out on the carpet. A book is put on it."
  },
  "8626": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's put in the work room."
  },
  "8627": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:Work room face the dinning room."
  },
  "8628": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle, transparent "
  },
  "8629": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are six chairs around the table. A plant is put on it."
  },
  "8630": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It was placed in the hallway between the open kitchen and the pool."
  },
  "8631": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:There's a pool on one side and an open kitchen on the other"
  },
  "8632": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black, rectangular, ratten"
  },
  "8633": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of the French door and next to the rectangular, ratten and black table and seven chairs with the same color and shape "
  },
  "8634": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in the balcony. "
  },
  "8635": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The balcony is next to the living room and in front of the coutyard with a swimming pool."
  },
  "8636": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soild, wooden and yellow."
  },
  "8637": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is settled near a red and brown chair, on the left side of a black bookshelf under a sculpture and two photos."
  },
  "8638": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is at the corner of a study."
  },
  "8639": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set near a corridor on the second floor."
  },
  "8640": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Cuboid, soild and white."
  },
  "8641": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is set near a white and brown bed and a rectangular painting."
  },
  "8642": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is in a bedroom."
  },
  "8643": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is next to a toilet."
  },
  "8644": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Red and brown, medium size and soild."
  },
  "8645": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set on the left side of a brown wooden desk, behind a round wooden table and on the opposite side of a tall carbinet."
  },
  "8646": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in a corridor on the second floor."
  },
  "8647": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is next to a living room."
  },
  "8648": {
    "question": "Question:what does the plant look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, cylindrical, green"
  },
  "8649": {
    "question": "Question:where is the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the right side of the stone table, next to the glass door, in front of the glass window"
  },
  "8650": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the plant in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The plant is set in the spacious kitchen.\n"
  },
  "8651": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is on the third floor, next to the livingroom and next to the dining room."
  },
  "8652": {
    "question": "Question:what does the towel look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:column, white, soft"
  },
  "8653": {
    "question": "Question:where is the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:between a painting and a hand sink"
  },
  "8654": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the towel in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is put in a bathroom belong to the bedroom which is face the stairs"
  },
  "8655": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is next to the toilet. It is located in the second floor and there is a swimming pool downstairs. "
  },
  "8656": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bath look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A white square metal bath."
  },
  "8657": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bath?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is under a window and near a picture and a glass chair."
  },
  "8658": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bath in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a bathroom."
  },
  "8659": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bath?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a toilet and two sinks."
  },
  "8660": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cahir look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black, small, rectangular"
  },
  "8661": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cahir?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a bed, facing a chair"
  },
  "8662": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cahir in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is settled in the center of a big bedroom."
  },
  "8663": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cahir?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is next to a corridor and there is a living room downstairs."
  },
  "8664": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A black leather chair with a large backrest."
  },
  "8665": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is beside a white box and a yellow desk."
  },
  "8666": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is set near the corridor on the second floor."
  },
  "8667": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near the stairway , a kitchen and a bedroom."
  },
  "8668": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bottle look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:transparent, glass, big"
  },
  "8669": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bottle?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the table which is in the middle of two sofas, behind the photo"
  },
  "8670": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bottle in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bottle is set in the bright livingroom."
  },
  "8671": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bottle?",
    "answer": "Answer:The livingroom is on the first floor and next to the dining room."
  },
  "8672": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular; white;ceramic;"
  },
  "8673": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:in the middle of two identical sinks; opposite a shower cubicle;"
  },
  "8674": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:by side and at the end of the hallway;"
  },
  "8675": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:a men's changing room."
  },
  "8676": {
    "question": "Question:what does the drawer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is square, wooden and closed."
  },
  "8677": {
    "question": "Question:where is the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a oven next to the drawer and a television above the drawer."
  },
  "8678": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the drawer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is placed next to the drawer below the television in the kitchen."
  },
  "8679": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are two big tables and a wine cabinet on the opposite of the drawer."
  },
  "8680": {
    "question": "Question:what does the desk look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Brown, square and neat."
  },
  "8681": {
    "question": "Question:where is the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:The desk is next to the sofa with a vase on it."
  },
  "8682": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the desk in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Desk is in living room."
  },
  "8683": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:The desk is close to the balcony and the bedroom."
  },
  "8684": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, white"
  },
  "8685": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:below the mirror, next to the vase"
  },
  "8686": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the bathroom."
  },
  "8687": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the corridor and the children's room."
  },
  "8688": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is large, round and ceramic."
  },
  "8689": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is below the vase and above the carpet."
  },
  "8690": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is in the living room."
  },
  "8691": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is below the vase and above the carpet."
  },
  "8692": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chandelier look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:round,transparent,fragile"
  },
  "8693": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chandelier?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's above a bed and hang on the ceiling."
  },
  "8694": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chandelier in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a bedroom with a washroom and a storage room on the second floor."
  },
  "8695": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chandelier?",
    "answer": "Answer:the bedroom is near a corridor and a living room."
  },
  "8696": {
    "question": "Question:what does the flower look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:tall,elegant,in a mental vase"
  },
  "8697": {
    "question": "Question:where is the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a glass item and near a washstand on a table."
  },
  "8698": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the flower in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a bathroom on the second floor."
  },
  "8699": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:the bathroom is in a big bedroom which is near a open-balcony,and near a washroom,dressing room."
  },
  "8700": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:red ,big,leathery"
  },
  "8701": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in front of two sofa"
  },
  "8702": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a family cinema"
  },
  "8703": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's close to living room"
  },
  "8704": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:standing on the nightstand,cloth and glass,brown and white"
  },
  "8705": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to the bed and the box"
  },
  "8706": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's behind the bed and in front of the mirror"
  },
  "8707": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's behind the corridor"
  },
  "8708": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pillow look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cloth, square, small"
  },
  "8709": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the long sofa, among six pillows and on the right of them"
  },
  "8710": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pillow in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The pillow is set in the livingroom."
  },
  "8711": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:The livingroom is on the first floor and next to the kitchen."
  },
  "8712": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White and golden, big and porcelainous."
  },
  "8713": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is on the left side of a big vase and behind a brown table which is surrounded by eight chairs."
  },
  "8714": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is in a dining room."
  },
  "8715": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is near a kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "8716": {
    "question": "Question:what does the printer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cubic,medium-size,white"
  },
  "8717": {
    "question": "Question:where is the printer?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's on the drawer and under the sculpter"
  },
  "8718": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the printer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in the study"
  },
  "8719": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the printer?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's dining room outside the study"
  },
  "8720": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:steel, errect and stick"
  },
  "8721": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed between the door and the window."
  },
  "8722": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a chatting room on the first floor."
  },
  "8723": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chatting room is next to the hall."
  },
  "8724": {
    "question": "Question:what does the painting look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, normal size, wall-mounted"
  },
  "8725": {
    "question": "Question:where is the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:hung on the wall, next to the washing machine"
  },
  "8726": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the painting in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the laundry."
  },
  "8727": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the staircase and the corridor."
  },
  "8728": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden and leather, brown, small"
  },
  "8729": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:under the table, among four stools and second from left "
  },
  "8730": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is set in the bright kitchen."
  },
  "8731": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is on the first floor and next to the livingroom."
  },
  "8732": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bathtub look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:marble, rectangle and white"
  },
  "8733": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bathtub?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed on the right side of the door beneath the window."
  },
  "8734": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bathtub in?",
    "answer": "Answer:\nIt is in a restroom on the first floor."
  },
  "8735": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bathtub?",
    "answer": "Answer:The restroom is in the bedroom which is at the right turn of the gate."
  },
  "8736": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:thin, yellow, metallic"
  },
  "8737": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the woody table, next to the laptop and white table"
  },
  "8738": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is in the bedroom."
  },
  "8739": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is next to the door of the bedroom and in front of the bed."
  },
  "8740": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, medium, white"
  },
  "8741": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of a woody table with a white chair, next to a window with black curtains."
  },
  "8742": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is in the bedroom."
  },
  "8743": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is next to the stairs and near the closed door on the third floor."
  },
  "8744": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, circle, gray."
  },
  "8745": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:between two beach chairs, There is a small potted plant on the table."
  },
  "8746": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in a second-floor balcony, which facing the main bedroom."
  },
  "8747": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The balcony is on the second floor of the villa, directly below the garden."
  },
  "8748": {
    "question": "Question:what does the flower look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is withering, white and long."
  },
  "8749": {
    "question": "Question:where is the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is placed in the vase on the table."
  },
  "8750": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the flower in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is placed in the vase on the table in the living room."
  },
  "8751": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are many paintings on the wall of the living room."
  },
  "8752": {
    "question": "Question:what does the plant look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:green,wooden,erect stems with many leaves"
  },
  "8753": {
    "question": "Question:where is the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the right side of the dustbin and in front of a white pillar and the glass wall"
  },
  "8754": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the plant in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The plant is in a vast reading hall. "
  },
  "8755": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:The reading hall is behind the restaurant and near a meeting room and some boothes."
  },
  "8756": {
    "question": "Question:what does the dustbin look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:short,cuboid,plastic,black,empty,coverd by a plastic bag"
  },
  "8757": {
    "question": "Question:where is the dustbin?",
    "answer": "Answer:The dustbin is on the left side of two stools,on the right of the desk and under the document holder."
  },
  "8758": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the dustbin in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The dustbin is in the number 365 reception room ."
  },
  "8759": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the dustbin?",
    "answer": "Answer:The room is nearly at the end of a corridor ,next to a hollow office,and faces the stairs of exit at a slant."
  },
  "8760": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White double bed with white quilt."
  },
  "8761": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a mirror next to the bed with a wooden window."
  },
  "8762": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is in the bedroom."
  },
  "8763": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is next to the glass window and opposite the balcony with a view of the courtyard."
  },
  "8764": {
    "question": "Question:what does the power switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is small, square and white."
  },
  "8765": {
    "question": "Question:where is the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:The poster is on the opposite. The door is besides."
  },
  "8766": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the power switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is on the opposite of the poster next to the door."
  },
  "8767": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are many posters in the corridor."
  },
  "8768": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Brown,rectangular,wooden."
  },
  "8769": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is placed under a table with green top and in the lower left corner of the table."
  },
  "8770": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is set in the hall."
  },
  "8771": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is set near a small conference and the gate."
  },
  "8772": {
    "question": "Question:what does the drawer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Brown and black, cuboid and small."
  },
  "8773": {
    "question": "Question:where is the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is settled under a white and brown lamp and opposite to a gray and brown bed."
  },
  "8774": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the drawer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is in a bedroom."
  },
  "8775": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is near a corridor and a living room."
  },
  "8776": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bottle look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:glass, black and fragile."
  },
  "8777": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bottle?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bottle is on a table and near two red chairs."
  },
  "8778": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bottle in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bottle is in a big and bright living room."
  },
  "8779": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bottle?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area leads to outdoors via glass doors and connects with two small rooms."
  },
  "8780": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bush look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:purple and red,tall,lush"
  },
  "8781": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bush?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's near to a exit door and next to a gray wall.it's next to a potting"
  },
  "8782": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bush in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a garden on the second floor"
  },
  "8783": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bush?",
    "answer": "Answer:the garden is near a balcony which is near a study room with a stari"
  },
  "8784": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is irony, square and standing."
  },
  "8785": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are some pictures and laptop on the desk."
  },
  "8786": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The desk is placed in the bedroom next to the bed."
  },
  "8787": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a big bed in the bedroom."
  },
  "8788": {
    "question": "Question:what does the box look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden, big, brown"
  },
  "8789": {
    "question": "Question:where is the box?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the door, below the picture frames"
  },
  "8790": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the box in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The box is settled in the corridor on the second floor."
  },
  "8791": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the box?",
    "answer": "Answer:The corridor is bright and narrow with the wooden rail."
  },
  "8792": {
    "question": "Question:what does the washing machine look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:stand on the floor,cubic,white"
  },
  "8793": {
    "question": "Question:where is the washing machine?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the table and the wash basin"
  },
  "8794": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the washing machine in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's at the center of the room"
  },
  "8795": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the washing machine?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's on the right side of the bedroom"
  },
  "8796": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, white"
  },
  "8797": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the wall, below the picture"
  },
  "8798": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the corridor."
  },
  "8799": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the bathroom and the study."
  },
  "8800": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:midnight blue, medium, rectangular"
  },
  "8801": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer: The sofa is next to another sofa with the same color and shape and behind the French window."
  },
  "8802": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in the living room on the second floor."
  },
  "8803": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is next to a door and in front of a glass desk."
  },
  "8804": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is plastic, large and tall."
  },
  "8805": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is on the table and to the right of the door."
  },
  "8806": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is in the lounge."
  },
  "8807": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is on the table and to the right of the door."
  },
  "8808": {
    "question": "Question:what does the toilet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:elliptical, ceramic, white"
  },
  "8809": {
    "question": "Question:where is the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the washroom, under the picture"
  },
  "8810": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the toilet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The toilet is set in the washroom."
  },
  "8811": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washroom is on the first floor and next to the livingroom."
  },
  "8812": {
    "question": "Question:what does the drawer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:closed,square,white."
  },
  "8813": {
    "question": "Question:where is the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's on the left of the washing machine and under the computer"
  },
  "8814": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the drawer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's on the left side of washing machine and washstand"
  },
  "8815": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:there is a bedroom across the corridor"
  },
  "8816": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A white stone outdoor table"
  },
  "8817": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is beside a bench and big windows and there are some potted plants and bottles on it."
  },
  "8818": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near the entrance of the house."
  },
  "8819": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near the living room of the ground floor."
  },
  "8820": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stove look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, black,"
  },
  "8821": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stove?",
    "answer": "Answer:across from the staircase, below the clock"
  },
  "8822": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stove in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the living "
  },
  "8823": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stove?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the staircase and on the third floor."
  },
  "8824": {
    "question": "Question:what does the dispenser look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white; oblong; plastic;"
  },
  "8825": {
    "question": "Question:where is the dispenser?",
    "answer": "Answer:below a round clock; three deck chairs near it;"
  },
  "8826": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the dispenser in?",
    "answer": "Answer:almost at the turning of the corridor;"
  },
  "8827": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the dispenser?",
    "answer": "Answer:a very wide and long corridor with many doors leading to different rooms"
  },
  "8828": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:covered by leather ;brown and sunk."
  },
  "8829": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:below a wooden holder; towards a mirror with black frames."
  },
  "8830": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:almost in the middle of two sinks."
  },
  "8831": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:an empty space at the entrance of the room."
  },
  "8832": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, cylinder, white"
  },
  "8833": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:on a table, next to a bed"
  },
  "8834": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is settled in the corner of a bedroom on the first floor."
  },
  "8835": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is next to a bashroom on the first floor."
  },
  "8836": {
    "question": "Question:what does the display look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:metal,rectangle,black"
  },
  "8837": {
    "question": "Question:where is the display?",
    "answer": "Answer:above the shell,on the wall and behind the desk"
  },
  "8838": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the display in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is in the number 02 small meeting room."
  },
  "8839": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the display?",
    "answer": "Answer:The meeting room is between two meeting rooms,behind the stairway door and in front of the lobby."
  },
  "8840": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:blue, medium, rectangular"
  },
  "8841": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is in front of the mirror and the armoire, There are quilts decorated by triangles, rectangles and so on of a full range of colors on the bed."
  },
  "8842": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is in the bedroom."
  },
  "8843": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is behind a blue wall painting and near the stairs on the third floor."
  },
  "8844": {
    "question": "Question:what does the glass look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Rectangular, soild and transparent."
  },
  "8845": {
    "question": "Question:where is the glass?",
    "answer": "Answer:The glass is behind a transparent dining-table and beside a picture with white border."
  },
  "8846": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the glass in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The glass is in a dining room."
  },
  "8847": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the glass?",
    "answer": "Answer:The glass is near a living room."
  },
  "8848": {
    "question": "Question:what does the towel look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is soft, rectangular and white."
  },
  "8849": {
    "question": "Question:where is the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is above the pool and beside the door."
  },
  "8850": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the towel in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is inside the bathroom."
  },
  "8851": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is above the pool and beside the door."
  },
  "8852": {
    "question": "Question:what does the book look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, square, papery"
  },
  "8853": {
    "question": "Question:where is the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the third row of the bookcase, on the right of the television"
  },
  "8854": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the book in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The book is set in the small bedroom."
  },
  "8855": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is in the end of the corridor and on the right of the end."
  },
  "8856": {
    "question": "Question:what does the wardrobe look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, rectangle, wooden brown"
  },
  "8857": {
    "question": "Question:where is the wardrobe?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's facing a black and tallow painting. It's next to a door."
  },
  "8858": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the wardrobe in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's put in the work room."
  },
  "8859": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the wardrobe?",
    "answer": "Answer:Work room face the dinning room."
  },
  "8860": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:glass, bright, rectangular"
  },
  "8861": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the vase, above the sank"
  },
  "8862": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the bathroom."
  },
  "8863": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the corridor and the children's room."
  },
  "8864": {
    "question": "Question:what does the glass look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:glassy, empty, transparent"
  },
  "8865": {
    "question": "Question:where is the glass?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the furnace, next to a picture"
  },
  "8866": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the glass in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The glass is put in a study,"
  },
  "8867": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the glass?",
    "answer": "Answer:The study has two pictures on the wall and connects with the outside via a door."
  },
  "8868": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Metal, white and brassy and soild."
  },
  "8869": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is on a black hollow table, next to a black telephone and opposite to a electronic keyboard."
  },
  "8870": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is in a living room."
  },
  "8871": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is near a bedroom."
  },
  "8872": {
    "question": "Question:what does the telephone look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:oblong;small;grey;"
  },
  "8873": {
    "question": "Question:where is the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the wallpaper; opposite a wall with a mirror."
  },
  "8874": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the telephone in?",
    "answer": "Answer:at the entrance of the room;"
  },
  "8875": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:a room within a shower room and a sink;"
  },
  "8876": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A small transparent glass chair."
  },
  "8877": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is beside a bath and under some towels."
  },
  "8878": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a bathroom."
  },
  "8879": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a toilet and two sinks."
  },
  "8880": {
    "question": "Question:what does the television look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Black, metal and cubiod."
  },
  "8881": {
    "question": "Question:where is the television?",
    "answer": "Answer:The television is set on a yellow and white table and near a gray and black bed."
  },
  "8882": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the television in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The television is in a bedroom."
  },
  "8883": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the television?",
    "answer": "Answer:The television is near a corridor and a living room."
  },
  "8884": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown,big,leathery"
  },
  "8885": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's behind a desk and television"
  },
  "8886": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in the living room."
  },
  "8887": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's close to the family cinema"
  },
  "8888": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:square,cloth,grey"
  },
  "8889": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's on the left of mirror  and on the right of the door"
  },
  "8890": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in the bedroom."
  },
  "8891": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a bathroom  on the left of it"
  },
  "8892": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bottle look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:glass, small, transparent"
  },
  "8893": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bottle?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the table, next to the vase, behind the photo"
  },
  "8894": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bottle in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bottle is set in the spacious livingroom."
  },
  "8895": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bottle?",
    "answer": "Answer:The livingroom is on the first floor and next to the kitchen."
  },
  "8896": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bathtub look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, big "
  },
  "8897": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bathtub?",
    "answer": "Answer:below the mirror and across from the bed"
  },
  "8898": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bathtub in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the bedroom "
  },
  "8899": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bathtub?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the corridor and another bedroom."
  },
  "8900": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, small-sized, white and green"
  },
  "8901": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to another bed with the same color and shape, in front of a black and white wall painting, near the window"
  },
  "8902": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is in the bedroom."
  },
  "8903": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is in front of the bathroom on the third floor and next to the stairs."
  },
  "8904": {
    "question": "Question:what does the drawer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is wooden, square and small."
  },
  "8905": {
    "question": "Question:where is the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is placed below the oven near the floor. "
  },
  "8906": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the drawer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is placed below the oven near the floor in the kitchen."
  },
  "8907": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are two big tables and a wine cabinet on the opposite."
  },
  "8908": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, tall, glass"
  },
  "8909": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:across from the bed, next to the door"
  },
  "8910": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the children's bedroom."
  },
  "8911": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the study and the bathroom."
  },
  "8912": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is h-shaped, red and leather."
  },
  "8913": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is on the left side of a wooden carbinet and on the right side of a small wooden table under a vase with roses."
  },
  "8914": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is at the corner of a bedroom on the second floor."
  },
  "8915": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is near a empty room."
  },
  "8916": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White and porcelain sink with a iron tap."
  },
  "8917": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is installed on a white platform and is front of a mirror."
  },
  "8918": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is in the restroom."
  },
  "8919": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is in the toilet beside a bedroom."
  },
  "8920": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Brown, big and round."
  },
  "8921": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is surrounded by four brown chairs and under a blue and white vase."
  },
  "8922": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is in a living room."
  },
  "8923": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is near a bedroom."
  },
  "8924": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A square wooden high-leg stool"
  },
  "8925": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near some metal items ,white bottles and newspapers and beside the ring table."
  },
  "8926": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the living room."
  },
  "8927": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a stair and a storage room."
  },
  "8928": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A big white sofa formed by two smaller sofas."
  },
  "8929": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:It faces the projector and a black desk."
  },
  "8930": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the living room."
  },
  "8931": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a big carpet."
  },
  "8932": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:crooked,white,metal"
  },
  "8933": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:on a book,behind a green book,next to the glass wall and on the left of the photo frame"
  },
  "8934": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is in a small office."
  },
  "8935": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is at the corner of a junction of three roads and next to the corridor door."
  },
  "8936": {
    "question": "Question:what does the switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A small white switch on the wall."
  },
  "8937": {
    "question": "Question:where is the switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a white closed door and near the corridor."
  },
  "8938": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near the entrance of a hall on the second floor."
  },
  "8939": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near the stair and a bedroom."
  },
  "8940": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Black, round, short."
  },
  "8941": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are green plants in the vase at the corner."
  },
  "8942": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is in the study."
  },
  "8943": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase gym is next door, near the desk."
  },
  "8944": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, wooden and metallic, brown"
  },
  "8945": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:under the big table, in front of the stairs, among four stools and second from left"
  },
  "8946": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is set in the middle of the kitchen."
  },
  "8947": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to the dining room, facing the stairs and on the third floor."
  },
  "8948": {
    "question": "Question:what does the model plane look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden,small,brown"
  },
  "8949": {
    "question": "Question:where is the model plane?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the left side of the timeglass on the shell,above some books and under the displayer"
  },
  "8950": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the model plane in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The model plane is in a meeting room that has the number 05."
  },
  "8951": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the model plane?",
    "answer": "Answer:The meeting room is by the side of the vast reading area and behind the restaurant."
  },
  "8952": {
    "question": "Question:what does the telephone look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Quadrangular, small and white."
  },
  "8953": {
    "question": "Question:where is the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:The telephone is on the right side of a green bed and next to a white and brassy lamp."
  },
  "8954": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the telephone in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The telephone is in a bedroom."
  },
  "8955": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:The telephone is near a toilet and a corridor."
  },
  "8956": {
    "question": "Question:what does the shower look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:tall, metallic, orbicular"
  },
  "8957": {
    "question": "Question:where is the shower?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the closestool, near the window"
  },
  "8958": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the shower in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The shower is in the bathroom."
  },
  "8959": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the shower?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathroom is next to the cloakroom and in the master bedroom."
  },
  "8960": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bookshelf look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, tall, stable"
  },
  "8961": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bookshelf?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to stairs, in the corner"
  },
  "8962": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bookshelf in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bookshelf is located in the bar."
  },
  "8963": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bookshelf?",
    "answer": "Answer:This bar has decorations on the wall and has a bar counter."
  },
  "8964": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Big, rectangular and beige."
  },
  "8965": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is settled near a transparent oval table and opposite to a long black sofa."
  },
  "8966": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in a living room."
  },
  "8967": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is near a balcony and a dining room."
  },
  "8968": {
    "question": "Question:what does the clock look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown and white, middle, round"
  },
  "8969": {
    "question": "Question:where is the clock?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the cabinet, next to the vase, next to the photo"
  },
  "8970": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the clock in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The clock is set in the bright livingroom."
  },
  "8971": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the clock?",
    "answer": "Answer:The livingroom is on the first floor and next to the kitchen."
  },
  "8972": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pen look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:long,black and oblique"
  },
  "8973": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pen?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the desk next to the glass wall,on the right of the green box and in a crystal pen box"
  },
  "8974": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pen in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The pen is in a small office."
  },
  "8975": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pen?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is at the corner of a junction of three roads and next to the corridor door."
  },
  "8976": {
    "question": "Question:what does the tap look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:silver, cylindrical, thin"
  },
  "8977": {
    "question": "Question:where is the tap?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the table, above the sink"
  },
  "8978": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the tap in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The tap is set in the kitchen."
  },
  "8979": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the tap?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to the livingroom and next to the dining room."
  },
  "8980": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Medium size, rectangular, film theme"
  },
  "8981": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:Next to the living room door and a socket"
  },
  "8982": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:picture is hanging on the living room wall"
  },
  "8983": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:picture  near the corridor connecting the gym"
  },
  "8984": {
    "question": "Question:what does the drawer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, wood, white"
  },
  "8985": {
    "question": "Question:where is the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:under a hand sink, under a bowl"
  },
  "8986": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the drawer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is in the center of a kitchen with wood floor."
  },
  "8987": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to a big dining room and there is a road outside."
  },
  "8988": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A white lamp with a whit glass base and a lampshade."
  },
  "8989": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to a bed and on a bedside table."
  },
  "8990": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a bedroom which has a double door."
  },
  "8991": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a bathroom and a living room."
  },
  "8992": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White ,soft,big"
  },
  "8993": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is set near a brown table and a shelf ,against a wall ."
  },
  "8994": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is set in the hall."
  },
  "8995": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is placed near a bedroom and a tearoom."
  },
  "8996": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, cylindrical, transparent"
  },
  "8997": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the table, next to the book"
  },
  "8998": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is set in the spacious livingroom."
  },
  "8999": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The livingroom is on the first floor and next to the kitchen."
  },
  "9000": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bathtub look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle , brown and white , hard"
  },
  "9001": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bathtub?",
    "answer": "Answer:surrounded by a bathroom , a bed and a cabinet"
  },
  "9002": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bathtub in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathtub is located at a corner of the bedroom."
  },
  "9003": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bathtub?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is surrounded by a balcony , a living room and a bathroom."
  },
  "9004": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:outdoor, blue and circular"
  },
  "9005": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pool?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is surrounded by cacti and facing the mountain."
  },
  "9006": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in front of the house."
  },
  "9007": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pool?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is outside the house and in front of the gate."
  },
  "9008": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:leather, brown, small"
  },
  "9009": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:facing the screen, on the first row of stairs, under the projector"
  },
  "9010": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is located in the small home theatre."
  },
  "9011": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The home theatre is on the first floor and next to the kitchen."
  },
  "9012": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown, white, fray, black and so on,  Silk and cotton"
  },
  "9013": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:between two table lamp, facing a big painting."
  },
  "9014": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in a small bright bedroom."
  },
  "9015": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:It has the main bedroom on one side and the laundry on the other."
  },
  "9016": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a white ,brand new rectangler table.\n"
  },
  "9017": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is above a stool, in the middle of two chairs."
  },
  "9018": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is by the window of the study.\n"
  },
  "9019": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a very classic study."
  },
  "9020": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stairs look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Narrow wooden stairs with wooden handrails."
  },
  "9021": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stairs?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is above a wooden container and below white candlestick-shaped lights."
  },
  "9022": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stairs in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It connects the ground floor and the second floor."
  },
  "9023": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stairs?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near the living room."
  },
  "9024": {
    "question": "Question:what does the door locker look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, golden, metallic"
  },
  "9025": {
    "question": "Question:where is the door locker?",
    "answer": "Answer:on a door, next to a wall"
  },
  "9026": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the door locker in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The door locker is located in a man washroom."
  },
  "9027": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the door locker?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a laundry basket and a wardrobe in a man washroom."
  },
  "9028": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Wooden, brown and layered."
  },
  "9029": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is under a mirror and near a small platform which has a lamp on it."
  },
  "9030": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is in a bedroom."
  },
  "9031": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom leads outdoors via a door and connects with a washroom."
  },
  "9032": {
    "question": "Question:what does the telephone look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:plastic;old-fashioned;grey;"
  },
  "9033": {
    "question": "Question:where is the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the wall behind the open dooor; faced with a white machine in the middle of two wall lamps;"
  },
  "9034": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the telephone in?",
    "answer": "Answer:at the entrance of the room."
  },
  "9035": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a wide mirror with black frames;"
  },
  "9036": {
    "question": "Question:what does the umbrella look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black,erect,columnar"
  },
  "9037": {
    "question": "Question:where is the umbrella?",
    "answer": "Answer:The umbrella is leaning against the glass wall,on the right side of a pillar,behind a chair."
  },
  "9038": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the umbrella in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The umberlla is in an office."
  },
  "9039": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the umbrella?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is at the corner of the three fork road,connecting to two corridors and next to an empty office and opposite to the room 356."
  },
  "9040": {
    "question": "Question:what does the dustbin look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black,short,plastic"
  },
  "9041": {
    "question": "Question:where is the dustbin?",
    "answer": "Answer:The dustbin is on the floor,in front of the cabinet and next to the socket."
  },
  "9042": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the dustbin in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The dustbin is in a median size meeting room with the identifier of 348."
  },
  "9043": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the dustbin?",
    "answer": "Answer:The meeting room is at the corner of the three fork road,opposite to an empty big room and has a road connecting to the rest area. "
  },
  "9044": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is white, large and ceramic."
  },
  "9045": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is in the middle of the oven and sink."
  },
  "9046": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is in the kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "9047": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is in the middle of the oven and sink."
  },
  "9048": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:square, big, cream color"
  },
  "9049": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:facing the door, next to nightstand"
  },
  "9050": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is located in the bright and small bedroom."
  },
  "9051": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is in the end of the corridor and on the right of the end."
  },
  "9052": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, cylindric, small"
  },
  "9053": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:some potted plant inside the vase, on a small black table, in the middle of two chairs"
  },
  "9054": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is set in the sunny balcony."
  },
  "9055": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The balcony is outside the bedroom and next to the washroom. There is some glass wall around the balcony."
  },
  "9056": {
    "question": "Question:what does the potted plant look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:green, woody, full of vigour "
  },
  "9057": {
    "question": "Question:where is the potted plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:in the corner, near a massage bed"
  },
  "9058": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the potted plant in?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are decorations on the pottted plant's right in the massage bedroom."
  },
  "9059": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the potted plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom connects with a gymnasium and is in fornt of another bedroom."
  },
  "9060": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is oval, ceramic and white."
  },
  "9061": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is to the right of the towel and under the mirror."
  },
  "9062": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is in the bedroom bathroom."
  },
  "9063": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is to the right of the towel and under the mirror."
  },
  "9064": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pillow look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A dark red square pillow."
  },
  "9065": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on the sofa which faces the projector and near a light yellow pillow."
  },
  "9066": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pillow in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the living room."
  },
  "9067": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a black bench."
  },
  "9068": {
    "question": "Question:what does the painting look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle, white and khaki"
  },
  "9069": {
    "question": "Question:where is the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:A wardrobe is on its right side, and it face the window."
  },
  "9070": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the painting in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's put in the work room."
  },
  "9071": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:Work room face the dinning room."
  },
  "9072": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bike look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Black,metal,big."
  },
  "9073": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bike?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bike is placed against a wall and next to a yellow chair."
  },
  "9074": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bike in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bike is placed in a reading room."
  },
  "9075": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bike?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bike is set near a tearoom."
  },
  "9076": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Square, white and double"
  },
  "9077": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is on a carpet and between two table lamps."
  },
  "9078": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is by the window, against a wall."
  },
  "9079": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:This bedroom is located at the end of the right turn on the second floor, next to another bedroom and a storage room."
  },
  "9080": {
    "question": "Question:what does the towel look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, big, cloth"
  },
  "9081": {
    "question": "Question:where is the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the handle, above the toilet"
  },
  "9082": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the towel in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is set in the washroom. "
  },
  "9083": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washroom is inside the office, which is on the first floor and next to the stairs."
  },
  "9084": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bench look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bench is rectangular, wooden and black."
  },
  "9085": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bench?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bench is in the middle of the two pillars."
  },
  "9086": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bench in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bench is beside the outdoor swimming pool."
  },
  "9087": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bench?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bench is in the middle of the two pillars."
  },
  "9088": {
    "question": "Question:what does the fan look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:woody, wide, brown "
  },
  "9089": {
    "question": "Question:where is the fan?",
    "answer": "Answer:above a table, in front of a shelf"
  },
  "9090": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the fan in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The fan is hanging in a study."
  },
  "9091": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the fan?",
    "answer": "Answer:The study is facing the outside and connects with a bedroom."
  },
  "9092": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:stands at the corner, median size,its color is black "
  },
  "9093": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are two small handicrafts put on the top of the cabinet, and it's close to the glass door"
  },
  "9094": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:A blacj cabinet is placed at the corner of the dining room ,which is under a picture of tiger."
  },
  "9095": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a eating table and eight chairs put in the dining room ,and a black cabinet is close to the table."
  },
  "9096": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Rectangle, metal frame, complex pattern"
  },
  "9097": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a table and two vases below"
  },
  "9098": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Mirror on the wall of the corridor"
  },
  "9099": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:Mirror between balcony and living room, opposite stairs"
  },
  "9100": {
    "question": "Question:what does the flower look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, gray, wood"
  },
  "9101": {
    "question": "Question:where is the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:below a light, next to a picture"
  },
  "9102": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the flower in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is in the corner of a small bathroom."
  },
  "9103": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bashroom is next to a gym and is connected with a bedroom."
  },
  "9104": {
    "question": "Question:what does the book look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:tidy, paper books, blue"
  },
  "9105": {
    "question": "Question:where is the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:under a  clock, in front of a table"
  },
  "9106": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the book in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The books are on the fourth layer of a shelf in a study."
  },
  "9107": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:The study has many shelves on the wall and has a big table in the center."
  },
  "9108": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown, middle, wooden"
  },
  "9109": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the table, next to the window"
  },
  "9110": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set in the bright kitchen."
  },
  "9111": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is on the first floor and next to the livingroom."
  },
  "9112": {
    "question": "Question:what does the fan look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Round, metal, silvery."
  },
  "9113": {
    "question": "Question:where is the fan?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a woody  statue near the fan and some bottles near it."
  },
  "9114": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the fan in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The  fan  is set on a  corridior of the  hall."
  },
  "9115": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the fan?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area has  a woody statue  and  a picture."
  },
  "9116": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stairs look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:one-stepped, marble and fan-shaped"
  },
  "9117": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stairs?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is the access connecting the pool and the house."
  },
  "9118": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stairs in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in front of the house."
  },
  "9119": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stairs?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is outside the house and close to the pool."
  },
  "9120": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Wooden and leather, red and beige and soild."
  },
  "9121": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is the third one in a row of chairs from right to left while facing to the chairs, behind a red leather sofa and opposite to a brown wooden desk."
  },
  "9122": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in a reception room."
  },
  "9123": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is near a porch."
  },
  "9124": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bowl look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Brown,wooden,big."
  },
  "9125": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bowl?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bowl is placed on a table with white top and under a lamp."
  },
  "9126": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bowl in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bowl is placed in a tearoom."
  },
  "9127": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bowl?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bowl is set near a reading room and the hall."
  },
  "9128": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a brand new blue wooden chair.\n"
  },
  "9129": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is beside another wooden chair, behind a stool."
  },
  "9130": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in a living room."
  },
  "9131": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's beside a kitchen."
  },
  "9132": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cloth, beige, big"
  },
  "9133": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the lamp, next to the phone"
  },
  "9134": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is in the center of a warm child-bedroom. "
  },
  "9135": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The child-bedroom is next to the corridor on the second floor with a fireplace and a bathroom."
  },
  "9136": {
    "question": "Question:what does the tv look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A black LCD TV."
  },
  "9137": {
    "question": "Question:where is the tv?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a window and over a chair."
  },
  "9138": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the tv in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is hung on the wall."
  },
  "9139": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the tv?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a toilet."
  },
  "9140": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a pink round brilliant ceiling light."
  },
  "9141": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is directly above the bed and directly below the roof."
  },
  "9142": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in the bedroom."
  },
  "9143": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is beside the corridor."
  },
  "9144": {
    "question": "Question:what does the dustbin look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black,small,cuboid,with a plastic bag in it"
  },
  "9145": {
    "question": "Question:where is the dustbin?",
    "answer": "Answer:The dustbin is under a white desk and in front of the root of the chair."
  },
  "9146": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the dustbin in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The computer is in an office numbering 356 that filled with stationery,book and poster."
  },
  "9147": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the dustbin?",
    "answer": "Answer:The dustbin is on the right of a white huge pillar and face the corridor at a slant."
  },
  "9148": {
    "question": "Question:what does the remoter look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A small black remoter with many buttons."
  },
  "9149": {
    "question": "Question:where is the remoter?",
    "answer": "Answer:It lies on a black board, and under the projector."
  },
  "9150": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the remoter in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the living room."
  },
  "9151": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the remoter?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a desk and several sofas."
  },
  "9152": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:hanged, rectangle and grey"
  },
  "9153": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is hanged above some towels and next to a piece of glass."
  },
  "9154": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a restroom on the second floor."
  },
  "9155": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The restroom is at the left rear corner of the stairs."
  },
  "9156": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is big, square and colorful."
  },
  "9157": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is hung on the wall facing the sofa."
  },
  "9158": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is hung on the wall facing the sofa in the living room."
  },
  "9159": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a big sofa, tables and chairs in the living room."
  },
  "9160": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a yellow, small ceiling light."
  },
  "9161": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is directly above a wooden chair and a table."
  },
  "9162": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is set in a corridor at the door of a house."
  },
  "9163": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is set beside the door of a kitchen."
  },
  "9164": {
    "question": "Question:what does the dining table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wood, white,with vases on it"
  },
  "9165": {
    "question": "Question:where is the dining table?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's on the right of the piano and lamp"
  },
  "9166": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the dining table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in dining room"
  },
  "9167": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the dining table?",
    "answer": "Answer:there is a kitch  behind it"
  },
  "9168": {
    "question": "Question:what does the flower look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wood, white, small"
  },
  "9169": {
    "question": "Question:where is the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:on a table, below a picture"
  },
  "9170": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the flower in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is placed in a bedroom on the first floor."
  },
  "9171": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is next to a bashroom and there is a bashroom upstairs."
  },
  "9172": {
    "question": "Question:what does the painting look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Papery, green and blue and rectangular."
  },
  "9173": {
    "question": "Question:where is the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is near a white and brassy lamp and a green bed."
  },
  "9174": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the painting in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is in a bedroom."
  },
  "9175": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is near a corridor and a toilet."
  },
  "9176": {
    "question": "Question:what does the tissue look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:papery, white and rounded."
  },
  "9177": {
    "question": "Question:where is the tissue?",
    "answer": "Answer:The tissue is near a toilet and under some switches."
  },
  "9178": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the tissue in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The tissue is in a bathroom."
  },
  "9179": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the tissue?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area connects with a bedroom and near a toilet."
  },
  "9180": {
    "question": "Question:what does the fan look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:New,metal and tall"
  },
  "9181": {
    "question": "Question:where is the fan?",
    "answer": "Answer:The fan is in front of a white pillar, next to the stairs covered by a red carpet. \n"
  },
  "9182": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the fan in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The fan is set in a corner of the hall."
  },
  "9183": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the fan?",
    "answer": "Answer:The fan is nearby to the altar and next to a corridor."
  },
  "9184": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:middle size, transparent,round and fragile"
  },
  "9185": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's above a wash table and near a closestool."
  },
  "9186": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a washroom on the first floor."
  },
  "9187": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:the washroom is near a corridor and a living room."
  },
  "9188": {
    "question": "Question:what does the toilet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white"
  },
  "9189": {
    "question": "Question:where is the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the cabinet and the mirror"
  },
  "9190": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the toilet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the bathroom."
  },
  "9191": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the corridor and the children's room."
  },
  "9192": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A large square white picture."
  },
  "9193": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on the left of another white picture and faces a switch."
  },
  "9194": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a bedroom."
  },
  "9195": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near the entrance of the bedroom."
  },
  "9196": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bench look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:square,unbacked and on the floor"
  },
  "9197": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bench?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's under some switches and two pictures."
  },
  "9198": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bench in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's put on the corner of the room"
  },
  "9199": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bench?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a corridor outside the room"
  },
  "9200": {
    "question": "Question:what does the Bathtub look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:ceramic,cuboid,smooth,white"
  },
  "9201": {
    "question": "Question:where is the Bathtub?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a round short stool and a glass table with a telephone."
  },
  "9202": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the Bathtub in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a bathroom on the second floor."
  },
  "9203": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the Bathtub?",
    "answer": "Answer:the bathroom is in a big bedroom which is in the end of a corridor and near a open-balcony."
  },
  "9204": {
    "question": "Question:what does the telephone look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, white and stick-shaped"
  },
  "9205": {
    "question": "Question:where is the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed between the computer and a green plant."
  },
  "9206": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the telephone in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in living roon on the first floor."
  },
  "9207": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is the room facing the door."
  },
  "9208": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, pink, light"
  },
  "9209": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the TV, over against the bed"
  },
  "9210": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is on the table settled in a warm child-bedroom. "
  },
  "9211": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The child-bedroom is next to the corridor on the second floor with a fireplace and a bathroom."
  },
  "9212": {
    "question": "Question:what does the painting look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:paper,square and hanged on the wall"
  },
  "9213": {
    "question": "Question:where is the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:near another painting and some switches"
  },
  "9214": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the painting in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's on the corner of the room"
  },
  "9215": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a corridor outside the room"
  },
  "9216": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Double bed with black quilt with four pillows on it."
  },
  "9217": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed was lined with white sheets and pillows and black quilts"
  },
  "9218": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is in the bedroom."
  },
  "9219": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:Bed at the end of the corridor on the second floor on the first floor living room"
  },
  "9220": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Double bed with black quilt with four pillows on it."
  },
  "9221": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed was lined with white sheets and pillows and black quilts"
  },
  "9222": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is in the bedroom."
  },
  "9223": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:Bed at the end of the corridor on the second floor on the first floor living room"
  },
  "9224": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden, circle, brown"
  },
  "9225": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's put between two sofas, a book, a glass bottle and a glass lamp is put on it."
  },
  "9226": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's put in the reception area where next to the stairs."
  },
  "9227": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's next to the garden. "
  },
  "9228": {
    "question": "Question:what does the door look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:woody , brown , tall"
  },
  "9229": {
    "question": "Question:where is the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the wall , next to the bathtub"
  },
  "9230": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the door in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The door is located at a corner of the bedroom."
  },
  "9231": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is surrounded by a balcony , a living room and a bathroom."
  },
  "9232": {
    "question": "Question:what does the desk look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Brown, wooden and medium size."
  },
  "9233": {
    "question": "Question:where is the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:The desk is settled between two red and brown chairs, oppposite to a tall wooden carbinet and behind a round wooden table."
  },
  "9234": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the desk in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The desk is in a corridor."
  },
  "9235": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:The desk is near a living room."
  },
  "9236": {
    "question": "Question:what does the microwave look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:silvery, metal, rectangular"
  },
  "9237": {
    "question": "Question:where is the microwave?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a cupboard, under a screen"
  },
  "9238": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the microwave in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The microwave is settled in the corner of a kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "9239": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the microwave?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to a small storeroom and there is a cloakroom upstairs"
  },
  "9240": {
    "question": "Question:what does the tv look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:square, black, big"
  },
  "9241": {
    "question": "Question:where is the tv?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the window, over against the bed"
  },
  "9242": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the tv in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The TV is on the table settled in a warm child-bedroom. "
  },
  "9243": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the tv?",
    "answer": "Answer:The child-bedroom is next to the corridor on the second floor with a fireplace and a bathroom."
  },
  "9244": {
    "question": "Question:what does the television look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Medium size, black and metal."
  },
  "9245": {
    "question": "Question:where is the television?",
    "answer": "Answer:The television is on the right side of a blue and white bed and above a brown guitar."
  },
  "9246": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the television in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The television is in a bedroom."
  },
  "9247": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the television?",
    "answer": "Answer:The television is near a corridor and a storage room."
  },
  "9248": {
    "question": "Question:what does the curtain look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, long, filmy"
  },
  "9249": {
    "question": "Question:where is the curtain?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the window, next to a wall painting and a table with a chair"
  },
  "9250": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the curtain in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The curtain is in the study."
  },
  "9251": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the curtain?",
    "answer": "Answer:The study is next to the dining roon and the bathroom on the second floor."
  },
  "9252": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:yellow, wood, hard"
  },
  "9253": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:between the kitchen and the stairs, below five light bulbs"
  },
  "9254": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is set at the center of the living room, on the second floor."
  },
  "9255": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is next to the kitchen and the bedrooms."
  },
  "9256": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle, long, yellow"
  },
  "9257": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:below five light bulbs, between the kitchen and the stairs"
  },
  "9258": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is set at the center of the living room, on the second floor."
  },
  "9259": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is next to the kitchen and the bedrooms."
  },
  "9260": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:long, rectangle, yellow"
  },
  "9261": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:between the kitchen and the stairs, below five light bulbs"
  },
  "9262": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is set at the center of the living room, on the second floor."
  },
  "9263": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is surrounded by a kitchen and two bedrooms."
  },
  "9264": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:These are two new, brown wooden chairs.\n"
  },
  "9265": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is beside a cabinet and a sofa chair.\n"
  },
  "9266": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in a living room."
  },
  "9267": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's beside a kitchen."
  },
  "9268": {
    "question": "Question:what does the deck chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black; long; has two towels."
  },
  "9269": {
    "question": "Question:where is the deck chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:below a decorative piture;faces a rounded table;"
  },
  "9270": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the deck chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:counting from left to right, the third one;"
  },
  "9271": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the deck chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:a big hall with a glass door."
  },
  "9272": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Wooden, wood color, round"
  },
  "9273": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:table there is a vase on it, and there are 7 chairs around it"
  },
  "9274": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:table In the living room"
  },
  "9275": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:table next to the balcony"
  },
  "9276": {
    "question": "Question:what does the broom look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:light, useful, yellow"
  },
  "9277": {
    "question": "Question:where is the broom?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a furnace, against a wall"
  },
  "9278": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the broom in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The broom is in the corner in a study."
  },
  "9279": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the broom?",
    "answer": "Answer:This study connects with the outside via a door and has a long table."
  },
  "9280": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White, fabric, double"
  },
  "9281": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:sofa there are six pillows on it and a small table in front"
  },
  "9282": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:sofa In the living room"
  },
  "9283": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:sofa Next to the balcony"
  },
  "9284": {
    "question": "Question:what does the drawer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is small, wooden and square."
  },
  "9285": {
    "question": "Question:where is the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a toaster and microwave above the drawer."
  },
  "9286": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the drawer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is placed below the toaster and microwave next to the toilet."
  },
  "9287": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a toilet and sink in the toilet."
  },
  "9288": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cupboard look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown,woolen and hard"
  },
  "9289": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cupboard?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a oven and above a glass bottle."
  },
  "9290": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cupboard in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in the corner of a kitchen on the second floor."
  },
  "9291": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cupboard?",
    "answer": "Answer:the kitchen is next to a open-balcony and a living room."
  },
  "9292": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:gray, rectangular, big"
  },
  "9293": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:facing a table, next to a lamp"
  },
  "9294": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is settled in the corner of a bedroom on the first floor."
  },
  "9295": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is facing a corridor and is between two bashrooms."
  },
  "9296": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A yellow and black,wooden square picture."
  },
  "9297": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is beside a lamp and a small black sofa."
  },
  "9298": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on the wall near the corridor."
  },
  "9299": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near the stair to the second floor and close to a bedroom and laundry room."
  },
  "9300": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:ceramic,white and green,fragile"
  },
  "9301": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a curtain and it's behind a sofa"
  },
  "9302": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in the living room on the first floor"
  },
  "9303": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:the living room is near the dining room and the kitchen"
  },
  "9304": {
    "question": "Question:what does the box look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:High up, black, metal"
  },
  "9305": {
    "question": "Question:where is the box?",
    "answer": "Answer:The box is placed on a tall black box and next to a yellow desk."
  },
  "9306": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the box in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The box is set in the front desk."
  },
  "9307": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the box?",
    "answer": "Answer:The box is placed next to the gate and near the stairs."
  },
  "9308": {
    "question": "Question:what does the corridor lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:metal,tall,round"
  },
  "9309": {
    "question": "Question:where is the corridor lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a door and in front of a desk."
  },
  "9310": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the corridor lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a rest room on the second floor."
  },
  "9311": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the corridor lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:the rest room is in a big bedroom which is in the end of a corridor and next to a open-balcony."
  },
  "9312": {
    "question": "Question:what does the towel look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:dry , white , smooth"
  },
  "9313": {
    "question": "Question:where is the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:on a platform , below the water tap"
  },
  "9314": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the towel in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is located at a corner of the shower room."
  },
  "9315": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The shower room is inside of the bathroom."
  },
  "9316": {
    "question": "Question:what does the power switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is square, plastic and white."
  },
  "9317": {
    "question": "Question:where is the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is on the wall and under the light."
  },
  "9318": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the power switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is next to the stairs on the first floor."
  },
  "9319": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is on the wall and under the light."
  },
  "9320": {
    "question": "Question:what does the painting look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Wooden, rectangular and soild."
  },
  "9321": {
    "question": "Question:where is the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is set near a black and round clock and near a brown and round table."
  },
  "9322": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the painting in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is in a living room."
  },
  "9323": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is near a corridor and a bedroom."
  },
  "9324": {
    "question": "Question:what does the drawer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:woolen,white"
  },
  "9325": {
    "question": "Question:where is the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's on the left of the door inside and in front of a table."
  },
  "9326": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the drawer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a dressing room on the second floor."
  },
  "9327": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:the dressing room is near a washroom and a bathroom which is in a bedroom near a open-balcony."
  },
  "9328": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Silk and cotton"
  },
  "9329": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's between two lamp, It's in the center of the main room"
  },
  "9330": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's put in a big and  bright main bedroom."
  },
  "9331": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The master bedroom faces the balcony. Right below the room is the swimming pool."
  },
  "9332": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle, small, woody"
  },
  "9333": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:near a stove with a television, between a small sofa and the window"
  },
  "9334": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is set at a corner of the living room, on the second floor."
  },
  "9335": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is very spacious."
  },
  "9336": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a white, clean and new, porcelain cabinet.\n"
  },
  "9337": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It was directly under a few bowls and two pots.\n"
  },
  "9338": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in the kitchen.\n"
  },
  "9339": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to the study."
  },
  "9340": {
    "question": "Question:what does the plant look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:botanical, cylindrical, green"
  },
  "9341": {
    "question": "Question:where is the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the middle of the stone table, in front of the glass window"
  },
  "9342": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the plant in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The plant is set in the bright and spacious kitchen."
  },
  "9343": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is on the third floor, facing the stairs, next to the livingroom and dining room."
  },
  "9344": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:metal and cloth,unmbrella,brown"
  },
  "9345": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's on the drawer and next to the bed"
  },
  "9346": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's on the left side of the bed and on the right side of the door."
  },
  "9347": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:there is a bedroom across the corridor"
  },
  "9348": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cup look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:glass,transparent,small"
  },
  "9349": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cup?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's on a dish which is on a white table.\n"
  },
  "9350": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cup in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a kitchen on the second floor."
  },
  "9351": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cup?",
    "answer": "Answer:the kitchen is near a living room and a open-balcony."
  },
  "9352": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is glass, large and white."
  },
  "9353": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is in the upper right corner of the oven and to the left of the window."
  },
  "9354": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is in the kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "9355": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is in the upper right corner of the oven and to the left of the window."
  },
  "9356": {
    "question": "Question:what does the fllower look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is polygonal, wooden and white."
  },
  "9357": {
    "question": "Question:where is the fllower?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is in a vase and on the table."
  },
  "9358": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the fllower in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is in the living room."
  },
  "9359": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the fllower?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is in a vase and on the table."
  },
  "9360": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cupboard look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, wooden, brown"
  },
  "9361": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cupboard?",
    "answer": "Answer:above the coffee maker, facing the lamp"
  },
  "9362": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cupboard in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cupboard is set in the bright kitchen."
  },
  "9363": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cupboard?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is on the first floor and next to the dining room."
  },
  "9364": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:ceramic, rounded and with branches."
  },
  "9365": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is on a black box and near a beautiful sofa."
  },
  "9366": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is in a small attic, which is on the second floor."
  },
  "9367": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The attic is above the living room, and connects with a staircase."
  },
  "9368": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:oval; with two taps; deep"
  },
  "9369": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:opposite the flank of a table; against a wall with blue hamps."
  },
  "9370": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:at the left side of this room"
  },
  "9371": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:a washroom with a wooden door."
  },
  "9372": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:soft, large and white."
  },
  "9373": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is near a black platform and is in front of a dresser."
  },
  "9374": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is in a bedroom."
  },
  "9375": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom leads outdoors via a door and connects with a washroom."
  },
  "9376": {
    "question": "Question:what does the typewriter look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, black, metallic"
  },
  "9377": {
    "question": "Question:where is the typewriter?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the glass table, facing the curtain"
  },
  "9378": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the typewriter in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The typewriter is set in the middle of the office."
  },
  "9379": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the typewriter?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is on the first floor and next to the livingroom."
  },
  "9380": {
    "question": "Question:what does the oven look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black and silver, small"
  },
  "9381": {
    "question": "Question:where is the oven?",
    "answer": "Answer:The is a cupboard on its left. In front of it was a glass bottle with green apples in it"
  },
  "9382": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the oven in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's installed in a  open kitchen."
  },
  "9383": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the oven?",
    "answer": "Answer:Here you can see the swimming pool, reception area and a wicket."
  },
  "9384": {
    "question": "Question:what does the door look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, wooden, white"
  },
  "9385": {
    "question": "Question:where is the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the television, facing the sofa"
  },
  "9386": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the door in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The door is set in the spacious bedroom."
  },
  "9387": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is on the first floor and next to the bedroom."
  },
  "9388": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, cloth, gray"
  },
  "9389": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:facing a black table, next to a lamp"
  },
  "9390": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is placed in the corner of a wide and bright study."
  },
  "9391": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The study is facing a long corridor and next to a bashroom on the first floor."
  },
  "9392": {
    "question": "Question:what does the handbag look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:piled together,leathery and on the top of the box"
  },
  "9393": {
    "question": "Question:where is the handbag?",
    "answer": "Answer:the handbag are on the top of the box and under the bench"
  },
  "9394": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the handbag in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The handbags are on the side of the room"
  },
  "9395": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the handbag?",
    "answer": "Answer:there is a corridors outside the room"
  },
  "9396": {
    "question": "Question:what does the container look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, black, hard"
  },
  "9397": {
    "question": "Question:where is the container?",
    "answer": "Answer:between a box and a penholder, on the table"
  },
  "9398": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the container in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The small container with many cards is put in the study."
  },
  "9399": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the container?",
    "answer": "Answer:The study has two laptops and two leather chairs."
  },
  "9400": {
    "question": "Question:what does the book look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Rectangular, new, green."
  },
  "9401": {
    "question": "Question:where is the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:The book is set behind a chair and next to a fan."
  },
  "9402": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the book in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The book is set at the corner near a stone pillar."
  },
  "9403": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area has ranges of wooden benches."
  },
  "9404": {
    "question": "Question:what does the towel look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:soft, rectangular"
  },
  "9405": {
    "question": "Question:where is the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:hung on the wall and next to the picture "
  },
  "9406": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the towel in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the bathroom"
  },
  "9407": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is in the bedroom and on the second floor "
  },
  "9408": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cylindrical, brown, wooden"
  },
  "9409": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:in the middle of two sofas, there are two vases and two photos on it"
  },
  "9410": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is set in the spacious livingroom."
  },
  "9411": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The livingroom is on the first floor and next to the dining room."
  },
  "9412": {
    "question": "Question:what does the candle look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big,trident,black"
  },
  "9413": {
    "question": "Question:where is the candle?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's on the table and on the right of switch"
  },
  "9414": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the candle in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in study"
  },
  "9415": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the candle?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's dinning room outside the study"
  },
  "9416": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, blue and white, cloth"
  },
  "9417": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the carpet, facing the picture, next to the door"
  },
  "9418": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is located in the bright bedroom."
  },
  "9419": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is on the second floor and on the left of the stairs when go upstairs."
  },
  "9420": {
    "question": "Question:what does the massage bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, rectangular, soft"
  },
  "9421": {
    "question": "Question:where is the massage bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:in the center, near a potted plant"
  },
  "9422": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the massage bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is put in a massage bedroom."
  },
  "9423": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the massage bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area has decorations on the wall and a massage bed."
  },
  "9424": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big,grey,cloth-made"
  },
  "9425": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's on the left side of the piano and the lamp"
  },
  "9426": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in dinning room"
  },
  "9427": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:there is study next to the dinning room"
  },
  "9428": {
    "question": "Question:what does the book look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:opened, paper, thick"
  },
  "9429": {
    "question": "Question:where is the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:on a small table, between a small sofa and the window"
  },
  "9430": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the book in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The book is set at a corner of the living room."
  },
  "9431": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is surrounded by a kitchen and two bedrooms."
  },
  "9432": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white and black, square, wooden and black"
  },
  "9433": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the wall, among five picture and first from left"
  },
  "9434": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is set on the left side of the corridor."
  },
  "9435": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The corridor is on the second floor, has two stairs and some rooms."
  },
  "9436": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:stainless steel,bright"
  },
  "9437": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:it is between two cabinets and under a big window"
  },
  "9438": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's on a table in the kitchen"
  },
  "9439": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:the kitchen is near the dining room and living room"
  },
  "9440": {
    "question": "Question:what does the window look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, rectangle"
  },
  "9441": {
    "question": "Question:where is the window?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's covered with gauze curtains, a table is under it."
  },
  "9442": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the window in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is face the dinning table. It's put in the work room."
  },
  "9443": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the window?",
    "answer": "Answer:Work room face the dinning room."
  },
  "9444": {
    "question": "Question:what does the glass door look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big one\uff0csquare\uff0cthere is black frame surround glass door"
  },
  "9445": {
    "question": "Question:where is the glass door?",
    "answer": "Answer:the door is to small balcony\uff0cthere are grey curtains hanging close to the glass door close "
  },
  "9446": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the glass door in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The glass door is to a small balcony which is placed outside living room\uff0cthe one which is placed close to the leisure area with two same glass made tea table in it."
  },
  "9447": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the glass door?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are several big sofas placed in the big living room, and a median size mirror installed on the side wall."
  },
  "9448": {
    "question": "Question:what does the towel look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, soft, cotton"
  },
  "9449": {
    "question": "Question:where is the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's put on a sink. The tap is on its left."
  },
  "9450": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the towel in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is put in the toilet in the workshop."
  },
  "9451": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:Work room face the dinning room."
  },
  "9452": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Medium size, wooden and brown."
  },
  "9453": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is settled under a silver ship, opposite to a beige floriated sofa and near six pictures."
  },
  "9454": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is at the corner of a living room."
  },
  "9455": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is near a study and a corridor on the second floor."
  },
  "9456": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A white columnal lamp with a lampshade."
  },
  "9457": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on a black desk and beside a small picture leaning on it."
  },
  "9458": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a bed."
  },
  "9459": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near an empty room and a toilet."
  },
  "9460": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, black, white and gray, "
  },
  "9461": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is facing the bed, There is a picture above it."
  },
  "9462": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in a small bright bedroom."
  },
  "9463": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It has the main bedroom on one side and the laundry on the other."
  },
  "9464": {
    "question": "Question:what does the television look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A black television serving as a monitor."
  },
  "9465": {
    "question": "Question:where is the television?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on a black board and near wires."
  },
  "9466": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the television in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in an empty room."
  },
  "9467": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the television?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a bedroom which is connected with a bathroom."
  },
  "9468": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is made of iron, silver and rectangular."
  },
  "9469": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is on the table and beside the vase."
  },
  "9470": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is in the kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "9471": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is on the table and beside the vase."
  },
  "9472": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A large gray cabinet with many drawers and a granite board. "
  },
  "9473": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is surrounded by shelves."
  },
  "9474": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a room on the second floor."
  },
  "9475": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near the bathroom and a hall."
  },
  "9476": {
    "question": "Question:what does the painting look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown and red,rectangle,paper"
  },
  "9477": {
    "question": "Question:where is the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:above the clock,on the wall opposite to the door and on the right of the printer"
  },
  "9478": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the painting in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is in a big office."
  },
  "9479": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is in front of a corridor door,along the road connecting the tea room and the restaurant."
  },
  "9480": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soild, round and wooden."
  },
  "9481": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is next to a tiger skin rug, near a mirror with brown border and in front of the window."
  },
  "9482": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is in a beadroom with a blue carpet."
  },
  "9483": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is on the opposite side of a narrow empty room."
  },
  "9484": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soild, wooden and round."
  },
  "9485": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is surrounded by four chairs and near a black television."
  },
  "9486": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is in a dining room."
  },
  "9487": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The dining room is near a kitchen and a living room."
  },
  "9488": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pillow look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle, cotton and patterned"
  },
  "9489": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on the bed and close to the head of the bed."
  },
  "9490": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pillow in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a bedroom on the second floor."
  },
  "9491": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is at the left rear corner of the stairs."
  },
  "9492": {
    "question": "Question:what does the toilet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:porcelain, white"
  },
  "9493": {
    "question": "Question:where is the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:there is a cabinet on it's left and a bathtub on it's right"
  },
  "9494": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the toilet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is installed on a small washing room."
  },
  "9495": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washing room is built in a small bright bedroom which has the main bedroom on one side and the laundry on the other."
  },
  "9496": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pillows look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:They are small soft pillows,two of which is light blue with different patterns and another one is purple with no patterns."
  },
  "9497": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pillows?",
    "answer": "Answer:They are on the head of a bed and below a fan."
  },
  "9498": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pillows in?",
    "answer": "Answer:They are placed in the bedroom."
  },
  "9499": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pillows?",
    "answer": "Answer:They are near a toilet."
  },
  "9500": {
    "question": "Question:what does the book look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:numerous, papery and oblong."
  },
  "9501": {
    "question": "Question:where is the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:These books are in a big cabinet and is on the left of a big picture and in the middle of the books."
  },
  "9502": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the book in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The books are in a big living room."
  },
  "9503": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is next to a dining room and leads to outdoors via a door."
  },
  "9504": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cuboid, yellow and metal frame."
  },
  "9505": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is above a bench and a light shines it."
  },
  "9506": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is on a wall under the stairs."
  },
  "9507": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to a kitchen and across from a fireplace."
  },
  "9508": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Rectangular, wooden and vitreous and black."
  },
  "9509": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is near two white sofas and near a black television."
  },
  "9510": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is in a living room."
  },
  "9511": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is near a bedroom."
  },
  "9512": {
    "question": "Question:what does the guitar look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black, middle, wooden"
  },
  "9513": {
    "question": "Question:where is the guitar?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the nightstand, on the left of the bed"
  },
  "9514": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the guitar in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The guitar is set in the small bedroom. "
  },
  "9515": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the guitar?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is in the end of the corridor and on the right of the end."
  },
  "9516": {
    "question": "Question:what does the television look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Big, soild and black."
  },
  "9517": {
    "question": "Question:where is the television?",
    "answer": "Answer:The television is set near two small beige sofas and above a beige table."
  },
  "9518": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the television in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The television is in a rest room."
  },
  "9519": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the television?",
    "answer": "Answer:The television is near a corridor on the second floor."
  },
  "9520": {
    "question": "Question:what does the potted plant look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:erect, round and green"
  },
  "9521": {
    "question": "Question:where is the potted plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is the second closest plant next to the open door."
  },
  "9522": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the potted plant in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in front of the house."
  },
  "9523": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the potted plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is outside the house and in front of the gate."
  },
  "9524": {
    "question": "Question:what does the Tea table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:glass, rectangular, black"
  },
  "9525": {
    "question": "Question:where is the Tea table?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the carpet, in front of the sofa and a big mirror"
  },
  "9526": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the Tea table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The tea table is in the living room."
  },
  "9527": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the Tea table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The tea table is in front of door and next to the French window with a garden outsides."
  },
  "9528": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Truncated cone shaped, white and soild."
  },
  "9529": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is near a white closetool and near a tall brown cabinet."
  },
  "9530": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is in a toilet."
  },
  "9531": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is near a study and a dining room."
  },
  "9532": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cotton, brown and hexagon"
  },
  "9533": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed on a carpet and next to the window."
  },
  "9534": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a chatting room on the first floor."
  },
  "9535": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chatting room is next to the hall."
  },
  "9536": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bar look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:red and argent,large,full of food"
  },
  "9537": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bar?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the left of a wooden shell and near many sets of desks and chairs"
  },
  "9538": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bar in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bar is in a vast lobby."
  },
  "9539": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bar?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bar is in front of the vast resting area and towards the service desk and near some meeting offices."
  },
  "9540": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pillow look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:square, cloth, cream color"
  },
  "9541": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the sofa, among three pillows and in the middle of them"
  },
  "9542": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pillow in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The pillow is set in the livingroom."
  },
  "9543": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:The livingroom is on the first floor and next to the kitchen."
  },
  "9544": {
    "question": "Question:what does the yoga mat look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, small, black"
  },
  "9545": {
    "question": "Question:where is the yoga mat?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a treadmill, next to a plant"
  },
  "9546": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the yoga mat in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The yogamat is in a small gym with wood floor."
  },
  "9547": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the yoga mat?",
    "answer": "Answer:The gym is facing a long corridor and is next to a bashroom."
  },
  "9548": {
    "question": "Question:what does the power switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is small, square and white."
  },
  "9549": {
    "question": "Question:where is the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are some posters on the opposite of the power switch."
  },
  "9550": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the power switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is placed on the wall."
  },
  "9551": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are many posters in the corridor."
  },
  "9552": {
    "question": "Question:what does the painting look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:square, green, big"
  },
  "9553": {
    "question": "Question:where is the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the wall, facing the sofa"
  },
  "9554": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the painting in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is located on the corridor."
  },
  "9555": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:The corridor is next to the livingroom and on the first floor."
  },
  "9556": {
    "question": "Question:what does the laptop look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:metallic, black, rectangular"
  },
  "9557": {
    "question": "Question:where is the laptop?",
    "answer": "Answer:on a woody table, next to a desk lamp, in front of a white chair"
  },
  "9558": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the laptop in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The laptop is set in the bedroom on the third floor."
  },
  "9559": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the laptop?",
    "answer": "Answer:The laptop is face a bed and behind a wall painting."
  },
  "9560": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, wooden, white"
  },
  "9561": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the carpet, in front of the big sofa, next to a chair"
  },
  "9562": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is located in a bright livingroom."
  },
  "9563": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The livingroom is on the third floor, next to the kitchen and stairs, there is a balcony outside the livingroom."
  },
  "9564": {
    "question": "Question:what does the desk look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A black wooden dsek with some trophies and books."
  },
  "9565": {
    "question": "Question:where is the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a green plant and a set of sofa."
  },
  "9566": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the desk in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a bedroom which has a balcony."
  },
  "9567": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a window."
  },
  "9568": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stairs look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wood, yellow, long"
  },
  "9569": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stairs?",
    "answer": "Answer:surrounded by a small table and a long table, connecting two floors"
  },
  "9570": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stairs in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stairs is set at a corner of the living room, on the second floor."
  },
  "9571": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stairs?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is surrounded by a kitchen and two bedrooms."
  },
  "9572": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stairs look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wood, yellow, long"
  },
  "9573": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stairs?",
    "answer": "Answer:surrounded by a small table and a long table, connecting two floors"
  },
  "9574": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stairs in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stairs is set at a corner of the living room, on the second floor."
  },
  "9575": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stairs?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is surrounded by a kitchen and two bedrooms."
  },
  "9576": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is soft, white and rectangular"
  },
  "9577": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is beside the window and lamp."
  },
  "9578": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is in the bedroom."
  },
  "9579": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is beside the window and lamp."
  },
  "9580": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:metallic, black and brown and with four legs."
  },
  "9581": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is near a cabinet and there is the same stool behind of it."
  },
  "9582": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is in a kitchen."
  },
  "9583": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to a dining room and leads to outdoors via a door."
  },
  "9584": {
    "question": "Question:what does the television look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular,glass,reflective"
  },
  "9585": {
    "question": "Question:where is the television?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's above a cabinet and next to a painting."
  },
  "9586": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the television in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a living room on the second floor."
  },
  "9587": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the television?",
    "answer": "Answer:the living room is near a dining room and a stair."
  },
  "9588": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Black,metal,low"
  },
  "9589": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is placed  near a black table and a brown box."
  },
  "9590": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is set in a tearoom."
  },
  "9591": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is placed  near a reading room and next to the hall."
  },
  "9592": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp post look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:blue, cylindrical and glass"
  },
  "9593": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp post?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is close to the door and next to a table with six chairs surrounded."
  },
  "9594": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp post in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a chatting room on the first floor."
  },
  "9595": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp post?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chatting room is next to the hall."
  },
  "9596": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is large, metallic and brown."
  },
  "9597": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp hangs on the ceiling and above the table."
  },
  "9598": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is in the parlor on the first floor."
  },
  "9599": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp hangs on the ceiling and above the table."
  },
  "9600": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:green,slight,leather and metal"
  },
  "9601": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:behind the first row of the desk,on the most right side of the first row and nearst to the door"
  },
  "9602": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in a large discussing room."
  },
  "9603": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The room faces the lobby at a slant and opposite to a no entry room."
  },
  "9604": {
    "question": "Question:what does the oven look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:tectangular, silver, big"
  },
  "9605": {
    "question": "Question:where is the oven?",
    "answer": "Answer:between two cabinets, next to the coffee maker"
  },
  "9606": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the oven in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The oven is set in the bright kitchen."
  },
  "9607": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the oven?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to the livingroom and on the first floor."
  },
  "9608": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Metal, soild and gray."
  },
  "9609": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is set near a microwave and next to a big table with a sink."
  },
  "9610": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is in a kitchen."
  },
  "9611": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is near a dining room."
  },
  "9612": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:stand  front facing the bookcase, irregular shape, its color is brown "
  },
  "9613": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:tThere is a small table with several books put next to the target, and it's front facing the wite bookcase"
  },
  "9614": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The single sofa is placed front facing the bookcase ,and back facing the glass door to the balcony in the relaxing area."
  },
  "9615": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a wooden circle table put nearby and a carp put on the ground  in front of the single chair."
  },
  "9616": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:stand  front facing the bookcase, irregular shape, its color is brown "
  },
  "9617": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:tThere is a small table with several books put next to the target, and it's front facing the wite bookcase"
  },
  "9618": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The single sofa is placed front facing the bookcase ,and back facing the glass door to the balcony in the relaxing area."
  },
  "9619": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a wooden circle table put nearby and a carp put on the ground  in front of the single chair."
  },
  "9620": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:yellow, woody and round"
  },
  "9621": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to a table and closest to the lamp."
  },
  "9622": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a chatting room on the first floor."
  },
  "9623": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chatting room is next to the hall."
  },
  "9624": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white;rotatable;with wheels;"
  },
  "9625": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:beside the other similar stool; beside the drinking dispenser;"
  },
  "9626": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:behind the front desk;"
  },
  "9627": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:a bar with a vase on it."
  },
  "9628": {
    "question": "Question:what does the box look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, empty, white "
  },
  "9629": {
    "question": "Question:where is the box?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of a door, on a table"
  },
  "9630": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the box in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The box is settled in the corner of a table in a study."
  },
  "9631": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the box?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a big table and two chairs and ii is on the first floor in the study"
  },
  "9632": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Black, square, leather."
  },
  "9633": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are grey cushions and pillows on the sofa, and a coffee table in front."
  },
  "9634": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is inside the open-air balcony."
  },
  "9635": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is near the living room, by the street."
  },
  "9636": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Beige and brown, soild and wooden. "
  },
  "9637": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is on the right side of a white bed, near a colorful painting and near a blue chair."
  },
  "9638": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is in a bedrioom on the second floor."
  },
  "9639": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is near a toilet."
  },
  "9640": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White, wooden and layered."
  },
  "9641": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is on a corner and near a clutter."
  },
  "9642": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is in a utility room."
  },
  "9643": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The room connects with a big living room and leads to a small bedroom via a ladder."
  },
  "9644": {
    "question": "Question:what does the power switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is white, small and square."
  },
  "9645": {
    "question": "Question:where is the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is between the window and the door."
  },
  "9646": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the power switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is in the aisle."
  },
  "9647": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is between the window and the door."
  },
  "9648": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is red, big and square."
  },
  "9649": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is hung on the wall above the guitar."
  },
  "9650": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is hung on the wall above the guitar."
  },
  "9651": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are many posters in the corridor."
  },
  "9652": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A small metal sink integrated with the cabinet."
  },
  "9653": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is under a shelf and  neara picture and some flowers."
  },
  "9654": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a laundry room."
  },
  "9655": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near the bedroom on the second floor."
  },
  "9656": {
    "question": "Question:what does the closestool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cylindrical, porcellanous, white"
  },
  "9657": {
    "question": "Question:where is the closestool?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a towel, next to a refuse bin"
  },
  "9658": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the closestool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The closestool is settled in a toilte. "
  },
  "9659": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the closestool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The toilet is settled in the corner of a bedroom."
  },
  "9660": {
    "question": "Question:what does the seat look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:long\uff1bblack leather;wooden frames;"
  },
  "9661": {
    "question": "Question:where is the seat?",
    "answer": "Answer:beside a big box;near two cabinets;"
  },
  "9662": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the seat in?",
    "answer": "Answer:in the center of this room."
  },
  "9663": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the seat?",
    "answer": "Answer:having washrooms and shower cubicles."
  },
  "9664": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Square, glass and clean."
  },
  "9665": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is near the washstand and the door."
  },
  "9666": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Mirror is in the living room."
  },
  "9667": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is near the toilet and bedroom."
  },
  "9668": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Blue, leather and soild."
  },
  "9669": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is next to a round table under a white hollow-out tablecloth, on the left side of a tall brown mirror and behind a tiger skin rug."
  },
  "9670": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in a bedroom with a blue carpet."
  },
  "9671": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is near a study and opposite to a corridor with a wooden stair."
  },
  "9672": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soild, cuboid and silvery."
  },
  "9673": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is set above the fruits and a induction cooker, and near a big table with a silvery sink."
  },
  "9674": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is set in a kitchen."
  },
  "9675": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is near a rest room."
  },
  "9676": {
    "question": "Question:what does the light look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:orange yellow, electronic and having four."
  },
  "9677": {
    "question": "Question:where is the light?",
    "answer": "Answer:These lights is on a sink and in front of a big mirror."
  },
  "9678": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the light in?",
    "answer": "Answer:These lights are in a bathroom."
  },
  "9679": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the light?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area connects with a bedroom and near a toilet."
  },
  "9680": {
    "question": "Question:what does the light look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:orange yellow, electronic and having four."
  },
  "9681": {
    "question": "Question:where is the light?",
    "answer": "Answer:These lights is on a sink and in front of a big mirror."
  },
  "9682": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the light in?",
    "answer": "Answer:These lights are in a bathroom."
  },
  "9683": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the light?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area connects with a bedroom and near a toilet."
  },
  "9684": {
    "question": "Question:what does the light look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:orange yellow, electronic and having four."
  },
  "9685": {
    "question": "Question:where is the light?",
    "answer": "Answer:These lights is on a sink and in front of a big mirror."
  },
  "9686": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the light in?",
    "answer": "Answer:These lights are in a bathroom."
  },
  "9687": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the light?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area connects with a bedroom and near a toilet."
  },
  "9688": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:laigh; large; covered by black leather;"
  },
  "9689": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:towards two similar decorative pictures.beside a sink;"
  },
  "9690": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:in the center of the squared room;"
  },
  "9691": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:a room with wooden floors."
  },
  "9692": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A medium-sized wooden chair with a backrest."
  },
  "9693": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is the rightmost chair placed by the table,behind which are a wall and three chairs. "
  },
  "9694": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair lies  near the corridor and is set on a carpet"
  },
  "9695": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a cooktop and is near stairs."
  },
  "9696": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden, rectangular, brown"
  },
  "9697": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:under the chandelier, next to the small table"
  },
  "9698": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is located in the bright dining room."
  },
  "9699": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The dining room is on the first floor and next to the kitchen."
  },
  "9700": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:regular octagon,glass,smooth"
  },
  "9701": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's above a table and near a white small chair."
  },
  "9702": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a corridor on the first floor."
  },
  "9703": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:the corridor links a living room and a stair and a storage room."
  },
  "9704": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:stony,black and round"
  },
  "9705": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to two black chairs and a big windows"
  },
  "9706": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is located on the balcony "
  },
  "9707": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:the balcony is next to a study room and there is a stair in the corner"
  },
  "9708": {
    "question": "Question:what does the snik look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, metallic, rectangular"
  },
  "9709": {
    "question": "Question:where is the snik?",
    "answer": "Answer:in the middle of big table, above the cabinet"
  },
  "9710": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the snik in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is set in the middle of the kitchen."
  },
  "9711": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the snik?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to the balcony, next to the dining room and on the third floor."
  },
  "9712": {
    "question": "Question:what does the doorhand look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:silver, "
  },
  "9713": {
    "question": "Question:where is the doorhand?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the door, next to the living room"
  },
  "9714": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the doorhand in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The doorhand is located in a corner which is between the living room and the toilet."
  },
  "9715": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the doorhand?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is between the living room and the toilet."
  },
  "9716": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown, rounded, short"
  },
  "9717": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the sofa, across to the TV"
  },
  "9718": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the living room."
  },
  "9719": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the dining room and the kitchen."
  },
  "9720": {
    "question": "Question:what does the plant look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:green,wooden and with strong stems and leaves"
  },
  "9721": {
    "question": "Question:where is the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the left side of the big shelf and next to the glass wall"
  },
  "9722": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the plant in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The plant is in a meeting area."
  },
  "9723": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is near the balcony outside the window and at the back of the restaurant."
  },
  "9724": {
    "question": "Question:what does the guitar look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:middle size,yellow and brown"
  },
  "9725": {
    "question": "Question:where is the guitar?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a sofa and a fireplace."
  },
  "9726": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the guitar in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a living room on the first floor"
  },
  "9727": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the guitar?",
    "answer": "Answer:the living room is near a dining room and kitchen and a stair."
  },
  "9728": {
    "question": "Question:what does the paintings look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Rectangular, monochrome and small."
  },
  "9729": {
    "question": "Question:where is the paintings?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is settled on the wall, above a bookshelf under a black sculpture and two photos and it is in the second row and second column of the six pictures."
  },
  "9730": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the paintings in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is in a study."
  },
  "9731": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the paintings?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is near a living and a bathroom."
  },
  "9732": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is small, leather and grey."
  },
  "9733": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is placed under the desk below the flower."
  },
  "9734": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is placed under the desk below the flower in the living room."
  },
  "9735": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are many paintings and a keyboard in the living room."
  },
  "9736": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is small, leather and grey."
  },
  "9737": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is placed under the desk below the flower."
  },
  "9738": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is placed under the desk below the flower in the living room."
  },
  "9739": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are many paintings and a keyboard in the living room."
  },
  "9740": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Leather, red and soild."
  },
  "9741": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is set on the right side of a blue sofa, near a green bed and near a black television."
  },
  "9742": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in a bedroom."
  },
  "9743": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is near a corridor."
  },
  "9744": {
    "question": "Question:what does the air conditioning look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White middle-sized hanging air conditioning."
  },
  "9745": {
    "question": "Question:where is the air conditioning?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near the fan and just under the ceiling"
  },
  "9746": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the air conditioning in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is attached to the front wall of the bedroom."
  },
  "9747": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the air conditioning?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a toilet and two bedrooms."
  },
  "9748": {
    "question": "Question:what does the paintings look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Medium size, balck and white and blue and rectangular."
  },
  "9749": {
    "question": "Question:where is the paintings?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is near a gray sculpture and a black bookshelf."
  },
  "9750": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the paintings in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is in a living room."
  },
  "9751": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the paintings?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is near a balcony."
  },
  "9752": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, rectangular, white"
  },
  "9753": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a table, facing a mirror"
  },
  "9754": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is settled in a wide bedroom on the second floor."
  },
  "9755": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is next to a long corridor and there is a living downstairs."
  },
  "9756": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, rectangular, white"
  },
  "9757": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a table, facing a mirror"
  },
  "9758": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is settled in a wide bedroom on the second floor."
  },
  "9759": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is next to a long corridor and there is a living downstairs."
  },
  "9760": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soild, wooden and beige and brown."
  },
  "9761": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is near a white bed, on a bedside table and near a white cabinet."
  },
  "9762": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is in a bedroom on the second floor."
  },
  "9763": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is near a toilet."
  },
  "9764": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black and white, cylinder, big"
  },
  "9765": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a bed, on a table"
  },
  "9766": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is in a large bedroom on the second floor."
  },
  "9767": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is next to a corridor and has a balcony, and there are many sofas in it."
  },
  "9768": {
    "question": "Question:what does the paintings look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Rectangular, soild and papery."
  },
  "9769": {
    "question": "Question:where is the paintings?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is settled on the white wall, above a black wooden screen and between two windows."
  },
  "9770": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the paintings in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is in the living room."
  },
  "9771": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the paintings?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is on the opposite side of a corridor and a art studio."
  },
  "9772": {
    "question": "Question:what does the poster look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The poster is big, square and colorful."
  },
  "9773": {
    "question": "Question:where is the poster?",
    "answer": "Answer:The poster is next to the power switch and the door."
  },
  "9774": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the poster in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The poster is next to the power switch and the door."
  },
  "9775": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the poster?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are many posters in the corridor."
  },
  "9776": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, gray, cloth"
  },
  "9777": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:facing a white table, next to a chair"
  },
  "9778": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is settled in a kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "9779": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to a dining room and a small storeroom."
  },
  "9780": {
    "question": "Question:what does the switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, wall-mounted, white"
  },
  "9781": {
    "question": "Question:where is the switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:hung on the wall, across the picture"
  },
  "9782": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the toilet."
  },
  "9783": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is in a corner which is next to the dining room."
  },
  "9784": {
    "question": "Question:what does the desk look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:woody, white and cuboid."
  },
  "9785": {
    "question": "Question:where is the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are some machines and a lamp on the desk, and a black chair is in front of it."
  },
  "9786": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the desk in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The desk is in a big and bright living room."
  },
  "9787": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:The desk is next to a kitchen and a bedroom upstairs. "
  },
  "9788": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rattan, heavy, brown"
  },
  "9789": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a woody bed, face a window with blue curtain"
  },
  "9790": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in the bedroom."
  },
  "9791": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is next to the stairs and the master bedroom."
  },
  "9792": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stair handrail look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:gray, hollow, tall "
  },
  "9793": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stair handrail?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to stairs, near a bookshelf"
  },
  "9794": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stair handrail in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stair handrail is located in a bar."
  },
  "9795": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stair handrail?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a bookshelf and stairs in the corner of the bar."
  },
  "9796": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:metal bracket; black; long;"
  },
  "9797": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:with one towel on the backrest and the other on the cushion;"
  },
  "9798": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:below a security identifier;opposite a TV hung on the ceilng;"
  },
  "9799": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:a big hall with a row of chairs and a big rounded bar in the center of it."
  },
  "9800": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bedside table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle, black, wooden"
  },
  "9801": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bedside table?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a lamp on it, it's on the left side of the bed."
  },
  "9802": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bedside table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's put in a big and  bright main bedroom."
  },
  "9803": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bedside table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The master bedroom faces the balcony. Right below the room is the swimming pool."
  },
  "9804": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is large, white and rectangular."
  },
  "9805": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is in the corner and beside the table."
  },
  "9806": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is the kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "9807": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is in the corner and beside the table."
  },
  "9808": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown chair and grey cushion, a small chair "
  },
  "9809": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's put at the corner outside the hovel , there is a picture put on the back wall"
  },
  "9810": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The small chair is put at the cornerr outside the hovel ,which is under a beautiful picture."
  },
  "9811": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a median size table put at the corridor and there are two small bedrooms close to the small chair."
  },
  "9812": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:oval; delicate; grey stripes."
  },
  "9813": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:below a spotlight; against a blue wall."
  },
  "9814": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:at the right corner of the room"
  },
  "9815": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:a room full of grey stripes."
  },
  "9816": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:soft\u3001long and it's a lounge chair"
  },
  "9817": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a square stool and near a same kind of sling chair"
  },
  "9818": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in the corner of the balcony on the second floor "
  },
  "9819": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:the balcony is near a garden and a study room with a stair"
  },
  "9820": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:soft\u3001long and it's a lounge chair"
  },
  "9821": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a square stool and near a same kind of sling chair"
  },
  "9822": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in the corner of the balcony on the second floor "
  },
  "9823": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:the balcony is near a garden and a study room with a stair"
  },
  "9824": {
    "question": "Question:what does the toilet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, small, white"
  },
  "9825": {
    "question": "Question:where is the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the washstand, under the white picture "
  },
  "9826": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the toilet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The toilet is set in the washroom."
  },
  "9827": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washroom is inside the bedroom, which is on the second floor and on the left of the corridor when go upstairs."
  },
  "9828": {
    "question": "Question:what does the drawer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is small, closed and wooden."
  },
  "9829": {
    "question": "Question:where is the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a shelf and some bottles of wine above the drawer."
  },
  "9830": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the drawer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is placed below the shelf and some bottles of wine."
  },
  "9831": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a desk and some chairs on the opposite."
  },
  "9832": {
    "question": "Question:what does the toilet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White, porcelainous and soild."
  },
  "9833": {
    "question": "Question:where is the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The toilet is set opposite to a white sink and near a brown and blue drawer."
  },
  "9834": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the toilet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The toilet is in a bathroom."
  },
  "9835": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The toilet is near a corridor."
  },
  "9836": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is rectangular, leathery and white."
  },
  "9837": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in the middle of the two tables."
  },
  "9838": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is on the ground floor kitchen."
  },
  "9839": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in the middle of the two tables."
  },
  "9840": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Wooden and leather, green and big."
  },
  "9841": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is near a green sofa and red sofa and next to a tall brown lamp."
  },
  "9842": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is in a bedroom."
  },
  "9843": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is near a toilet and a corridor."
  },
  "9844": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden, quaint and delicate."
  },
  "9845": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is the same chair on the left of it, and a sofa is across from the chair."
  },
  "9846": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:This chair is on a dining room."
  },
  "9847": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area is near a kitchen and near a stair."
  },
  "9848": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:median size ,rectangle ,wooden frame "
  },
  "9849": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:the bedroom door is close to the mirror ,and it is installed on the wall opposite the dressing room"
  },
  "9850": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The median size mirror is installed on the side wall of the detached bedroom,close to the door and opposite the dressing room."
  },
  "9851": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a balcony in the bedroom and the door is not very big."
  },
  "9852": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, brown, leather"
  },
  "9853": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of the yellow and tall table, next to the long sofa, there is a pillow on it"
  },
  "9854": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is located in the spacious livingroom."
  },
  "9855": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The livingroom is on the first floor and next to the kitchen."
  },
  "9856": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:silver, metallic, small"
  },
  "9857": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a bed and a white chair, on a white nightstand"
  },
  "9858": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's located in a bright bedroom and near the wall"
  },
  "9859": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is at the end of the corridor. There is a balcony outside and a washroom inside. There is a stair outside the door and it's on the right of the stairs."
  },
  "9860": {
    "question": "Question:what does the microwave look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, silver and black, wall-mounted"
  },
  "9861": {
    "question": "Question:where is the microwave?",
    "answer": "Answer:hung on the wall, above the cooking bench"
  },
  "9862": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the microwave in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the kitchen."
  },
  "9863": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the microwave?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the dining room and the living room."
  },
  "9864": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, rectangular, colorful"
  },
  "9865": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a door, in front of a printer and a box"
  },
  "9866": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is on the wall in the living room."
  },
  "9867": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room has a salver in the center and a big sofa."
  },
  "9868": {
    "question": "Question:what does the newspaper look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:paper,thin and rectangle,colorful and with a lofs of word on it"
  },
  "9869": {
    "question": "Question:where is the newspaper?",
    "answer": "Answer:The newspaper is surrouded by two green staplers and on the left of  a laptop and it's on a white desk, and is in front of a chair."
  },
  "9870": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the newspaper in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The newspaper is in a big office that is large enough for six people to work."
  },
  "9871": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the newspaper?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is at the corner is at the corner of the three fork road and next to an empty office and opposite to the room 356."
  },
  "9872": {
    "question": "Question:what does the toilet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Porcelainous, medium size and black."
  },
  "9873": {
    "question": "Question:where is the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The toilet is set on the opposite side of a black and golden sink and near a silvery and yellow vase."
  },
  "9874": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the toilet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The toilet is in a toilet on the first floor."
  },
  "9875": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The toilet is near a corridor and a kitchen."
  },
  "9876": {
    "question": "Question:what does the toy look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Cloth, soild and small."
  },
  "9877": {
    "question": "Question:where is the toy?",
    "answer": "Answer:The toy is set on a brown table, before the window and between two photos."
  },
  "9878": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the toy in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The toy is in a bedrooom."
  },
  "9879": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the toy?",
    "answer": "Answer:The toy is near a corridor."
  },
  "9880": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A blue sofa with a blue and yellow pillow."
  },
  "9881": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is beside a black bench and faces a big patterned carpet."
  },
  "9882": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the living room."
  },
  "9883": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a stair and a storage room."
  },
  "9884": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:blue,tidy and big."
  },
  "9885": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is next to nightstand and under a picture."
  },
  "9886": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is in the bedroom."
  },
  "9887": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is close to the balcony and the bathroom."
  },
  "9888": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big,cloth and tidy."
  },
  "9889": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is under the picture, next to the dressing table."
  },
  "9890": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is set in the bedroom."
  },
  "9891": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is close to balcony and living room."
  },
  "9892": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Cloth, big and tidy."
  },
  "9893": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is under a picture on the wall and next to the lamp."
  },
  "9894": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is in the bedroom."
  },
  "9895": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is close to the balcony and the living room."
  },
  "9896": {
    "question": "Question:what does the power switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is white, square and plastic."
  },
  "9897": {
    "question": "Question:where is the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is on the wall and under the light."
  },
  "9898": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the power switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is beside the stairs."
  },
  "9899": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is on the wall and under the light."
  },
  "9900": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a large, new, square table."
  },
  "9901": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a router and TV directly above it."
  },
  "9902": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in the bedroom."
  },
  "9903": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is beside the corridor."
  },
  "9904": {
    "question": "Question:what does the drawer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, wood, white"
  },
  "9905": {
    "question": "Question:where is the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:behind a shelter, facing a door"
  },
  "9906": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the drawer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is in a wide and empty storeroom on the second room."
  },
  "9907": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The storeroom is next to a bathroom and is facing a cloakroom."
  },
  "9908": {
    "question": "Question:what does the towel look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, grey and oranges, hairy"
  },
  "9909": {
    "question": "Question:where is the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of the window and the closestool, next to the door of the bathroom"
  },
  "9910": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the towel in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towels are in the bathroom."
  },
  "9911": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathroom is next to the cloakroom and in the master bedroom on the third floor."
  },
  "9912": {
    "question": "Question:what does the window look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:glass, rectangular, bright"
  },
  "9913": {
    "question": "Question:where is the window?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the woody table and green chairs"
  },
  "9914": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the window in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the study."
  },
  "9915": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the window?",
    "answer": "Answer:The study is next to the bathroom and children's bedroom."
  },
  "9916": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cylinder, cloth, white"
  },
  "9917": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:on a brown table, next to a photo"
  },
  "9918": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is settled in a bright bedroom on the second floor."
  },
  "9919": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is next to a bashroom and connected with a gym."
  },
  "9920": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soild, h-shaped and brown."
  },
  "9921": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chairs are set under a big painting with golden border and near a brown cuboid table."
  },
  "9922": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chairs are in a dining room."
  },
  "9923": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chairs are near a kitchen."
  },
  "9924": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:tall; black;no armrest;"
  },
  "9925": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:against a big rounded bar; beside another three identical stools. near the huge pillar;"
  },
  "9926": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:the far left one near the pool"
  },
  "9927": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:the men's and women's changing rooms are out of the big hall "
  },
  "9928": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Big, brown and wooden."
  },
  "9929": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The carbinet is settled on the right side of a red leather chair and on the opposite side of a round wooden table under a vase."
  },
  "9930": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The carbinet is in a bedroom."
  },
  "9931": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The carbinet is opposite to a corridor."
  },
  "9932": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown, short and round."
  },
  "9933": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:There has a few bottles of wine on the table and has two red chairs on either hand."
  },
  "9934": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is set in a big and bright living room."
  },
  "9935": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is near a balcony and two black sofas are in front of it."
  },
  "9936": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pillow look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A small light yellow pillow."
  },
  "9937": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a dark red pillow and beside another light yellow pillow."
  },
  "9938": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pillow in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on the sofa which faces the projector directly."
  },
  "9939": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the living room."
  },
  "9940": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is closed, brown and square."
  },
  "9941": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a water-tap and a sink above the cabinet."
  },
  "9942": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is placed below the cupboard in the kitchen."
  },
  "9943": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are two big tables and a wine cabinet on the opposite of the cabinet."
  },
  "9944": {
    "question": "Question:what does the shower look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, cylinder, silvery"
  },
  "9945": {
    "question": "Question:where is the shower?",
    "answer": "Answer:below a light, next to a door"
  },
  "9946": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the shower in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The shower is in a small and bright bashroom."
  },
  "9947": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the shower?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bashroom is between a gym and a bedroom on the second floor."
  },
  "9948": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:static , glass , reflective"
  },
  "9949": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:under a list of bulb, above the sink"
  },
  "9950": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is located on the wall , at a corner of the bathroom."
  },
  "9951": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathroom is inside of the bedroom."
  },
  "9952": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chairs are black, golden and standing."
  },
  "9953": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is placed under the table and the flower."
  },
  "9954": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is placed under the table and the flower in the dining room."
  },
  "9955": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are many recliners and sofas in the balcony."
  },
  "9956": {
    "question": "Question:what does the flowers look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Small, floriated and pink and white."
  },
  "9957": {
    "question": "Question:where is the flowers?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flowers are set in a transparent vase, on a beige table and near two white sinks."
  },
  "9958": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the flowers in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flowers are in a bathroom."
  },
  "9959": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the flowers?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flowers are near a bedroom."
  },
  "9960": {
    "question": "Question:what does the desk look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:woody , big , rectangular"
  },
  "9961": {
    "question": "Question:where is the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the sofa and the green chair"
  },
  "9962": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the desk in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the living room"
  },
  "9963": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the staircase and on the third floor."
  },
  "9964": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pillows look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White, soild and soft."
  },
  "9965": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pillows?",
    "answer": "Answer:The pillows are set on a white and brown bed and underneath two skateboards."
  },
  "9966": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pillows in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The pillows are in a bedroom."
  },
  "9967": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pillows?",
    "answer": "Answer:The pillows are near a toilet."
  },
  "9968": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Medium size, rectangular and brown."
  },
  "9969": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set next to a blue and brown bed and near three white doors."
  },
  "9970": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in a bedroom."
  },
  "9971": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is near a living room and a toilet."
  },
  "9972": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:ceramic, square, white"
  },
  "9973": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:under the mirror, facing the balcony, next to the toilet"
  },
  "9974": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is located in the washroom."
  },
  "9975": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washroom is inside the bedroom, which is on the second floor and on the left of the corridor when go upstairs."
  },
  "9976": {
    "question": "Question:what does the doorhand look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Small, black and golden, metal."
  },
  "9977": {
    "question": "Question:where is the doorhand?",
    "answer": "Answer:Doorhand is on the door, next to the button."
  },
  "9978": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the doorhand in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The doorhand is in the living room."
  },
  "9979": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the doorhand?",
    "answer": "Answer:The doorhand is close to the toilet and bathroom."
  },
  "9980": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle , made of cotton, it's a small bed which only allows one people to sleep"
  },
  "9981": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:there is a white clothing cabinet placed opposite the bed ,and a beautiful painting put on the back wall"
  },
  "9982": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The small bed is placed at the center of the small bedroom, which is opposite the white clothing cabinet.,"
  },
  "9983": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are two wooden side cupboards put at each side of the small bed, and some curtains placed close to the french windows."
  },
  "9984": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sanitary bucket look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:long,dark,ceramic"
  },
  "9985": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sanitary bucket?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's near a big bucket and the dining table."
  },
  "9986": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sanitary bucket in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a dining room on the first floor."
  },
  "9987": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sanitary bucket?",
    "answer": "Answer:the dining room is near a living room and a stair ."
  },
  "9988": {
    "question": "Question:what does the drawer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a large, white wooden drawer."
  },
  "9989": {
    "question": "Question:where is the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the middle of two white cabinets."
  },
  "9990": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the drawer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in the dining room."
  },
  "9991": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to a study and kitchen."
  },
  "9992": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Leather, big and white."
  },
  "9993": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is set near a white sofa, near a black television and next to a black table."
  },
  "9994": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in a living room."
  },
  "9995": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is near a bedroom."
  },
  "9996": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stairs look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:yellow, spiral and woody"
  },
  "9997": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stairs?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is nex to the light post and under a light."
  },
  "9998": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stairs in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the chatting room on the first floor."
  },
  "9999": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stairs?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is the access between the charring room and office."
  },
  "10000": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is large, square and white."
  },
  "10001": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is on the right of two sofas and the left of a sofa."
  },
  "10002": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in the entertainment hall."
  },
  "10003": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is on the right of two sofas and the left of a sofa."
  },
  "10004": {
    "question": "Question:what does the ball look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:metal,globular,smooth\n"
  },
  "10005": {
    "question": "Question:where is the ball?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's on a round transparent table and next to 2 chairs."
  },
  "10006": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the ball in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a living room on the second floor ."
  },
  "10007": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the ball?",
    "answer": "Answer:the living room is near a dining room and a open-balcony."
  },
  "10008": {
    "question": "Question:what does the telescope look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:precise, black and with a tripod."
  },
  "10009": {
    "question": "Question:where is the telescope?",
    "answer": "Answer:The telescope is in front of a big window, and near flower beds."
  },
  "10010": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the telescope in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The telescope is on a narrow room."
  },
  "10011": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the telescope?",
    "answer": "Answer:The narrow room is connected with an attic and stairs."
  },
  "10012": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a small, black, square stool."
  },
  "10013": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:It was beside a cabinet and a chair."
  },
  "10014": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is in a living room.\n"
  },
  "10015": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a clean, tidy and spacious living room."
  },
  "10016": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, rectangle "
  },
  "10017": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:right above it is a tap, a sink and a mirror."
  },
  "10018": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is installed on a small washing room."
  },
  "10019": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washing room is built in a small bright bedroom which has the main bedroom on one side and the laundry on the other."
  },
  "10020": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mouse look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:plastic cement,cuboid,black,small"
  },
  "10021": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mouse?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mouse is on the right side of two water bottles and two pack granule,at the edge of a desk,on a white book and above a note."
  },
  "10022": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mouse in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mouse is in a big office that is large enough for six people to work."
  },
  "10023": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mouse?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is at the corner is at the corner of the three fork road  and opposite to the room 356."
  },
  "10024": {
    "question": "Question:what does the television look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:electronic , small , rectangle"
  },
  "10025": {
    "question": "Question:where is the television?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the cabinet , next to the wall"
  },
  "10026": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the television in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The television is located in front of the bed , in the bedroom."
  },
  "10027": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the television?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is surrounded by a bal, a living room and a bathroom."
  },
  "10028": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:short, leather, black"
  },
  "10029": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:under the window, next to the sofa"
  },
  "10030": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is set in the spacious livingroom."
  },
  "10031": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The livingroom is on the first floor and next to the kitchen."
  },
  "10032": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a yellow, glass transparent ceiling light."
  },
  "10033": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is directly above a wooden chair and a table."
  },
  "10034": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is set in a corridor at the door of a house."
  },
  "10035": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is set beside the door of a kitchen."
  },
  "10036": {
    "question": "Question:what does the flower look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white,elegant \n"
  },
  "10037": {
    "question": "Question:where is the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a washstand and a mirror ."
  },
  "10038": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the flower in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's on a white table in a washroom on the second floor."
  },
  "10039": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:the washroom is next to a stair,a living room and a rest room."
  },
  "10040": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, white and gray, cloth"
  },
  "10041": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a tea table, facing a long table"
  },
  "10042": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in a big and white living room on the first floor."
  },
  "10043": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is in front a corridor and next to a small living room."
  },
  "10044": {
    "question": "Question:what does the telephone look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:plastic; white; cambered;"
  },
  "10045": {
    "question": "Question:where is the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:above two boxes; opposite a closed door."
  },
  "10046": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the telephone in?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the wall of a hallway which leads to a small bathing pool;"
  },
  "10047": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a room specially used for washing near it."
  },
  "10048": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Tall,yellow,wooden."
  },
  "10049": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is placed near a table with white top ,on the right of a wooden stool."
  },
  "10050": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is set in a tearoom."
  },
  "10051": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is placed near a reading room and the hall."
  },
  "10052": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is large, rectangular and white."
  },
  "10053": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is beside the window and door."
  },
  "10054": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in the bedroom."
  },
  "10055": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is beside the window and door."
  },
  "10056": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, rectangular"
  },
  "10057": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:above the mirror, across from the bed"
  },
  "10058": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the children's bedroom."
  },
  "10059": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the study and the bathroom."
  },
  "10060": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a square, old mirror with a golden frame."
  },
  "10061": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's on a cabinet next to the flower."
  },
  "10062": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in a living room."
  },
  "10063": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's beside a kitchen."
  },
  "10064": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:yellow,reflective,oval"
  },
  "10065": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's near a door, some books and hang on wall."
  },
  "10066": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a living room on the first floor."
  },
  "10067": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:the living room is near a dining room ,a kitchen ,a corridor and a stair."
  },
  "10068": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stairs look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Brown, woody and carpet-covered"
  },
  "10069": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stairs?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is covered by a checkered carpet and beneath a light along the stairs."
  },
  "10070": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stairs in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is the connection of the living room and the bedroom on the second floor."
  },
  "10071": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stairs?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed between the kitchen and the living room."
  },
  "10072": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown with wood grains; quite tall;simple style;"
  },
  "10073": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:below two identical mirrors and a wall lamp; next to a hair dryer;"
  },
  "10074": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:aginst the wall behind the open door;"
  },
  "10075": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:a changing room equipped with a shower cubicle and a restroom;"
  },
  "10076": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bush look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:static,green ,lush"
  },
  "10077": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bush?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a stone lion and straightly in front of a balcony "
  },
  "10078": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bush in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it  is located in a garden on the second floor"
  },
  "10079": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bush?",
    "answer": "Answer:the garden is near a balcony and the balcony is near a study room with a stair"
  },
  "10080": {
    "question": "Question:what does the windows look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Normal, rectangle and iron-covered"
  },
  "10081": {
    "question": "Question:where is the windows?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed opposite the door and in the middle of the wall."
  },
  "10082": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the windows in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed in a storeroom."
  },
  "10083": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the windows?",
    "answer": "Answer:This storeroom is located at the end of the right turn on the second floor."
  },
  "10084": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:square, wooden and glass, black and white"
  },
  "10085": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the wall, facing the stairs, among six pictures and third from left"
  },
  "10086": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is set on the corridor."
  },
  "10087": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The corridor has two stairs and on the second floor."
  },
  "10088": {
    "question": "Question:what does the dustbin look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black,short,plastic,hollow"
  },
  "10089": {
    "question": "Question:where is the dustbin?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the left of the innermost desks ,in front of a black cabinet and on the right side of the white cabinet"
  },
  "10090": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the dustbin in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a large office owning the number 377 containing many sets of tables and chairs."
  },
  "10091": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the dustbin?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is at the corner of a junction of three roads and on the left of the stairway door."
  },
  "10092": {
    "question": "Question:what does the drawer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Medium size, soild and brown and black."
  },
  "10093": {
    "question": "Question:where is the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is below a small rectangular painting, on the left side of a black and gray bed and opposite to a yellow and white table."
  },
  "10094": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the drawer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is in a bedroom."
  },
  "10095": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is near a corridor and a living room."
  },
  "10096": {
    "question": "Question:what does the trash bin look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:square, grey and plastic"
  },
  "10097": {
    "question": "Question:where is the trash bin?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to a cabinet and the piano."
  },
  "10098": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the trash bin in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a hall on the first floor.\n"
  },
  "10099": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the trash bin?",
    "answer": "Answer:The hall is next to the chatting room.\n"
  },
  "10100": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabniet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Braided, rectangle and brown"
  },
  "10101": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabniet?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a piece of glass on it and it is beneath a picture."
  },
  "10102": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabniet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed in the corner of the bedroom and between the door and the wardrobe."
  },
  "10103": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabniet?",
    "answer": "Answer:This bedroom is located at the end of the right turn on the second floor, next to another bedroom and a storage room."
  },
  "10104": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:long, wooden, brown "
  },
  "10105": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:Right above it is a big picture and a plant."
  },
  "10106": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in a small bright bedroom."
  },
  "10107": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It has the main bedroom on one side and the laundry on the other."
  },
  "10108": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cahir look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:round, yellow and woody"
  },
  "10109": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cahir?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to a table and closest to a carpet."
  },
  "10110": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cahir in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a chatting room on the first floor."
  },
  "10111": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cahir?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chatting room is next to the hall."
  },
  "10112": {
    "question": "Question:what does the curtain look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Beige, big and cloth."
  },
  "10113": {
    "question": "Question:where is the curtain?",
    "answer": "Answer:The curtain is opposite to a small brassy switch and near a beige and brown lamp."
  },
  "10114": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the curtain in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The curtain is in a bedroom."
  },
  "10115": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the curtain?",
    "answer": "Answer:The curtain is near a toilet and a corridor."
  },
  "10116": {
    "question": "Question:what does the curtain look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Beige, big and cloth."
  },
  "10117": {
    "question": "Question:where is the curtain?",
    "answer": "Answer:The curtain is opposite to a small brassy switch and near a beige and brown lamp."
  },
  "10118": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the curtain in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The curtain is in a bedroom."
  },
  "10119": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the curtain?",
    "answer": "Answer:The curtain is near a toilet and a corridor."
  },
  "10120": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle, brown and woody"
  },
  "10121": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is above the cabinet and under the light."
  },
  "10122": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a restroom on the first floor."
  },
  "10123": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The restroom is in the bedroom which is at the right turn of the gate."
  },
  "10124": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, glass, big"
  },
  "10125": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the wall, facing the curtain"
  },
  "10126": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is set in the spacious office."
  },
  "10127": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is on the first floor and next to the livingroom and stairs."
  },
  "10128": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:movable, brown, leather chair"
  },
  "10129": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a table, near a box"
  },
  "10130": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is settled in the middle of a study."
  },
  "10131": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The study connects with a bedroom and a living room."
  },
  "10132": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Wooden, rectangular and small."
  },
  "10133": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is near a green sofa, in front of a beige cabinet and near a television."
  },
  "10134": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is in a bedroom."
  },
  "10135": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is near a corridor."
  },
  "10136": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a white wooden rectangular table.\n"
  },
  "10137": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are two desk lamps on it.\n"
  },
  "10138": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a living room.\n"
  },
  "10139": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a clean, tidy and spacious living room.\n"
  },
  "10140": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Tall,cylindrical\uff0cwhite\n"
  },
  "10141": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is set next to a white stool in a corner."
  },
  "10142": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is set in a small conference room."
  },
  "10143": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is placed near a bigger conference room and next to the hall."
  },
  "10144": {
    "question": "Question:what does the dustbin look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black,cuboid and plastic"
  },
  "10145": {
    "question": "Question:where is the dustbin?",
    "answer": "Answer:under the table,in front of a chair and between two cabinets on the floor"
  },
  "10146": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the dustbin in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The dustbin is in an office with the number 302."
  },
  "10147": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the dustbin?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is in front of a corridor door and next to the tea room."
  },
  "10148": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Brown, circular and wooden."
  },
  "10149": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is set on a rectangular patterned carpet and under a ceiling lamp with yellow light."
  },
  "10150": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is in the middle of the corridor."
  },
  "10151": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is near a stair and near a dining room."
  },
  "10152": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black and white,short and small,metal,cuboid"
  },
  "10153": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the left of the glass wall,behind the chair and faces the door directly"
  },
  "10154": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in a small single office signed number 362."
  },
  "10155": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is opposite to a public working office and has a path leading to the stairs on the left."
  },
  "10156": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Black and white, rectangular, real"
  },
  "10157": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a window next to it and a switch below the side"
  },
  "10158": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Picture on the wall of the corridor"
  },
  "10159": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:Picture between the living room stairs and bedroom, opposite the toilet"
  },
  "10160": {
    "question": "Question:what does the umbrella look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Black,cloth,collapsible"
  },
  "10161": {
    "question": "Question:where is the umbrella?",
    "answer": "Answer:The umbrella is set in a metal jar near a wall."
  },
  "10162": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the umbrella in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The umbrella is placed in a reading room."
  },
  "10163": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the umbrella?",
    "answer": "Answer:The umbrella is placed next to a tearoom."
  },
  "10164": {
    "question": "Question:what does the glass door look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black frame ,rectangle ,median size "
  },
  "10165": {
    "question": "Question:where is the glass door?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a small white cabinet put next to the glass door ,and a white sofa put close to it."
  },
  "10166": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the glass door in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The glass door is installed in the living room ,which is close to a white cabinet ."
  },
  "10167": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the glass door?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a big TV and several different size sofas put in the living room which without balcony."
  },
  "10168": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A tall and small, grey baby chair."
  },
  "10169": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to a glass door and a dark green carpet."
  },
  "10170": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is at the corner of the room,close to a stone wall and a white cement wall."
  },
  "10171": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a kicthen and a dining table."
  },
  "10172": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is ceramic, large and white."
  },
  "10173": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is beside the window and the vase."
  },
  "10174": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is in the kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "10175": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is beside the window and the vase."
  },
  "10176": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:yellow,long,soft"
  },
  "10177": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a big window and in front of a pool table."
  },
  "10178": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a living room on the first floor."
  },
  "10179": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:the living room is near a dining room and a stair."
  },
  "10180": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, elliptical and smooth"
  },
  "10181": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on the cabinet beneath the mirror."
  },
  "10182": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a restroom on the first floor."
  },
  "10183": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The restroom is in the bedroom which is at the right turn of the gate."
  },
  "10184": {
    "question": "Question:what does the potted plant look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:green, potted and round"
  },
  "10185": {
    "question": "Question:where is the potted plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is the third closest plant next to the open door and at the corner of the pool."
  },
  "10186": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the potted plant in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in front of the house."
  },
  "10187": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the potted plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is outside the house and in front of the gate."
  },
  "10188": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:plaid, small, soft"
  },
  "10189": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the wall, below the lamp"
  },
  "10190": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the living room "
  },
  "10191": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is on the second floor and next to the staircase and corridor."
  },
  "10192": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:modern, grey, thin"
  },
  "10193": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:set on a woody night table and next to a woody bed, near a window with blue curtain"
  },
  "10194": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is in the bedroom."
  },
  "10195": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer: The bedroom is next to the stairs and the master bedroom."
  },
  "10196": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black,tall,plastic and metal,with five wheels  "
  },
  "10197": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of a pillar,on the right side of the door"
  },
  "10198": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in a simply equipped office."
  },
  "10199": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is opposite to 302 big office,in front of the corridor gate and near the tea room."
  },
  "10200": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bench look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle, wooden "
  },
  "10201": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bench?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are some books put on it, It face the bed, Right above it is a picture"
  },
  "10202": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bench in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's put in a big and  bright main bedroom."
  },
  "10203": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bench?",
    "answer": "Answer:The master bedroom faces the balcony. Right below the room is the swimming pool."
  },
  "10204": {
    "question": "Question:what does the towel look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is small, square and grey."
  },
  "10205": {
    "question": "Question:where is the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is hung between the sink and the toilet."
  },
  "10206": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the towel in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is hung between the sink and the toilet in the bathroom."
  },
  "10207": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a shower room, sink and toilet in the bathroom."
  },
  "10208": {
    "question": "Question:what does the book look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle, paper, small"
  },
  "10209": {
    "question": "Question:where is the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:It has a plant and two books on the lower left, a glass bottle and a calendar on the right, and a display below."
  },
  "10210": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the book in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's put in a  open kitchen."
  },
  "10211": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:Here you can see the swimming pool, reception area and a wicket."
  },
  "10212": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is leather, big and grey."
  },
  "10213": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are some pillows on the sofa and a table in front of the table."
  },
  "10214": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is placed in front of the table."
  },
  "10215": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are many paintings on the wall of the living room."
  },
  "10216": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is grey, big and leather."
  },
  "10217": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are some pillows on the sofa and a table in front of the table."
  },
  "10218": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is placed in front of the table."
  },
  "10219": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is placed in front of the table in the living room."
  },
  "10220": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is leather, grey and big."
  },
  "10221": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a table and some flowers in front of the sofa."
  },
  "10222": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is placed in front of the table."
  },
  "10223": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is placed in front of the table in the living room."
  },
  "10224": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is big, square and grey."
  },
  "10225": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a table and some flowers in front of the sofa."
  },
  "10226": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is placed in front of the table facing some flowers."
  },
  "10227": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is placed in front of the table in the living room."
  },
  "10228": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is leather, big and lying."
  },
  "10229": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are some pillows on the sofa and a table in front of the sofa."
  },
  "10230": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is placed in front of the table facing the flower."
  },
  "10231": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are some paintings on the wall of the living room."
  },
  "10232": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Small, rectangular, red."
  },
  "10233": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are  one  chair  with the same size,  state on their left and a small  desk   opposite to it."
  },
  "10234": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chairs is in front of a  stone pillar."
  },
  "10235": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area has lots of red  chairs and a red carpet."
  },
  "10236": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a small, square, black table."
  },
  "10237": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a landline phone above it and a cabinet next to it."
  },
  "10238": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in the bedroom."
  },
  "10239": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is beside the corridor."
  },
  "10240": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stair handrail look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:gray, hollow, tall"
  },
  "10241": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stair handrail?",
    "answer": "Answer:near the stairs, near a bar counter"
  },
  "10242": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stair handrail in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stair handrail is in the bar."
  },
  "10243": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stair handrail?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bar connects with a gymnasium and has a trashcan."
  },
  "10244": {
    "question": "Question:what does the carbinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Big, ladder-shaped and brown."
  },
  "10245": {
    "question": "Question:where is the carbinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The carbinet is behind a brown wooden table with a whith hollow-out tablecloth and behind three brown chairs with blue mat."
  },
  "10246": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the carbinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The carbinet is at the corner of a bedroom with a blue carpet."
  },
  "10247": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the carbinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The carbinet is near a study."
  },
  "10248": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, rectangular, small"
  },
  "10249": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:under the white lamp, next to the window"
  },
  "10250": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the children's bedroom."
  },
  "10251": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the study and the bathroom."
  },
  "10252": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Wooden, brown and cuboid."
  },
  "10253": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is on a corner and near a beautiful carpet."
  },
  "10254": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stool is in a narrow room."
  },
  "10255": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The narrow room is connected with an attic and stairs."
  },
  "10256": {
    "question": "Question:what does the shower look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:metal, silvery, small"
  },
  "10257": {
    "question": "Question:where is the shower?",
    "answer": "Answer:below a cabinet, facing a door"
  },
  "10258": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the shower in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The shower is placed in the corner of a small bashroom."
  },
  "10259": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the shower?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bashroom is between a big empty room and a storeroom."
  },
  "10260": {
    "question": "Question:what does the window look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:transparent, normal, marginate"
  },
  "10261": {
    "question": "Question:where is the window?",
    "answer": "Answer:hung on the white wall, next to the curtain"
  },
  "10262": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the window in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the dining room. "
  },
  "10263": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the window?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a kitchen and a living room next to the dining room."
  },
  "10264": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Wooden frame, oblong and big."
  },
  "10265": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is on a cabinet and across from a big bed."
  },
  "10266": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is in a bedroom."
  },
  "10267": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom leads outdoors via a door and connects with a washroom."
  },
  "10268": {
    "question": "Question:what does the flowers look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soild, pink and beige and beautiful."
  },
  "10269": {
    "question": "Question:where is the flowers?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flowers are set in the transparent vases and on a transparent table surrounded by twelve transparent chairs."
  },
  "10270": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the flowers in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flowers are in a dining room."
  },
  "10271": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the flowers?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flowers are near a kitchen."
  },
  "10272": {
    "question": "Question:what does the flowers look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soild, pink and beige and beautiful."
  },
  "10273": {
    "question": "Question:where is the flowers?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flowers are set in the transparent vases and on a transparent table surrounded by twelve transparent chairs."
  },
  "10274": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the flowers in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flowers are in a dining room."
  },
  "10275": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the flowers?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flowers are near a kitchen."
  },
  "10276": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:elliptical, white and smooth"
  },
  "10277": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is beneath the mirror and on a cabinet."
  },
  "10278": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a restroom on the second floor."
  },
  "10279": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The restroom is at the left rear corner of the stairs."
  },
  "10280": {
    "question": "Question:what does the massage bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, rectangular, soft"
  },
  "10281": {
    "question": "Question:where is the massage bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:between decorations and a same massage bed, near a door\n\n"
  },
  "10282": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the massage bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is put in a small bedroom which is used to massage."
  },
  "10283": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the massage bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom has decorations and a big mural on the wall. "
  },
  "10284": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:square, white and black, wooden and black"
  },
  "10285": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the wall, next to the door, among five pictures and fifth from left"
  },
  "10286": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is set on the left of the corridor."
  },
  "10287": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The corridor is on the second floor, has some rooms and two stairs."
  },
  "10288": {
    "question": "Question:what does the paintings look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soild, small and rectangular."
  },
  "10289": {
    "question": "Question:where is the paintings?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is in the second row and the third column of the six paintings, on the wall and above a red and brown chair."
  },
  "10290": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the paintings in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is in a study."
  },
  "10291": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the paintings?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is near a bathroom."
  },
  "10292": {
    "question": "Question:what does the glass look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white ,oblong,tall"
  },
  "10293": {
    "question": "Question:where is the glass?",
    "answer": "Answer:leaning against the window and the book shelf and on the right of a dustbin"
  },
  "10294": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the glass in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The glass is in a large reading area."
  },
  "10295": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the glass?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is on the left side of the number 05 meeting room and behind the restaurant."
  },
  "10296": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cupboard look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big,wood,brown"
  },
  "10297": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cupboard?",
    "answer": "Answer:over the drawer and switch"
  },
  "10298": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cupboard in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in corridor"
  },
  "10299": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cupboard?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's dining room on the left of the cupboard and kitchen on the right side"
  },
  "10300": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, graceful, cylindrical"
  },
  "10301": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:near the mazarine bed and another lamp with the same color and shape, next to a long wall painting"
  },
  "10302": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is in the bedroom."
  },
  "10303": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is near the stairs and the bathroom."
  },
  "10304": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wide, rectangle, white"
  },
  "10305": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:behind the door, in the first position of the right side of the room"
  },
  "10306": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is in a big simple shared office with the number 363."
  },
  "10307": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is along the road to exit, around the corner of a junction of three roads and opposite to the single office."
  },
  "10308": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirrior look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Beige, soild and tall."
  },
  "10309": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirrior?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is set behind a brown wooden desk and on the opposite side of a red round sofa."
  },
  "10310": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirrior in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is in a reception room."
  },
  "10311": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirrior?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is near a porch."
  },
  "10312": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirrior look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Beige, soild and tall."
  },
  "10313": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirrior?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is set between two doors and on the left side of two same mirrors."
  },
  "10314": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirrior in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is in a reception room."
  },
  "10315": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirrior?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is settled next to a porch."
  },
  "10316": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirrior look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Wooden, beige and tall."
  },
  "10317": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirrior?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is set between wooden doors and next to two big, red and golden chairs."
  },
  "10318": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirrior in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is in a reception room."
  },
  "10319": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirrior?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is near a porch."
  },
  "10320": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a slightly old, rectangular, white frame.\n"
  },
  "10321": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is behind a door, directly opposite a switch.\n"
  },
  "10322": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's on a wall in an aisle."
  },
  "10323": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a narrow aisle."
  },
  "10324": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is square, closed and wooden."
  },
  "10325": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a sink and a water-tap above the drawer. "
  },
  "10326": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is placed below the sink and the water-tap."
  },
  "10327": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are some stools and table nearby."
  },
  "10328": {
    "question": "Question:what does the book look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Rectangular, yellow , thick."
  },
  "10329": {
    "question": "Question:where is the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a white cabinet under the book and a short desk next to it."
  },
  "10330": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the book in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The book is set close to the wall of the hall."
  },
  "10331": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area is located on the corner of the hall."
  },
  "10332": {
    "question": "Question:what does the toilet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small ,white,made by china"
  },
  "10333": {
    "question": "Question:where is the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's on the left of washstand and mirror"
  },
  "10334": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the toilet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in bathroom"
  },
  "10335": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:the bedroom is on the left side of it"
  },
  "10336": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A double bed with white sheets and black and white pillows."
  },
  "10337": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is between two nightstands and faces the balcony."
  },
  "10338": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a large room,near black sofa and a small table."
  },
  "10339": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near the stair to the large room."
  },
  "10340": {
    "question": "Question:what does the toilet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:taocide, oval and white"
  },
  "10341": {
    "question": "Question:where is the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is next to a cabinet and facing the bath."
  },
  "10342": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the toilet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:\nIt is in a restroom on the second floor."
  },
  "10343": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The restroom is on the life side of the stairs."
  },
  "10344": {
    "question": "Question:what does the drawer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is wooden, small and square."
  },
  "10345": {
    "question": "Question:where is the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a big suitcase besides and some books above."
  },
  "10346": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the drawer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is placed next to the suitcase below the books."
  },
  "10347": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are many clothes in the closet."
  },
  "10348": {
    "question": "Question:what does the drawer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is wooden, small and square."
  },
  "10349": {
    "question": "Question:where is the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a big suitcase besides and some books above."
  },
  "10350": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the drawer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is placed next to the suitcase below the books."
  },
  "10351": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are many clothes in the closet."
  },
  "10352": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bathtub look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Porcelainous, hollow and white."
  },
  "10353": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bathtub?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathtub is settled near a white towel and a table with two white sinks."
  },
  "10354": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bathtub in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathtub is in a bathroom."
  },
  "10355": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bathtub?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathtub is near a bedroom."
  },
  "10356": {
    "question": "Question:what does the switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:plastic, rectangle."
  },
  "10357": {
    "question": "Question:where is the switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:It has a very similar switch on its right and It has an outlet on the bottom right"
  },
  "10358": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in the first floor where  face the dinning table."
  },
  "10359": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:the garden is on its left and the swimming pool is on it's right."
  },
  "10360": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bike look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black,metal,with two wheels"
  },
  "10361": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bike?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of the entrance door,a big billboard,on the left of a shelf and behind a white sofa"
  },
  "10362": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bike in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bike is in the big lobby."
  },
  "10363": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bike?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bike is in front of the service desk and towards the food bar and the resting area."
  },
  "10364": {
    "question": "Question:what does the glasses look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Rectangular, colorless and transparent."
  },
  "10365": {
    "question": "Question:where is the glasses?",
    "answer": "Answer:The glasses are settled behind a beige long sofa, near a red painting and a black stove."
  },
  "10366": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the glasses in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The glasses are in a living room."
  },
  "10367": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the glasses?",
    "answer": "Answer:The glassed are near a balcony."
  },
  "10368": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is white, cloth and large."
  },
  "10369": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is beside the table and the lamp."
  },
  "10370": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in the lounge."
  },
  "10371": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is beside the table and the lamp."
  },
  "10372": {
    "question": "Question:what does the painting look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soild, rectangular and white and green."
  },
  "10373": {
    "question": "Question:where is the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is set near a brown table surrounded by four brown chairs and near a rectangular photo."
  },
  "10374": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the painting in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is set in a corridor."
  },
  "10375": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is near a bedroom and a living room."
  },
  "10376": {
    "question": "Question:what does the dining table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Rectangular, brown and wooden."
  },
  "10377": {
    "question": "Question:where is the dining table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The dining table is surrounded by nine brown wooden chairs, in front of a cabinet with three mirrors, and under a white tablecloth."
  },
  "10378": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the dining table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The dining table is set in a dining room."
  },
  "10379": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the dining table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The dining table is near a living room and a corridor."
  },
  "10380": {
    "question": "Question:what does the photo look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Papery, soild and small."
  },
  "10381": {
    "question": "Question:where is the photo?",
    "answer": "Answer:The photo is set in a bookcase, near a blue photo and near a black fitness equipment."
  },
  "10382": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the photo in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The photo is in a bedroom."
  },
  "10383": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the photo?",
    "answer": "Answer:The photo is near a toilet and a corridor."
  },
  "10384": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden and glass, square, black and white"
  },
  "10385": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the wall, facing the stairs, among six pictures and forth from left"
  },
  "10386": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is set on the corridor."
  },
  "10387": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The corridor has some rooms beside it and two stairs, it's on the second floor."
  },
  "10388": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:gray, leather"
  },
  "10389": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:There's an identical chair next to it but it's closer to the big sofa itself. It's next to a glass table."
  },
  "10390": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is put on the reception area."
  },
  "10391": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area faces the open kitchen, next to the pool, and dinning table on the other side."
  },
  "10392": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bench look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:long, wooden, brown"
  },
  "10393": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bench?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the table, under the chandelier"
  },
  "10394": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bench in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bench is set in the kitchen."
  },
  "10395": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bench?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is on the first floor and next to the livingroom."
  },
  "10396": {
    "question": "Question:what does the paintings look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Medium size, rectangular and with golden border."
  },
  "10397": {
    "question": "Question:where is the paintings?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is in the first row and the second column of the six paintings, on the wall and above a black bookshelf."
  },
  "10398": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the paintings in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is in a study."
  },
  "10399": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the paintings?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is near a bathroom and a living room."
  },
  "10400": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bottle look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:tall, glass, black"
  },
  "10401": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bottle?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the table, among four bottles and second from right"
  },
  "10402": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bottle in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bottle is set in the small kitchen."
  },
  "10403": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bottle?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is on the first floor and next to the livingroom. "
  },
  "10404": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black,tall,plastic and metal,with five wheels "
  },
  "10405": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of the desk,on the left side of the room,on the far left seat of the row"
  },
  "10406": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in a big simple shared office with the number 363."
  },
  "10407": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is along the road to the exit and around the corner of a junction of three roads."
  },
  "10408": {
    "question": "Question:what does the book look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:square, yellow and red, thin"
  },
  "10409": {
    "question": "Question:where is the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the stairs, on the third floor of the bookshelf"
  },
  "10410": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the book in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The book is set on the corridor."
  },
  "10411": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:The corridor is on the second floor and facing the stairs."
  },
  "10412": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Big, leather and gray and black."
  },
  "10413": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is set near two white and yellow chairs and a yellow and white table, and underneath a painting."
  },
  "10414": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is in a bedroom."
  },
  "10415": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is near a corridor and a living room."
  },
  "10416": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wood, cubic, brown"
  },
  "10417": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:between window and bed, under a book and a lamp"
  },
  "10418": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is set at a corner of the bedroom."
  },
  "10419": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:A living room is next to the bedroom"
  },
  "10420": {
    "question": "Question:what does the poster look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The poster is dark, square and big."
  },
  "10421": {
    "question": "Question:where is the poster?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a power switch on the opposite. There is a door besides."
  },
  "10422": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the poster in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The poster is placed on the opposite of the power switch next to the door."
  },
  "10423": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the poster?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are many posters in the corridor."
  },
  "10424": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Porcelain, small"
  },
  "10425": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is an identical sink on its right, right above it is a mirror."
  },
  "10426": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's installed in a bathroom."
  },
  "10427": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathroom is built in the main room which  faces the balcony. Right below the room is the swimming pool."
  },
  "10428": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, red, woody."
  },
  "10429": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are two chairs with the same state, colour on its right and one chair with the same state, colour on its left.There are five chairs with the same state, colour opposite to it."
  },
  "10430": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set on one side of the corridor via the altar."
  },
  "10431": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area has lots of benches on each side of corridor ."
  },
  "10432": {
    "question": "Question:what does the towel look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cotton, hanged adn spotted"
  },
  "10433": {
    "question": "Question:where is the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is beneath the window and next to the toliet."
  },
  "10434": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the towel in?",
    "answer": "Answer:\nIt is in a restroom on the second floor."
  },
  "10435": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The restroom is on the life side of the stairs."
  },
  "10436": {
    "question": "Question:what does the hinge look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, golden, stable"
  },
  "10437": {
    "question": "Question:where is the hinge?",
    "answer": "Answer:between a door and a wall, above another hinge"
  },
  "10438": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the hinge in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The hinge is on a wall in a washroom."
  },
  "10439": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the hinge?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washroom has two washbasins and a trashcan."
  },
  "10440": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is white, rectangular and wooden."
  },
  "10441": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is on the top of the oven and on the right side of the refrigerator."
  },
  "10442": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is in the kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "10443": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is on the top of the oven and on the right side of the refrigerator."
  },
  "10444": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is white, rectangular and wooden."
  },
  "10445": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is on the top of the oven and on the right side of the refrigerator."
  },
  "10446": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is in the kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "10447": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is on the top of the oven and on the right side of the refrigerator."
  },
  "10448": {
    "question": "Question:what does the fan look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A golden fan made of matel with white light bulbs."
  },
  "10449": {
    "question": "Question:where is the fan?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near the white air-conditioner and over the bed."
  },
  "10450": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the fan in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is just below the ceiling."
  },
  "10451": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the fan?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a toilet and two bedrooms."
  },
  "10452": {
    "question": "Question:what does the plant look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:tall,standing leaves,green"
  },
  "10453": {
    "question": "Question:where is the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a black box on the desk and surrounded by seven chairs"
  },
  "10454": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the plant in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The plant is put in the reading area."
  },
  "10455": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:The reading area is behind the restaurant and by the side of the booth."
  },
  "10456": {
    "question": "Question:what does the light look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Elliptical plastic white light"
  },
  "10457": {
    "question": "Question:where is the light?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed on the roof above a fluffy carpet."
  },
  "10458": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the light in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a storeroom on the roof."
  },
  "10459": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the light?",
    "answer": "Answer:This storeroom is located at the end of the right turn on the second floor."
  },
  "10460": {
    "question": "Question:what does the window look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, glass, bright"
  },
  "10461": {
    "question": "Question:where is the window?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the paintings and the bed "
  },
  "10462": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the window in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the children's bedroom."
  },
  "10463": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the window?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the study and the bathroom."
  },
  "10464": {
    "question": "Question:what does the drawer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is small, wooden and closed."
  },
  "10465": {
    "question": "Question:where is the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a mirror behind the drawer and some books on the drawer."
  },
  "10466": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the drawer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The drawer is placed against the mirror in the closet."
  },
  "10467": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the drawer?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are many clothes in the closet."
  },
  "10468": {
    "question": "Question:what does the telephone look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soild, metal and plastic and black."
  },
  "10469": {
    "question": "Question:where is the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:The telephone is between two beige sofa, near a beige desk and next to a white and brown lamp."
  },
  "10470": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the telephone in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The telephone is in a living room."
  },
  "10471": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the telephone?",
    "answer": "Answer:The telephone is near a corridor and a toilet."
  },
  "10472": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:dark yellow and brown,soft,short"
  },
  "10473": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of a purple sofa,on the left side of a plant and in the middle of the road"
  },
  "10474": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in the corridor and a rest area."
  },
  "10475": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is opposite to the exit,locker and the tea room,and it's at the corner of a road."
  },
  "10476": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, gray and white"
  },
  "10477": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:You can see a small pillow on the left side of the chair, and it's facing two beach chairs."
  },
  "10478": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in a second-floor balcony, which facing the main bedroom."
  },
  "10479": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The balcony is on the second floor of the villa, directly below the garden. "
  },
  "10480": {
    "question": "Question:what does the paintings look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Rectangular, soild and papery."
  },
  "10481": {
    "question": "Question:where is the paintings?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is in the first row and the third column of the six paintings and above a red and brown chair."
  },
  "10482": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the paintings in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is in a study."
  },
  "10483": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the paintings?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is near a bathroom."
  },
  "10484": {
    "question": "Question:what does the model look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black,small,bird-shaped"
  },
  "10485": {
    "question": "Question:where is the model?",
    "answer": "Answer:between some books,under the plants,in the first row and the second column of the first book shelf to the left of the locker"
  },
  "10486": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the model in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The model is in a large resting area."
  },
  "10487": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the model?",
    "answer": "Answer:The model faces a big meeting room at a slant and behind the restaurant."
  },
  "10488": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Big, brown and wooden."
  },
  "10489": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is near a brown wooden desk and a wooden dresser with a mirror, under a red blanket and two red pillows."
  },
  "10490": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is in a bedroom."
  },
  "10491": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is near a corridor."
  },
  "10492": {
    "question": "Question:what does the radio look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Metal,small,red"
  },
  "10493": {
    "question": "Question:where is the radio?",
    "answer": "Answer:The radio is placed in front of a window and behine a  roll of paper towels."
  },
  "10494": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the radio in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The radio is placed in a tearoom."
  },
  "10495": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the radio?",
    "answer": "Answer:The radio is placed near the hall and a reading room."
  },
  "10496": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, beautiful, light"
  },
  "10497": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the wall, above a picture"
  },
  "10498": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is on the wall in a study."
  },
  "10499": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a furnace in the corner of the study and the study is on the first floor."
  },
  "10500": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:yellow,small size,metal"
  },
  "10501": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a double bed and under a painting on the wall"
  },
  "10502": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a bedroom with a big washroom on the first floor"
  },
  "10503": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:the bedroom is near a corridor which is near a living room"
  },
  "10504": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:leather, black, smooth"
  },
  "10505": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:between a table and a stove with a television, between two small sofa"
  },
  "10506": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is set at the center of the living room."
  },
  "10507": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is surrounded by a kitchen and two bedrooms."
  },
  "10508": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:leather, black, smooth"
  },
  "10509": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:between a table and a stove with a television, between two small sofa"
  },
  "10510": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is set at the center of the living room."
  },
  "10511": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is surrounded by a kitchen and two bedrooms."
  },
  "10512": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:leather, black, smooth"
  },
  "10513": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:between a table and a stove with a television, between two small sofa"
  },
  "10514": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is set at the center of the living room."
  },
  "10515": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is surrounded by a kitchen and two bedrooms."
  },
  "10516": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:leather, black, smooth"
  },
  "10517": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:between a table and a stove with a television, between two small sofa"
  },
  "10518": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is set at the center of the living room."
  },
  "10519": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is surrounded by a kitchen and two bedrooms."
  },
  "10520": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown; with four lockers; wooden."
  },
  "10521": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:beside a big basket for used clothes.near a mirror with black rims."
  },
  "10522": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:against the wall opposite two mirrors."
  },
  "10523": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:a small changing room next to the men's."
  },
  "10524": {
    "question": "Question:what does the flower look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is white and tall."
  },
  "10525": {
    "question": "Question:where is the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is placed in the vase on the table."
  },
  "10526": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the flower in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is put in the vase facing the balcony in the kitchen."
  },
  "10527": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are many cabinets and sinks in the kitchen."
  },
  "10528": {
    "question": "Question:what does the flower look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is white and tall."
  },
  "10529": {
    "question": "Question:where is the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is placed in the vase on the table."
  },
  "10530": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the flower in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is put in the vase facing the balcony in the kitchen."
  },
  "10531": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are many cabinets and sinks in the kitchen."
  },
  "10532": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cup look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white,small,paper"
  },
  "10533": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cup?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cup is at the edge of the desk,on the left of a book and in front of the phone."
  },
  "10534": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cup in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cup is in the number 361 small office."
  },
  "10535": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cup?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is along the corridor leading to the exit and at the corner of a junction of three roads."
  },
  "10536": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, black, cloth"
  },
  "10537": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a bed, on a table"
  },
  "10538": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lamp is settled in the corner of a bedroom on the second floor."
  },
  "10539": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is next to a long corridor and has a small balcony."
  },
  "10540": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black,big,plastic and metal,with five wheels "
  },
  "10541": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:behind the table,in front of the cabinet"
  },
  "10542": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in a small office whose number is 362."
  },
  "10543": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is opposite to a public working office and has a path leading to the stairs on the left.\n"
  },
  "10544": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White, layered and with some bowls."
  },
  "10545": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is near a stool and there are some bowls in it."
  },
  "10546": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is in a kitchen."
  },
  "10547": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to a dining room and leads to outdoors via a door."
  },
  "10548": {
    "question": "Question:what does the switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A small white switch with four buttons."
  },
  "10549": {
    "question": "Question:where is the switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on a black wall near the washstand."
  },
  "10550": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the bathroom on the second floor."
  },
  "10551": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a hall and a toilet."
  },
  "10552": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black, small, bright"
  },
  "10553": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the small table and below the picture "
  },
  "10554": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the corridor"
  },
  "10555": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the living room and  on the second floor."
  },
  "10556": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:middle, black, square"
  },
  "10557": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the table, in front of the fireplace"
  },
  "10558": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is set in the bright kitchen."
  },
  "10559": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to the diningroom."
  },
  "10560": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bucket look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:steel, cylindrical and grey"
  },
  "10561": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bucket?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is placed on a cabinet and next to a glass bowl."
  },
  "10562": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bucket in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "10563": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bucket?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to the chatting room and the door."
  },
  "10564": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown, leather, short"
  },
  "10565": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the nightstand, under the window"
  },
  "10566": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is set in the small bedroom. "
  },
  "10567": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is in the end of the corridor and on the right of the end."
  },
  "10568": {
    "question": "Question:what does the hair dryer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Plastic, white and small."
  },
  "10569": {
    "question": "Question:where is the hair dryer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The hair dryer is on the wall, next to the table."
  },
  "10570": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the hair dryer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Hair dryer is in the bedroom."
  },
  "10571": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the hair dryer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The hairdryer is close to the bathroom and living room."
  },
  "10572": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:middle, wooden, brown"
  },
  "10573": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the table, next to the window, among three chairs and first from right"
  },
  "10574": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set in the bright kitchen."
  },
  "10575": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is on the first floor and next to the livingroom."
  },
  "10576": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, tall, large"
  },
  "10577": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer: faces another carbinet with the same shape and color and is next to the door of the clakroom and the bathroom"
  },
  "10578": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The carbinet is in the cloakroom."
  },
  "10579": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cloakroom is in the master bedroom and next to the bathroom."
  },
  "10580": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Porcelainous, white and big."
  },
  "10581": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is near a black and golden table and set between two paintings."
  },
  "10582": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is in a corridor on the first floor."
  },
  "10583": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is next to a toilet and a kitchen."
  },
  "10584": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A large mirror with a metal frame."
  },
  "10585": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on the gray wall and beside three white sinks."
  },
  "10586": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the bathroom and under light cabinets."
  },
  "10587": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on the second floor and near the corridor."
  },
  "10588": {
    "question": "Question:what does the curtain look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Gray, cloth and thin."
  },
  "10589": {
    "question": "Question:where is the curtain?",
    "answer": "Answer:The curtain is set on the right side of a black table under a black lamp and a black sculpture and near a white and brown bed."
  },
  "10590": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the curtain in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The curtain is in a bedroom."
  },
  "10591": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the curtain?",
    "answer": "Answer:The curtain is next to a bathroom."
  },
  "10592": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, wooden and three-tiered."
  },
  "10593": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are some decoration on the cabinet and a wash basin under the cabinet."
  },
  "10594": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is on a laundry."
  },
  "10595": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is connected with a kitchen and across from a toilet."
  },
  "10596": {
    "question": "Question:what does the dustbin look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:short,black,cuboid"
  },
  "10597": {
    "question": "Question:where is the dustbin?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the floor,between two desks,on the left side of the red box"
  },
  "10598": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the dustbin in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a large office whose number is 377."
  },
  "10599": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the dustbin?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is around the corner of a junction of three paths and on the left of the stairway door."
  },
  "10600": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown, rectangle and fluffy"
  },
  "10601": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is above the black carpet and next to the window."
  },
  "10602": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in living roon on the first floor."
  },
  "10603": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is the room facing the door."
  },
  "10604": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soild, medium size and red and beige."
  },
  "10605": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is the fifth one in a row of chairs from right to left while facing to the chairs, behind a red leather sofa and opposite to a brown wooden desk."
  },
  "10606": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set in a reception room on the first floor."
  },
  "10607": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is near a porch."
  },
  "10608": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Wooden and leather, soild and red and beige."
  },
  "10609": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is settled in the middle of the chairs row and it is on the opposite side to a tall mirror."
  },
  "10610": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in a reception room."
  },
  "10611": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is near a porch."
  },
  "10612": {
    "question": "Question:what does the toy bear look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, tall, black"
  },
  "10613": {
    "question": "Question:where is the toy bear?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the staircase and the plaid sofa"
  },
  "10614": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the toy bear in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the living room"
  },
  "10615": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the toy bear?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is on the second floor and next to the staircase and corridor."
  },
  "10616": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Arc-shaped, medium size and leather."
  },
  "10617": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is behind a brown table, near a small round table and a transparent table surrouded by six orange chairs."
  },
  "10618": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in a rest room."
  },
  "10619": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is near a kitchen."
  },
  "10620": {
    "question": "Question:what does the flower look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is small and colorful."
  },
  "10621": {
    "question": "Question:where is the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is above the flower. The sink is next to the flower."
  },
  "10622": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the flower in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The flower is placed upon the table in the kitchen."
  },
  "10623": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the flower?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are two big tables and a wine cabinet on the opposite of the flower."
  },
  "10624": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle, black and hanged"
  },
  "10625": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is hanging on the wall next to the piano and the stairs."
  },
  "10626": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in living roon on the first floor."
  },
  "10627": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is the room facing the door."
  },
  "10628": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wood, rectangular, tall"
  },
  "10629": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a wall, facing a door"
  },
  "10630": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is placed in a small cloakroom."
  },
  "10631": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The small cloakroom is between a corridor and a bashroom."
  },
  "10632": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bush look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:green plants,lush"
  },
  "10633": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bush?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a white bench a roiling.it's also in front of  flower bed and near the balcony"
  },
  "10634": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bush in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's located in a garden with a flower bed on the second floor"
  },
  "10635": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bush?",
    "answer": "Answer:the garden is near a balcony which is near a study room with a stair in the corner"
  },
  "10636": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bush look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:green plants,lush"
  },
  "10637": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bush?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a white bench a roiling.it's also in front of  flower bed and near the balcony"
  },
  "10638": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bush in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's located in a garden with a flower bed on the second floor"
  },
  "10639": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bush?",
    "answer": "Answer:the garden is near a balcony which is near a study room with a stair in the corner"
  },
  "10640": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, cylindrical and erect"
  },
  "10641": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is standing on the windowsill between the window and the bathtub."
  },
  "10642": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a restroom on the first floor."
  },
  "10643": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The restroom is in the bedroom which is at the right turn of the gate."
  },
  "10644": {
    "question": "Question:what does the light look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, round and plastic"
  },
  "10645": {
    "question": "Question:where is the light?",
    "answer": "Answer:The light is on the right of the morror and above the sink."
  },
  "10646": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the light in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a restroom on the second floor."
  },
  "10647": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the light?",
    "answer": "Answer:The restroom is on the life side of the stairs."
  },
  "10648": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:sponge,grey and single."
  },
  "10649": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is close to the white sofa and the desk."
  },
  "10650": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in the living room."
  },
  "10651": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:Behind the chair is toilet and the bedroom is near the sofa."
  },
  "10652": {
    "question": "Question:what does the painting look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Rectangular, soild and big."
  },
  "10653": {
    "question": "Question:where is the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is set on a white wall, above a black stove and near a beige sofa and a black long sofa."
  },
  "10654": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the painting in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is in a living room."
  },
  "10655": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is near a balcony and a dining room."
  },
  "10656": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is wooden, white and rectangular."
  },
  "10657": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is under the table and to the right of the oven."
  },
  "10658": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is in the kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "10659": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is under the table and to the right of the oven."
  },
  "10660": {
    "question": "Question:what does the wall lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:bright, white, transparent"
  },
  "10661": {
    "question": "Question:where is the wall lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:near the decorations, in the corner of a bedroom"
  },
  "10662": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the wall lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The wall lamp is in a small massage bedroom."
  },
  "10663": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the wall lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The massage bedroom has only one massage bed and some decorations on the wall. "
  },
  "10664": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A square  wooden stool with high legs."
  },
  "10665": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is beside a ring table and at  the middle of the table."
  },
  "10666": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the living room between two same stool."
  },
  "10667": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stool?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a stair and a storage room."
  },
  "10668": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bathtub look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White, large and porcelain."
  },
  "10669": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bathtub?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathtub is close to the towel rail."
  },
  "10670": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bathtub in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Bathtub in the bathroom."
  },
  "10671": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bathtub?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathtub is near the bedroom and toilet."
  },
  "10672": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:long,soft,and brown"
  },
  "10673": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's below a television and in front of a double bed."
  },
  "10674": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a big bedroom on the second floor."
  },
  "10675": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:the bedroom is next to a open-balcony and a living room."
  },
  "10676": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:cloth, rectangular, white"
  },
  "10677": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the carpet, next to the mirror, on the right side of the table"
  },
  "10678": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set in the middle of the dining room.\n"
  },
  "10679": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The dining room is on the third floor, facing the washroom and next to the kitchen."
  },
  "10680": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is leather, square and white."
  },
  "10681": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is to the left of the three sofas and to the right of the wall."
  },
  "10682": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in the lounge."
  },
  "10683": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is to the left of the three sofas and to the right of the wall."
  },
  "10684": {
    "question": "Question:what does the toilet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:smooth,stony,middle size"
  },
  "10685": {
    "question": "Question:where is the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a small bench and a white and small sculpture"
  },
  "10686": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the toilet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a washroom on the first floor"
  },
  "10687": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:the washroom is near a corridor which is near 2 bedrooms and a living room"
  },
  "10688": {
    "question": "Question:what does the light look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small , glass , light"
  },
  "10689": {
    "question": "Question:where is the light?",
    "answer": "Answer:under a fan , below the ceiling"
  },
  "10690": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the light in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The lights are located on the ceiling of the bedroom."
  },
  "10691": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the light?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is surrounded by by a bal, a living room and a bathroom."
  },
  "10692": {
    "question": "Question:what does the TV look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black and white,liquid crystal,rectangular"
  },
  "10693": {
    "question": "Question:where is the TV?",
    "answer": "Answer:The TV is on a black table and between a magazine and a white flowerpot."
  },
  "10694": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the TV in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The TV is set in the living room."
  },
  "10695": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the TV?",
    "answer": "Answer:The TV is next to a door and in front of the stairs."
  },
  "10696": {
    "question": "Question:what does the wall lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white;semicircular column; common"
  },
  "10697": {
    "question": "Question:where is the wall lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:beside a calligraphy work of Chinese characters; above a cabinet;"
  },
  "10698": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the wall lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:right opposite the door across a bed;"
  },
  "10699": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the wall lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:a room within a bathtub."
  },
  "10700": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Wooden, rectangular and brown."
  },
  "10701": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is near a small, tall and black table and under a white blanket with royal emblem pattern."
  },
  "10702": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is in a bedroom which has blue carpet."
  },
  "10703": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is near the study and a wooden stair which in the corridor."
  },
  "10704": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden, brown and layered."
  },
  "10705": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is under a big mirror and across from a big bed."
  },
  "10706": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is in a bedroom."
  },
  "10707": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom leads outdoors via a door and connects with a washroom."
  },
  "10708": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:ceramic, white, small"
  },
  "10709": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a picture, below a light"
  },
  "10710": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The vase is in a white and small bashroom."
  },
  "10711": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bashroom is between a gym and a bedroom."
  },
  "10712": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A small square glass mirror."
  },
  "10713": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is behind a sink , on the right of another mirror and faces a bathtub."
  },
  "10714": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a bathroom connected to a bedroom."
  },
  "10715": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a bedroom and an empty room."
  },
  "10716": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stove look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, grass, rectangle"
  },
  "10717": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stove?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the chair, next to the closet"
  },
  "10718": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stove in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stove is located in a bright bedroom."
  },
  "10719": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stove?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bedroom is next to the corridor on the second floor with balcony. "
  },
  "10720": {
    "question": "Question:what does the book look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Rectangular , paper, white."
  },
  "10721": {
    "question": "Question:where is the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a blanket next to the book and a white cabinet near it."
  },
  "10722": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the book in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The book is set on a brown desk which is close to the wall."
  },
  "10723": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area is located on the corner of the hall."
  },
  "10724": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is glass, black and rectangular."
  },
  "10725": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is on the wall and on the top of the sofa."
  },
  "10726": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is in the bedroom."
  },
  "10727": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:The picture is on the wall and on the top of the sofa."
  },
  "10728": {
    "question": "Question:what does the power switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is rectangular, small and white."
  },
  "10729": {
    "question": "Question:where is the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is on the wall and beside the door."
  },
  "10730": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the power switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is in the aisle."
  },
  "10731": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is on the wall and beside the door."
  },
  "10732": {
    "question": "Question:what does the door handle look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:silver, metal, door-mounted"
  },
  "10733": {
    "question": "Question:where is the door handle?",
    "answer": "Answer:hung on the door, next to the towel"
  },
  "10734": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the door handle in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the bathroom."
  },
  "10735": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the door handle?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is in a corner which is next to the dining room."
  },
  "10736": {
    "question": "Question:what does the computer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white,thin,metal,with a apple logo"
  },
  "10737": {
    "question": "Question:where is the computer?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the right side of the counter,on the left side of the box full of cards and in front of a chair"
  },
  "10738": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the computer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The computer is in the reception."
  },
  "10739": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the computer?",
    "answer": "Answer:The computer is opposite to the entrance and in front of the food bar."
  },
  "10740": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is black, rectangular and wooden."
  },
  "10741": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is under the sink and towel."
  },
  "10742": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is in the bathroom of the bedroom."
  },
  "10743": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is under the sink and towel."
  },
  "10744": {
    "question": "Question:what does the clock look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:tall, big woody"
  },
  "10745": {
    "question": "Question:where is the clock?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the green chair and the Union jack"
  },
  "10746": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the clock in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the living room"
  },
  "10747": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the clock?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the staircase and corridor."
  },
  "10748": {
    "question": "Question:what does the painting look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Papery, soild and rectangular."
  },
  "10749": {
    "question": "Question:where is the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is set near a green and blue painting and opposite to a fitness equipment."
  },
  "10750": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the painting in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is in a corridor."
  },
  "10751": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is near a bedroom and a laundry."
  },
  "10752": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wooden chair and cotton cushion\uff0csingle chair which is  \uff0cmedian size\uff0cancient style"
  },
  "10753": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:a carpet is put on the front door\uff0cand there is another same chair next to it"
  },
  "10754": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The wooden chair is placed hard by the wall\uff0cclose to brown carpet in the living room\uff0cwhich is clser to sofa."
  },
  "10755": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a dark color carpet placed on the floor of living room\uff0cand there are several sofas placed in it."
  },
  "10756": {
    "question": "Question:what does the fan look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A metal brown fan with three bulbs."
  },
  "10757": {
    "question": "Question:where is the fan?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is hung under the ceiling and near an air conditioning."
  },
  "10758": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the fan in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a bedroom."
  },
  "10759": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the fan?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a toilet and another bedroom."
  },
  "10760": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, soft, cloth"
  },
  "10761": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:next the rounded and short table, below to three paintings"
  },
  "10762": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the living room."
  },
  "10763": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the dining room and the kitchen."
  },
  "10764": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Leather, soild and beige."
  },
  "10765": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is near a tall lamp and a painting and behind a wooden and vitreous desk."
  },
  "10766": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in a living room."
  },
  "10767": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is near a corridor and a toilet."
  },
  "10768": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soild, small and beige and brown."
  },
  "10769": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is on the left side of a black wooden screen, near a table under the ivory sculpture and behind a beige sofa."
  },
  "10770": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in a living room."
  },
  "10771": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is on the opposite side of a corridor."
  },
  "10772": {
    "question": "Question:what does the power switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is white, plastic and small."
  },
  "10773": {
    "question": "Question:where is the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is next to the door and refrigerator."
  },
  "10774": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the power switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is in the kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "10775": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the power switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:The power switch is next to the door and refrigerator."
  },
  "10776": {
    "question": "Question:what does the printer look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black, heavy, small"
  },
  "10777": {
    "question": "Question:where is the printer?",
    "answer": "Answer:between a door and a window, above a box"
  },
  "10778": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the printer in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in a bright living room."
  },
  "10779": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the printer?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are some trees outside the living room and a television in the living room."
  },
  "10780": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:metal, blue, with roller."
  },
  "10781": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is under a table and a computer."
  },
  "10782": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in a study."
  },
  "10783": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:Opposite to the chair is the hallway."
  },
  "10784": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, white, cloth"
  },
  "10785": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a chair, facing a black table"
  },
  "10786": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is settled in a dining room on the first floor."
  },
  "10787": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The dining is next to a kitchen and a corridor."
  },
  "10788": {
    "question": "Question:what does the carbinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Woody, rectangular, big."
  },
  "10789": {
    "question": "Question:where is the carbinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are  some carpet inside the  cabinet  and a red suitcase in front of it ."
  },
  "10790": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the carbinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is set  at the  corner of  the room and  close to  the wall."
  },
  "10791": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the carbinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area  is located  on the corner  of  the hall and  has some  cabinets."
  },
  "10792": {
    "question": "Question:what does the racket look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Partly black and partly white, flat, woody"
  },
  "10793": {
    "question": "Question:where is the racket?",
    "answer": "Answer:The racket is on a table with a green top, near a ping-pong ball."
  },
  "10794": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the racket in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The racket is placed in the hall."
  },
  "10795": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the racket?",
    "answer": "Answer:The racket is placed next to a gate and next to a conference room."
  },
  "10796": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Beige and white, small and wooden."
  },
  "10797": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is set under a sculpture of a man riding an elephant and near a round table under a brown vase."
  },
  "10798": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is at the corner of a bedroom on the second floor."
  },
  "10799": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is settled on the opposite side of a narrow room with a carbinet."
  },
  "10800": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White,curved,tough."
  },
  "10801": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is hung on the wall and next to two green sofa."
  },
  "10802": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is set in a small bedroom."
  },
  "10803": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is placed near the hall and a tearoom."
  },
  "10804": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is soft, leathery and white."
  },
  "10805": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is on the right of one sofa and the left of two sofas."
  },
  "10806": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in the entertainment hall.\n"
  },
  "10807": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is on the right of one sofa and the left of two sofas."
  },
  "10808": {
    "question": "Question:what does the towel look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown, cotton, soft"
  },
  "10809": {
    "question": "Question:where is the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:Hanging on the armrest of the glass door by the bathtub, hang above the toilet."
  },
  "10810": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the towel in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is installed on a small washing room."
  },
  "10811": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washing room is built in a small bright bedroom which has the main bedroom on one side and the laundry on the other."
  },
  "10812": {
    "question": "Question:what does the hourglass look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:limpid,glass,containing blue sand"
  },
  "10813": {
    "question": "Question:where is the hourglass?",
    "answer": "Answer:on two books and a shelf,on the right of a model plane"
  },
  "10814": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the hourglass in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The hourglass is in a big meeting room with the number 05."
  },
  "10815": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the hourglass?",
    "answer": "Answer:The meeting room is by the side of the reading area and behind the restaurant."
  },
  "10816": {
    "question": "Question:what does the painting look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Papery and wooden, medium size and rectangular."
  },
  "10817": {
    "question": "Question:where is the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is near a big desk, on the right side of a big beige sofa and near a tall lamp."
  },
  "10818": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the painting in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is in a living room."
  },
  "10819": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the painting?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is near a corridor and a toilet."
  },
  "10820": {
    "question": "Question:what does the book look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:thin, paper books, rectangular"
  },
  "10821": {
    "question": "Question:where is the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a clock, on the fifth layer of a shelf"
  },
  "10822": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the book in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The books are settled in a study."
  },
  "10823": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:The study has two chairs and it is on the first floor. "
  },
  "10824": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:midnight blue, big, rectangular"
  },
  "10825": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is next to another sofa with the same color and shape. There are three throw pillows on the sofa.The sofa is between two lamps."
  },
  "10826": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in the centre of the living room."
  },
  "10827": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in the second floor and in front of the door which opens outwards."
  },
  "10828": {
    "question": "Question:what does the television look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big,mental,black"
  },
  "10829": {
    "question": "Question:where is the television?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's above a chair and in front of a double bed."
  },
  "10830": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the television in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a big bedroom on the second floor."
  },
  "10831": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the television?",
    "answer": "Answer:the bedroom is next to a open-balcony and  a living room."
  },
  "10832": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle\uff0ccotton\uff0cpurple and white"
  },
  "10833": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:there are some pillows put on the head of the big bed\uff0cand a long grey couch is put at the end of it"
  },
  "10834": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bed is put at the center of big bedroom\uff0cwhich is placed close to the balcony, opposite the wooden cabinet."
  },
  "10835": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is shower room and a small work place in the big bedroom\uff0cand a carpet is placed close to the bed."
  },
  "10836": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A lamp with white lampshade and golden base."
  },
  "10837": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on a black table and beside a green plant in a black pot."
  },
  "10838": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a living room."
  },
  "10839": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a stair to a kitchen and a balcony."
  },
  "10840": {
    "question": "Question:what does the toaster look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The toaster is grey, irony and small."
  },
  "10841": {
    "question": "Question:where is the toaster?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a microwave besides. There is a cabinet above."
  },
  "10842": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the toaster in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The toaster is placed next to the microwave below the cabinet near the toilet."
  },
  "10843": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the toaster?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a sink, toilet and mirror in the toilet."
  },
  "10844": {
    "question": "Question:what does the stapler look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:metal case,black and white,tiny"
  },
  "10845": {
    "question": "Question:where is the stapler?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stapler is in the middle room of the cabinet and next to  the bookbinding machine and in front of a sharpener."
  },
  "10846": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the stapler in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stapler is in  a tea room at the end of the corridor."
  },
  "10847": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the stapler?",
    "answer": "Answer:The stapler is near the stairs of exit and opposite to a room which is not permitted to entry."
  },
  "10848": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:oval;white with grey stripes;small;"
  },
  "10849": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:below two brown taps; against a blue wall;"
  },
  "10850": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the left and close to the door of this washing room;"
  },
  "10851": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:a room specially used for washing and with many sinks."
  },
  "10852": {
    "question": "Question:what does the window look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:closed , large , transparent"
  },
  "10853": {
    "question": "Question:where is the window?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the wall of the bathroom , next to the toilet"
  },
  "10854": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the window in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The window is located on the wall of the bathroom."
  },
  "10855": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the window?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathroom is inside of the bedroom."
  },
  "10856": {
    "question": "Question:what does the plant look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:porcelain, cylindroid"
  },
  "10857": {
    "question": "Question:where is the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:Next to it is a ceramic pot with no plants.There is a glass table next to it"
  },
  "10858": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the plant in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It was placed in a corner of the reception area."
  },
  "10859": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the plant?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area faces the open kitchen, next to the pool, and dinning table on the other side."
  },
  "10860": {
    "question": "Question:what does the switch look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangle, white, plastic"
  },
  "10861": {
    "question": "Question:where is the switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:Next to the door.  There is a bathtub on its right side."
  },
  "10862": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the switch in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's installed in a bathroom's wall."
  },
  "10863": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the switch?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathroom is built in the main room which  faces the balcony. Right below the room is the swimming pool."
  },
  "10864": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, filmy, medium"
  },
  "10865": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:above a washbasin, next to the window of the bathroom"
  },
  "10866": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is in the bathroom."
  },
  "10867": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bathroom is next to the cloakroom and in the master bedroom."
  },
  "10868": {
    "question": "Question:what does the curtain look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big and long,large,blue"
  },
  "10869": {
    "question": "Question:where is the curtain?",
    "answer": "Answer:behind the door and two chairs,on the right side of the gate"
  },
  "10870": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the curtain in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The curtain is in a large office owning the number 377."
  },
  "10871": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the curtain?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is at the corner of a junction of three roads and on the left of the stairway door."
  },
  "10872": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:umbrella,metal and decorated"
  },
  "10873": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's between the armchair and the piano"
  },
  "10874": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in dinning room "
  },
  "10875": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:there is study next to the dinning room."
  },
  "10876": {
    "question": "Question:what does the toilet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:ceramic ,white,and hard"
  },
  "10877": {
    "question": "Question:where is the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a white washstand and a mirror."
  },
  "10878": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the toilet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in a washroom  on the second floor."
  },
  "10879": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the toilet?",
    "answer": "Answer:the washroom is next to a stair,a living room and a rest room."
  },
  "10880": {
    "question": "Question:what does the wine barrel look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:An old wooden columnal wine barrel with a tap on it."
  },
  "10881": {
    "question": "Question:where is the wine barrel?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is beside a linen container and a two-wheeled trolley."
  },
  "10882": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the wine barrel in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is under the stairs."
  },
  "10883": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the wine barrel?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near the living room."
  },
  "10884": {
    "question": "Question:what does the desk look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Wooden and vitreous, big and beige."
  },
  "10885": {
    "question": "Question:where is the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:The desk is surrounded by two sofas, opposite to a black television and near a painting."
  },
  "10886": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the desk in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The desk is in a living room."
  },
  "10887": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the desk?",
    "answer": "Answer:The desk is near a corridor and a toilet."
  },
  "10888": {
    "question": "Question:what does the paintings look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Papery, big and golden."
  },
  "10889": {
    "question": "Question:where is the paintings?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is set above two brown chairs, on the white wall and on the opposite side of a cuboid table."
  },
  "10890": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the paintings in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is set in a dining room."
  },
  "10891": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the paintings?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is near a kitchen."
  },
  "10892": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bin look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rufous;with a lid; small;"
  },
  "10893": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bin?",
    "answer": "Answer:beside the door of the washroom; opposite  a big basket."
  },
  "10894": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bin in?",
    "answer": "Answer:at the corner of the women's changing room."
  },
  "10895": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bin?",
    "answer": "Answer:a room with two identical cabinets."
  },
  "10896": {
    "question": "Question:what does the closestool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, normal size"
  },
  "10897": {
    "question": "Question:where is the closestool?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the woody door, below the grown towels"
  },
  "10898": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the closestool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the bathroom which is in the bedroom"
  },
  "10899": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the closestool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the living room and on the second floor."
  },
  "10900": {
    "question": "Question:what does the pillow look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, cloth, square"
  },
  "10901": {
    "question": "Question:where is the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the long sofa, among six sofas and second from left"
  },
  "10902": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the pillow in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The pillow is set in the livingroom."
  },
  "10903": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the pillow?",
    "answer": "Answer:The livingroom is on the first floor and next to the kitchen and dining room."
  },
  "10904": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:wood, brown, long"
  },
  "10905": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:under knives and the rice cooker, next to the fridge"
  },
  "10906": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is set at a side of the kitchen."
  },
  "10907": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is connected with the living room."
  },
  "10908": {
    "question": "Question:what does the wall look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, rough"
  },
  "10909": {
    "question": "Question:where is the wall?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the stair armrest, next to the stair."
  },
  "10910": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the wall in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the corner which is between the first floor and the second floor."
  },
  "10911": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the wall?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is above the kitchen and below the corridor."
  },
  "10912": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:dark,sponge,soft"
  },
  "10913": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a round same style stool , a same kind of chair and a tall lamp"
  },
  "10914": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's near a study room door where links a balcony on the second floor"
  },
  "10915": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:the study room is near a balcony and a stair"
  },
  "10916": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bush look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, green, alive"
  },
  "10917": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bush?",
    "answer": "Answer:set in the white flowerpot, above the white table surrounded by eight white chairs."
  },
  "10918": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bush in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The bush is in the dining room."
  },
  "10919": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bush?",
    "answer": "Answer:The dining room is in front of the kitchen and next to the study and the bathroom on the second floor."
  },
  "10920": {
    "question": "Question:what does the towel look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is rectangular, white and soft."
  },
  "10921": {
    "question": "Question:where is the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel hangs on the shelf and is on the left side of the pool."
  },
  "10922": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the towel in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel is inside the bathroom."
  },
  "10923": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the towel?",
    "answer": "Answer:The towel hangs on the shelf and is on the left side of the pool."
  },
  "10924": {
    "question": "Question:what does the vase look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, cylindrical, fragile"
  },
  "10925": {
    "question": "Question:where is the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the cabinet, next to the wall"
  },
  "10926": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the vase in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the corridor."
  },
  "10927": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the vase?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the bathroom and the study."
  },
  "10928": {
    "question": "Question:what does the wall look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:White, vertical and clean."
  },
  "10929": {
    "question": "Question:where is the wall?",
    "answer": "Answer:The wall is behind the door, next to the vase."
  },
  "10930": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the wall in?",
    "answer": "Answer:Wall is in the living room."
  },
  "10931": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the wall?",
    "answer": "Answer:The wall is close to the balcony and toilet."
  },
  "10932": {
    "question": "Question:what does the projector look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A white metal long projector."
  },
  "10933": {
    "question": "Question:where is the projector?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is beneath the ceiling and close to the stone wall."
  },
  "10934": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the projector in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the living room."
  },
  "10935": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the projector?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a desk and several sofas."
  },
  "10936": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Yellow,rectangular,wooden."
  },
  "10937": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is placed next to a black box with a bundle of black wire on it"
  },
  "10938": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is placed in the front desk."
  },
  "10939": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is placed near the hall and the gate."
  },
  "10940": {
    "question": "Question:what does the paintings look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Papery, rectangular and soild."
  },
  "10941": {
    "question": "Question:where is the paintings?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is in the second row, the first column of the six paintings and above two red and brown chairs."
  },
  "10942": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the paintings in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is in a study."
  },
  "10943": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the paintings?",
    "answer": "Answer:The painting is near a living room."
  },
  "10944": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bush look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:green,red and lush "
  },
  "10945": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bush?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's next to a stone lion and roiling"
  },
  "10946": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bush in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in the corner of a garden on the second floor"
  },
  "10947": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bush?",
    "answer": "Answer:the garden is near a balcony and the balcony is near a study room with a stair"
  },
  "10948": {
    "question": "Question:what does the glass door look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:its bulk is made of glass and its frame is made of iron, its frame is black, its size is not very big ,median size "
  },
  "10949": {
    "question": "Question:where is the glass door?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a white cabinet placed next to the glass door, and a rectangle table is placed nearby "
  },
  "10950": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the glass door in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The glass door is placed close to a white bookcase in the dining room."
  },
  "10951": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the glass door?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a big mirror put on the wall of dining room ,and a table close to the glass door."
  },
  "10952": {
    "question": "Question:what does the piano look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Soild, brown and wooden."
  },
  "10953": {
    "question": "Question:where is the piano?",
    "answer": "Answer:The piano is under two pictures with golden borders and near a brown wooden door."
  },
  "10954": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the piano in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The piano is at the corner of a living room."
  },
  "10955": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the piano?",
    "answer": "Answer:The piano is near a dining room."
  },
  "10956": {
    "question": "Question:what does the swimming pool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, hollow, large "
  },
  "10957": {
    "question": "Question:where is the swimming pool?",
    "answer": "Answer:near decorations, next to a potted plant"
  },
  "10958": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the swimming pool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The swimming pool is in a gymnasium."
  },
  "10959": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the swimming pool?",
    "answer": "Answer:The gymnasium connect with two washrooms and massage bedrooms."
  },
  "10960": {
    "question": "Question:what does the photo look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Colorful, small and rectangular."
  },
  "10961": {
    "question": "Question:where is the photo?",
    "answer": "Answer:The photo is settled next to a white and red bed and some books and near a black fitness equipment."
  },
  "10962": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the photo in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The photo is in a bedroom."
  },
  "10963": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the photo?",
    "answer": "Answer:The photo is near a corridor."
  },
  "10964": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, cloth, white"
  },
  "10965": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a chair, facing a table"
  },
  "10966": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in the center of a big and bright dining room."
  },
  "10967": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The kitchen is next to a kitchen and there is a bathroom upstairs."
  },
  "10968": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, circle, made of glass"
  },
  "10969": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is set in a table. A bigger sink is left to it. A small mirror is right to it. "
  },
  "10970": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is in a bathroom."
  },
  "10971": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:Opposite to the sink is a shower room."
  },
  "10972": {
    "question": "Question:what does the armchair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:stand on the floor,red,leathery"
  },
  "10973": {
    "question": "Question:where is the armchair?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the table and in front of a painting"
  },
  "10974": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the armchair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in a family cinema"
  },
  "10975": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the armchair?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's close to the toilet"
  },
  "10976": {
    "question": "Question:what does the book look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:yellow, rectangular, paper"
  },
  "10977": {
    "question": "Question:where is the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a flower, on a tea table"
  },
  "10978": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the book in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The book is placed in the center of a small living room with wood floor."
  },
  "10979": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is facing a big and white living room and is connected with a small dining room."
  },
  "10980": {
    "question": "Question:what does the picture look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A small black picture "
  },
  "10981": {
    "question": "Question:where is the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on the right side of a window and under another black picture."
  },
  "10982": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the picture in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a big room with a balcony."
  },
  "10983": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the picture?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a bed and a black desk."
  },
  "10984": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a blue, square sofa chair filled with cotton.\n"
  },
  "10985": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a table and stool in front of it.\n"
  },
  "10986": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's in a living room."
  },
  "10987": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's beside a kitchen."
  },
  "10988": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is rectangular, large and white."
  },
  "10989": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is behind the door and close to the corner."
  },
  "10990": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is in the kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "10991": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is behind the door and close to the corner."
  },
  "10992": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a brown, wooden round table lamp."
  },
  "10993": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on a table next to a desk lamp."
  },
  "10994": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a living room.\n"
  },
  "10995": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:This is a clean, tidy and spacious living room.\n"
  },
  "10996": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, middle, brown"
  },
  "10997": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the kitchen, next to the sofa, on the right of the main entrance"
  },
  "10998": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set in the bright and spacious livingroom."
  },
  "10999": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The livingroom is on the first floor and next to a washroom and kitchen."
  },
  "11000": {
    "question": "Question:what does the kitchen ventilator look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A metal kitchen ventilator with some lights."
  },
  "11001": {
    "question": "Question:where is the kitchen ventilator?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is over a gas stove and between two white cabinets."
  },
  "11002": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the kitchen ventilator in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a kitchen."
  },
  "11003": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the kitchen ventilator?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a dining room and a living room."
  },
  "11004": {
    "question": "Question:what does the cabinet look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is white, large and rectangular."
  },
  "11005": {
    "question": "Question:where is the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is above the eggs and the table."
  },
  "11006": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the cabinet in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is in the kitchen on the first floor."
  },
  "11007": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the cabinet?",
    "answer": "Answer:The cabinet is above the eggs and the table."
  },
  "11008": {
    "question": "Question:what does the tripod look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Silvery white, hard, metallic"
  },
  "11009": {
    "question": "Question:where is the tripod?",
    "answer": "Answer:The tripod is placed on the ground,next to a yellow box and a black loudspeaker box."
  },
  "11010": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the tripod in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The tripod is set in the hall."
  },
  "11011": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the tripod?",
    "answer": "Answer:The tripod is placed next to a wall and near the gate."
  },
  "11012": {
    "question": "Question:what does the furnace look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, white, heavy"
  },
  "11013": {
    "question": "Question:where is the furnace?",
    "answer": "Answer:under the pictures, next to a door "
  },
  "11014": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the furnace in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The furnace is in the corner of the study."
  },
  "11015": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the furnace?",
    "answer": "Answer:The study has a fan in the center and two pictures on the wall."
  },
  "11016": {
    "question": "Question:what does the tv look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, black, thin"
  },
  "11017": {
    "question": "Question:where is the tv?",
    "answer": "Answer:on the white table, next to the French window, in front of the sofa"
  },
  "11018": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the tv in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The TV is in the living room."
  },
  "11019": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the tv?",
    "answer": "Answer:The living room is in front of the dining room and next to the balcony."
  },
  "11020": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, normal size, fragile"
  },
  "11021": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the sofa, on the woody table"
  },
  "11022": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the living room."
  },
  "11023": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the kitchen and the dining room."
  },
  "11024": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sofa look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:circular, cotton and brown"
  },
  "11025": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is close to the window and next to the cabinet."
  },
  "11026": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sofa in?",
    "answer": "Answer:\nIt is in a chatting room on the first floor."
  },
  "11027": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sofa?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chatting room is next to the hall."
  },
  "11028": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black,erect,five wheels,plastic and metal,two handrails"
  },
  "11029": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is on the right side of the other same chair,on the right of socket and on the left of the window."
  },
  "11030": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is in  an empty office whose number is 355."
  },
  "11031": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The office is at the end of the corridor and seperated to a six person office by a glass wall."
  },
  "11032": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is large, ceramic and white."
  },
  "11033": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is under the towel and flower."
  },
  "11034": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is in the bathroom."
  },
  "11035": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sink is under the towel and flower."
  },
  "11036": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A four-leg wooden chair with yellow cushion."
  },
  "11037": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a small cabinet and close to a short stone wall."
  },
  "11038": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the bedroom."
  },
  "11039": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near a toilet."
  },
  "11040": {
    "question": "Question:what does the door look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Normal, white rectangle door"
  },
  "11041": {
    "question": "Question:where is the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is on the right side of the main door and next to a shelf."
  },
  "11042": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the door in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in a storeroom."
  },
  "11043": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:This storeroom is located at the end of the right turn on the second floor."
  },
  "11044": {
    "question": "Question:what does the bed look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big, soft, "
  },
  "11045": {
    "question": "Question:where is the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:below the bed net, next to the window"
  },
  "11046": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the bed in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the bedroom"
  },
  "11047": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the bed?",
    "answer": "Answer:The area is next to the living room and on the second floor."
  },
  "11048": {
    "question": "Question:what does the lamp look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:medium-size,white,on the table"
  },
  "11049": {
    "question": "Question:where is the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's on the table and on the left of the bed"
  },
  "11050": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the lamp in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in bedroom"
  },
  "11051": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the lamp?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's close to the door to the kitchen"
  },
  "11052": {
    "question": "Question:what does the light look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, glass"
  },
  "11053": {
    "question": "Question:where is the light?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a mirror behind the light, and the plant is under the light."
  },
  "11054": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the light in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's installed in the toilet."
  },
  "11055": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the light?",
    "answer": "Answer:The toilet is on the first floor of the villa, on its left is the garden and on its right is the swimming pool."
  },
  "11056": {
    "question": "Question:what does the washbasin look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:rectangular, hollow, white"
  },
  "11057": {
    "question": "Question:where is the washbasin?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a trashcan, next to a hair dryer"
  },
  "11058": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the washbasin in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washbasin is in a man washroom and there is another same washbasin on its right."
  },
  "11059": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the washbasin?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are a hair dryer and a trashcan in the man washroom."
  },
  "11060": {
    "question": "Question:what does the door look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:woody, tall, opaque"
  },
  "11061": {
    "question": "Question:where is the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to a furnace, next to a picture"
  },
  "11062": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the door in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is settled in a small study."
  },
  "11063": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the door?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area has a big table in the center and some boxes on the table. "
  },
  "11064": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is small, round and glass."
  },
  "11065": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is besides. The flower is on the sofa."
  },
  "11066": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is placed next to the sofa in the living room."
  },
  "11067": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a big sofa, chairs and tables in the living room."
  },
  "11068": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:black; long; deck chair;"
  },
  "11069": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:in the middle of two identical end tables; near  the swimming pool;"
  },
  "11070": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:counting from right to left, it's the second one;"
  },
  "11071": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:against a wall hanging three pictures;"
  },
  "11072": {
    "question": "Question:what does the closestool look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:porcelain; closed; white;"
  },
  "11073": {
    "question": "Question:where is the closestool?",
    "answer": "Answer:in the middle of a metal cabin and the racks for roll papers; near a sink below a mirror;"
  },
  "11074": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the closestool in?",
    "answer": "Answer:inside a small room towards a door and against the wall."
  },
  "11075": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the closestool?",
    "answer": "Answer:a small washroom belongs to a changing room;"
  },
  "11076": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:big,leaher,brown"
  },
  "11077": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's behind the table and in front of the computer"
  },
  "11078": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's in the study"
  },
  "11079": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:it's dining room"
  },
  "11080": {
    "question": "Question:what does the table look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:brown, rectangle, wooden"
  },
  "11081": {
    "question": "Question:where is the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:in front of a bed, beside a French windows"
  },
  "11082": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the table in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The table is put in a spacious and bright bedroom"
  },
  "11083": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the table?",
    "answer": "Answer:The balcony is next to the bedroom. It is located in the second floor and there is a swimming pool downstairs. "
  },
  "11084": {
    "question": "Question:what does the light look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Cylindrical,big,plastic"
  },
  "11085": {
    "question": "Question:where is the light?",
    "answer": "Answer:The light is placed near a green sofa and next to a book shelf."
  },
  "11086": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the light in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The light is set in a small bed room."
  },
  "11087": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the light?",
    "answer": "Answer:The light is placed next to the hall and a tearoom."
  },
  "11088": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:A medium-sized wooden chair with a backrest."
  },
  "11089": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is in the middle of two chairs which are the same to itself and it is located by a table."
  },
  "11090": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the dining room and there is a closet behind it."
  },
  "11091": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is near the stairs and faces a door."
  },
  "11092": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is big, black and leather."
  },
  "11093": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:The sofa is in front of the chair. The recliner is next to the chair."
  },
  "11094": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is placed behind the table next to the recliner in the room."
  },
  "11095": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are two tables, sofa and recliner in the room."
  },
  "11096": {
    "question": "Question:what does the mirror look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is white, glass and rectangular."
  },
  "11097": {
    "question": "Question:where is the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is on the wall and above the pool."
  },
  "11098": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the mirror in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is in the bedroom bathroom."
  },
  "11099": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the mirror?",
    "answer": "Answer:The mirror is on the wall and above the pool."
  },
  "11100": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:white, rectangle, porcelain"
  },
  "11101": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer: Below the sink is a cabinet, and it face another big cabinet. There is a mirror right above it."
  },
  "11102": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is installed on a small washing room."
  },
  "11103": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The washing room is built in a small bright bedroom which has the main bedroom on one side and the laundry on the other."
  },
  "11104": {
    "question": "Question:what does the book look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Pink, thick, paper"
  },
  "11105": {
    "question": "Question:where is the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:The book is under a cap and on top of the table surrounded by three chairs.\n "
  },
  "11106": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the book in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The book is set in the hall."
  },
  "11107": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the book?",
    "answer": "Answer:The book is placed near a wall and the gate."
  },
  "11108": {
    "question": "Question:what does the chair look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:Small, rectangular ,red."
  },
  "11109": {
    "question": "Question:where is the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:There are three chairs with the same size and state on its right and five chairs with the same size and state opposite to the chair."
  },
  "11110": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the chair in?",
    "answer": "Answer:The chair is set on one side of the corridor via the altar."
  },
  "11111": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the chair?",
    "answer": "Answer:This area has a fan and lots of benches on each side of the corridor ."
  },
  "11112": {
    "question": "Question:what does the glass door look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:glass, rectangular, transparent"
  },
  "11113": {
    "question": "Question:where is the glass door?",
    "answer": "Answer:next to the bed, next to the white lamp"
  },
  "11114": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the glass door in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It is located in the bedroom."
  },
  "11115": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the glass door?",
    "answer": "Answer:There is a rectangular balcony, a cloakroom, a washroom and a toilet in the bedroom. "
  },
  "11116": {
    "question": "Question:what does the sink look like?",
    "answer": "Answer:small, white, rectangle"
  },
  "11117": {
    "question": "Question:where is the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's right under the mirror and the tap."
  },
  "11118": {
    "question": "Question:which room or area is the sink in?",
    "answer": "Answer:It's installed in the toilet."
  },
  "11119": {
    "question": "Question:how to find the sink?",
    "answer": "Answer:The toilet is on the first floor of the villa, on its left is the garden and on its right is the swimming pool."
  }
}